<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<doc>
	<!--Arg: Creddit-->
	<arguments>
		<backgroundColor>bkgCreddit</backgroundColor>
		<headerColor>hdrCreddit</headerColor>
		<logo>logoCreddit</logo>

		<!--arg 0-->
		<argument>
			<text>While on the pick up artist subreddit, you gave some random AFC advice on how to pick up women: if you want to attract a girl at a bar, you need to dress like a true gentlesir and stay in the corner ignoring everybody while trying to look mysterious. Your advice was so euphoric, that the other pick up artists started to call you out! They said that method of pick up is outdated; "Nobody would approach you if you did that". In order to regain your PUA cred, you can either:</text>
			<choiceA>Post a fabricated story where you game on 2 Asian women and took both of them home in one night</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Call everyone unintelligent beta males and say that they will never understand how alpha you are</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The AFC acknowledges your superior game and comments that he aspires to be a man like you one day. He ended up buying a fedora and an untailored suit in your honor.</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The other men in the thread all call you pathetic and you can feel the AFC shake his head at you in disappointment through the internet.</responseWrong>
			<hint>I wouldn't appreciate being called an unintelligent beta male</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 7-->
		<argument>
			<text>While perusing the gonewild subcreddit, you saw an image of a lovely lady bent over her desk naked as the day she was born. You can tell this girl's special. Feeling the need to defend her honor from the horde of horny creeps and pervy comments, you write "These boys are quick to comment on your physical perfection. I'm not like them; your personality is the most breathtaking part of you." However, your post is getting downvoted! They are calling you a "chump knight" and say that you are missing the point of the subcreddit. As this fair maiden's white knight, you must lift up your shield:</text>
			<choiceA>Call all of the horny creeps who frequent gonewild virgins who can't get any</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"M'lady deserves a real man who can admire her beauty! I tip my fedora to her."</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Your original post got downvoted into oblivion. It's almost as if it never even existed! ARGUMENT IGNORED</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Your insult backfires as they start calling you a virgin who can't get any. How the hell did they figure that out? Are they stalking your MyFace page?! HEART BROKEN :(</responseWrong>
			<hint>You know what they say: you are what you make fun of. So don't</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 16-->
		<argument>
			<text>Obsessively partaking in the social networking website creddit, you were searching  for the answers to one of life's biggest questions: why do nice guys finish last? And by search I mean you wrote a whiny essay where you complain about how nice guys finish last, douchebags always win, and how the women are missing out for not choosing to date you. After submitting your soliloquy, you read the replies and they disagree with you! The common response was "Nice guys don't finish last, boring guys do". Wiping away your nice guy tears, you type your response:</text>
			<choiceA>Lie about yourself; "I am not a boring guy! I know kenjutsu and I am writing a book!"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"You guys are wrong. It's a scientific fact" and send them a link to an article that will augment your argument</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>You may have only learned kenjutsu through online videos and am writing a fanfiction about ponies, but they fall for your bluff. They suggest that rather than whine about your dateless life, you should focus on your passions. I mean... at least nobody is yelling at you? LIFE LESSONS FOR THE WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>You linked to an outdated late 90's article written by a has-been pick up artist. It had sexy pop-ups, uses the Comic-sans font, and it hurt your argument more than it helped. Research more next time :| ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>They don't know your life! They don't know what you've been through</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 17-->
		<argument>
			<text>Browsing through the social networking site creddit, you stumbled upon the thread "European vs. Japanese Swords". You scoff at the morons who believe European swords stand a chance against the glorious Nippon blade, however it's actually a fairly even argument. One posted a 4 paragraph essay explaining why European swords are stronger; the European design craft a more sturdy blade due to science and physics! Someone on the internet brought great dishonor to your favorite weapon of warfare. After all, you studied the blade:</text>
			<choiceA>"I am an expert with the katana and let me learn you a little bit of something about the lightning fast Iai style..."</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"Nippon steel is the strongest steel. The blacksmiths fold it 1000 times. Do you even know what tempering is, filthy Gaijin?"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The commenter does mention that yes, a katana can strike much faster than a European blade. He mentioned that it's not gonna penetrate European armor, but at this point you don't care as it's a WIN OF AN ARGUMENT!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The commenter linked you to a scientific experiment clip on LouTube of a European blade shattering a katana. When it was the katana's turn to strike the European blade, it actually cracked itself just like your heart did when you LOST THE ARGUMENT :(</responseWrong>
			<hint>I dunno, the facts are there. What does the katana even have going for it?</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 22-->
		<argument>
			<text>While on the social networking site creddit, you were looking at images of lovely ladies on the gonewild subcreddit. You saw one picture of a woman of Asian descent and instantly fell in love. You started to type a personal message to M'lady to woo her. "I'd love to get to know you better :)" After a few minutes, she still hasn't replied to which you started messaging her reasons why she should date you. Finally she replies with: "I'm busy." Clearly you deserve a better response than that! You start to put in everything you have into a last ditch effort to win her over:</text>
			<choiceA>Demonstrate higher value! "I am a hardworking man who can provide for you, m'lady."</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Neg her; lower her defense then sweep her off her feet! "I'd talk to you you, but you're not into nice guys!"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"I am. I just have no interest in you." Did m'lady just confirm she likes nice guys?! Maybe one of these days, she will have interest in you! ARGUMENT STRETCHED TO A WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"What the hell is wrong with you? Do you try that line on girls in person? Creep." I don't know what you were thinking please stop this. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>You? Hardworking?! Since when?!</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 35-->
		<argument>
			<text>Feeling more entitled than usual on the social networking site creddit, you made a post; "I am sick of being a nice guy! I helped a girl pass a class in college and she didn't even date me! I'm going to be an alpha male because that's what girls like!" Immediately your post was hit with people bashing your views: "Just because you helped a girl doesn't mean she owes you anything. The fact she didn't like you doesn't have anything to being an alpha male." Such an ignorant thing to say coming out of the lips of an alpha! Being an alpha male means everything:</text>
			<choiceA>"I'll show you... I'll show all of you!" then create a new account with the word Alpha in the name</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"You guys don't know what you are talking about! Why am I single then?"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Well I mean they don't know your new account and you avoided the original thread. Your quest to being an alpha male has begun with your new creddit account! You're feeling really good about yourself now! ARGUMENT AVOIDED</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"You are single because you are a bitter passive-aggressive beta male. I suggest speaking to a therapist because clearly you have some issues you need to sort through." You don't need to go to a therapist... alpha males don't believe in that! ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>The truth can sometime hurt more than it can ever heal...</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 39-->
		<argument>
			<text>While on the social networking site creddit, you uploaded a photo that you've worked hard on! You took four photos of yourself and created a four panel comic. In the comic, you added the text "Hai girls! Umm... did you know that when you wear make up nice guys think you're ugly?" You just wanted to make a statement that natural beauty is the best beauty! Thinking that this was your key to fame, you were shocked when it was hit with negative criticism! "This must be a joke! Please tell me this guy's not for real." You didn't mean for it to be a joke so you decide to defend yourself:</text>
			<choiceA>Flip flop. Say that this was all just a joke and then promptly delete the thread</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Stand your ground! Mention that this is a statement about society and their views of beauty</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Nothing really happened after you deleted your post which may have been the best option. Nobody has ever seen your four-panelled comic again. AVOIDED BECOMING A MEME</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Somebody made a response comic to counter yours! She made a comic that shows her reacting to your comic then applying a dubious amount of make up on her face. You have become a poster boy for cringe pictures. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Do you honestly think dank memes are worth fighting for?</hint>
			<accomplish>30</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 40-->
		<argument>
			<text>Indulging yourself with atheism on the social networking site creddit, you found one topic inquiring "I was wondering what age you were when you found out you were atheist. I need data for my religion class." You smirked as you commented with "Do us all a favor and enroll in some atheism classes. It'll be more valuable to you." One person commented "Why are you having such a hissy fit, man? It's for school." If being scientifically correct is wrong, then you don't want to be right! You just wanted to spread your enlightenment:</text>
			<choiceA>Post an image of a meme titled "U mad, bro?"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"I wasn't having a hissy fit! The topic was tame until you commented!"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Your verbal assailant does not reply. Maybe you scared him away with your higher intelligence and clever usage of appropriate memes! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"You are literally having a hissy fit now!" They also mention that you are just as pushy and annoying as those pushy annoying religious people you think you're better than. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>You already think you're a bad-ass; keep the combo going!</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 43-->
		<argument>
			<text>Indulging yourself with atheism on the social networking site creddit, you found one topic inquiring "Do you capitalize the letter G in god?"  You replied with a "Do you want to be wrong all the time? If the answer is yes, capitalize the G." Patting yourself on the back because your wit is A+, you were peeved when one commenter ignored you and replied "Typically if you use God as a name then you have to capitalize it. If you're talking about higher beings, then it stays lower-cased." How dare this pleb spread this slander! Kill him with information before the slander spreads:</text>
			<choiceA>Shift the focus of the debate: "That's stupid. What kind of name is God anyway?"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Bring up a professionally written article where the word god is lower-cased</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Other like-minded individuals did comment talking about the origin of the name God. Not what you intended, but you completely de-railed the conversation. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"The article is talking about polytheistic gods. It's supposed to be lower-cased..." What did I tell you about reading the article you are referencing before you post it? ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Have you even taken a look at the article?</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 46-->
		<argument>
			<text>Indulging yourself with atheism on the social networking site creddit, you found one topic asking "Does religion technically count as a cult?" Willing to share your wisdom, you provide an enlightening answer: "Of course. Religion turns it's followers into mindless sheep, and is entirely useless." However, not many other people can handle your wisdom: "Do you even know what the definition of cult is? The adults are having a discussion here." What a pleb! You're probably even older than this guy! You decide to prepare to crush this child with your thesis:</text>
			<choiceA>Quickly acquire the definition of the word cult from the encyclopedia</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Pull out a lengthy article where the author uses the word cult to describe religion</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Yeah, I'm not reading that." Wow,what a bum! Due to the participant dropping out of the debate, you count this as an ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Did you just copy and paste the first sentence from the online encyclopedia?" Next time, take your time with research. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>If he's such an adult, he must have a limited amount of free time!</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 51-->
		<argument>
			<text>Feeling edgy and fed up with being friendzoned on the social networking site creddit, you wrote up a new post "Sorry for being kind and considerate. I forgot that being attractive is all it takes to get into your pants. Sorry for treating you equally I guess." Mere moments after posting, commenters mention that attractiveness is not everything: "There's more to a human being than looks, man. Just because you're a 1/10 doesn't mean you need to stay a 1." These hypocritical comments probably come from 8's. What's a lowly 1/10 left to do in this world:</text>
			<choiceA>Talk beyond looks - if you have no money, a nice car, and no place you are pretty much undatable</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Lie and say that you have a disease that makes it hard for you to be attractive and that you are offended</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Well I mean, just learn to feel comfortable in your own skin. You can learn to accept yourself." SEE! They can't prove that they are right! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Confidence is key, man. There have been celebrities who have trouble getting dates because they lacked confidence. Obviously since you have none, it's no surprise you have trouble with women." These words cut deep. Oooooohhhhhhh... ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>On the internet, you can be anyone you want! Or have anything you want...</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 60-->
		<argument>
			<text>Feeling the need to stretch your brain muscles, you created a thread titled "Do People With High IQ See Those With Average IQs as Stupid?" on the social networking site creddit. Beginning the debate with your IQ and a brief introduction, you were surprised when the debate you planned for never came! Commenters instead mocked your attempt to feel superior: "Why is it always the insecure ones that feel the need to make everything about IQ?" You're not always on about IQ! If this commenter had a higher IQ, he would have known that! Prove yourself to this low IQ'd mouth breather:</text>
			<choiceA>Defend yourself! You are not an insecure baby-man!</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Post the results of an IQ test that you took from the internet</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Your post started dying out, but your photo of the results got two upvotes which is pretty high in my opinion... At least someone believes you! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"You used the word IQ nineteen times describing how yours is so high while saying that you didn't care about IQ." YOU'RE A BIG FAT PHONY! ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Would someone confident with themselves care what somebody on the internet says about insecurity?</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 70-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were looking at cosplay photos on the social networking site creddit. You stumbled upon a photo of an attractive girl cosplaying as a one of your favorite fictional character from an anime. However she did it all wrong; "2/10. Your hair is nowhere close to the source material and your weapons don't have the correct amount of notches". Your critique was hit with negative feedback from plebs saying that "She based the costume off of the manga. Stop being such a know-it-all". But you do know-it-all! And everyone knows that the anime is a better adaptation anyway:</text>
			<choiceA>Say that the manga is not as well known as the anime</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Insult the manga comparing it to garbage</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>You got flamed hard. But there are other posters that think it would be a better idea to go with the more popular form of the character. Sticking with the people who agree with you, you feel like this is an ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Maybe. But it doesn't change the fact that you tried to feel feel smarter than you really are". OUCH YOUR INTELLIGENCE INSULTED! ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Your mother told you that if you have nothing nice to say don't say it</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 75-->
		<argument>
			<text>You stumbled upon a selfie of a lovely woman introducing herself to the site on the social networking site creddit. Being instantly smitten, you send her a personal message; "If I was your boyfriend I would treat you as a princess, m'lady". Thinking the line you dropped was gonna make her fall for you, you were shocked when she didn't reply with a message of reciprocation "I don't want to be treated like a princess". But... everything on TV and in movies told you that's what she wanted to hear! You must seduce this woman you don't even know:</text>
			<choiceA>Insist that being treated like a princess is what she wants. Then write a poem for her</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Insult everything she stands for because she is wrong</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>She never got around to replying back to you. If you didn't successfully seduce her, maybe you taught her a very valuable lesson! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>After writing 10 different haikus about m'lady, she replies with "I have a boyfriend". Bet you didn't see that coming. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Don't tell her what you think she needs. That's a jerk move</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 78-->
		<argument>
			<text>Looking through a subreddit for the dating app Cinder, you saw photos of joke conversations with women. This triggered you because these good looking guys matched with many lovely females, but they'd blow the opportunity at obtaining flesh. "If I had half of the matches you guys had, I'd do everything I could to win m'lady's love!" However, you got one stinging reply; "Quit taking Cinder so seriously. It's a harmless app." Your whole body shook - your only chance to procreate rests on the shoulders of this dating app! Show this peasant that Cinder isn't just an app:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention that these good looking court jesters are leading these poor women on</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Say that people use this app for different things and how it's bad to assume everyone uses Cinder for entertainment</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Some people agreed with you. So at the end of the day, you taught random strangers on the internet a very valuable lesson... ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"I actually find it a breath of fresh air when guys message me like this... Much better than the usual boring openers and try-hard neckbeards." You clicked on the profile of the commenter and yup - female... ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Who knows, maybe m'lady enjoys all the jokes!</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 79-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the social networking site creddit, you found a subreddit for the dating app Cinder. You found a thread titled "Your Most Successful Openers". Wanting to feel like a part of the community, you posted: "I would write her a haiku involving her name then beg m'lady to date me!" You received a handful of sarcastic replies, but the most upvoted reply boiled your britches; "That's your best? I bet they unmatch you after that!" How dare this commenter! You wanted to feel like a part of the community, but they WON'T LET YOU IN! YOU NEED TO INVITE YOURSELF INTO THE COMMUNITY:</text>
			<choiceA>Lie and say that it's worked 80% of the time</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Look for the commenter's opener and insult it!</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Nobody bothered to comment on your reply. Maybe that means you're finally assimilated into the community? FOUND A PLACE YOU CAN CALL YOUR OWN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>After a quick Ctrl + F session, you found that the commenter... actually didn't post an opener. Not knowing what to do with your life now, you began to feel a bit empty. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>What if their opener is actually really good?</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 80-->
		<argument>
			<text>There was a highly controversial picture of a girl taking a selfie with her dying grandma in the hospital on the social networking site creddit. With great controversy comes great trolls who'd insult her lack of sensitivity and intelligence. Knowing what it's like to have your intelligence insulted, you jump to her defense! After a never-ending flame war, you sent m'lady a private message; "I just defended you from internet trolls for an hour. Can I get a what's up?" However she never replied. Sometimes you just need to remind someone to reply to you:</text>
			<choiceA>Beg for a reply; "C'mon, m'lady! It was a hard fight and I'm still fighting!"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Send her the same message. If she asks why you sent her the same thing twice, say it was a glitch</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Hah. Hi." Boom. There's your attention that you wanted. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Your "what's up" never came, and neither did you... ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>I don't think she'd be technologically knowledgeable...</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 95-->
		<argument>
			<text>Browsing the front page of the social networking site creddit, there was a trending photo of a user's grand proposal to his wife. It was a cute gesture, but I mean... it's just a proposal. Totally not being jealous of their love, you posted "I hate to break it to you, but love is just a chemical reaction that compels animals to breed. It hits hard then fades away, leaving you stranded in a failing marriage.":</text>
			<choiceA>Tell this guy to follow his passions instead - to focus on science</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Tell this guy to back out while he still has the chance</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>While your post was largely ignored, the amount of upvotes you have on it is one... from yourself... ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Did you just pull out a quote from a TV show?" Oh no! You were caught with no original thoughts in your brain. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Focus on science? That sounds like it's been ripped out of somewhere...</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
	</arguments>

	<!--Arg: MyFace-->
	<arguments>
		<backgroundColor>bkgMyFace</backgroundColor>
		<headerColor>hdrMyFace</headerColor>
		<logo>logoMyface</logo>

		<!--arg 1-->
		<argument>
			<text>Early in the day, you commented on an attractive woman's MyFace profile picture saying she looks rather ravishing. Later on you noticed one new notification. Maybe she likes your genuine compliment and would like to date with you! But a wild boyfriend appears! M'lady's boyfriend looks like a stupid meathead jock, and he replied to you on the girl's picture: "Who is this dweeb? Dont talk to my girlfriend, you creep." It appears that he is asking her, but you decided to cut the middle-man out and inform this pleb of who you really are:</text>
			<choiceA>Tell the girl's boyfriend how much better you are than him. He's a stupid muscle bound jock who just HAS to be a bum!</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Write a one word reply with the correct way to spell the word "don't"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The girl ends up unfriending you from MyFace. Now your euphoric online presence won't bless her news feed. It's her fault she's dating a meatheaded bum. ARGUMENTWIN++</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Despite his jock-ish looks; he has a solid career in political science and generally has his life together. Your ego takes a huge blow to the nads :(</responseWrong>
			<hint>You don't even know what this guy does in his free time!</hint>
			<accomplish>30</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 3-->
		<argument>
			<text>While you were scrolling through your news feed on the social media website MyFace, you saw a notification! However you see it's just your mother commenting on your wall with "There's more to life than video games and the Internet. You're wasting your life." The rest of your family agrees with her by liking her comment and replying to it. You suddenly became more introspective. You thought that you were doing fine in life; nice room, great sense of style, combat skills, etc. Have you been distracting yourself from the truth? You start to think of a way to reply to your mother:</text>
			<choiceA>Ignore the post and delete it from your wall. What's she going to do? Ground you? Psh, you're an adult!</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Blame your failures on your upbringing. You only never accomplished anything in life because of her!</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>After writing multiple paragraphs on how everything is her fault, she replies "You're absolutely right. I not only gave you everything growing up, but I spoiled you." You're life may be hollow and you may be a spoiled-brat, but she still agreed with you! LIFE IN SHAMBLES BUT ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Your family members who liked your mom's post all started posting on your wall with posts like "I saw what your mom said, you should listen to her" and started lecturing you. Can't run away from family. They'll find you. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Family always has a way of finding you...</hint>
			<accomplish>30</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 9-->
		<argument>
			<text>While on the social media site MyFace, a relationship status update showed up on your news feed. To your horror it's your best friend that you've been in love with since high school. Regaining your composure after hours of deep despair and crying into your pillow, you decide to fight for her! You stalked her new boyfriend's MyFace for research to see he's just a typical muscle bound pleb. She can do better. Like for a man who has a superior intellect. Somebody like you! Armed with a keyboard and your gifted way with words you craft just the private MyFace message to win her over:</text>
			<choiceA>Profess your love for her!</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Badmouth her new boyfriend, telling her she deserves much better</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>She replies to your message: "Sorry, I don't think I will ever see you in that way. But I still want to be friends with you." She did say that she doesn't THINK she will ever see you that way, so there may still be a chance! DELUSIONAL BUT ARGUMENT WIN I GUESS</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>She replies to your message: "You haven't even met him! You do this every time I date somebody new; you freak out and tell me how stupid I am. Just stop talking to me; you're a toxic friend." ARGUMENT AND FRIENDSHIP LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Don't start a war. Friendships can be lost that way</hint>
			<accomplish>30</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 13-->
		<argument>
			<text>While on the social media site MyFace, everyone seems to be posting about a tragedy that struck in a city in Africa. You decide to let the world know that you care. After thinking long and hard on how to formulate the words for your post, you come up with "Is the culprit African? Because they are A-frican bitch! My heart goes out to the victims." However a few minutes after posting, you MyFace "friends" are calling you an insensitive prick! You just wanted to spice up all the gloom with a joke! You try to come up with a response to all of the people that misinterpreted your status:</text>
			<choiceA>Apologise profusely. They misinterpreted your concern as insensitivity</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Say that you have a bunch of black friends</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>They accept your apology and urge you to delete your status. You never did, but people stopped calling you a prick at least. ARGUMENT WIN I GUESS</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>They comment saying that was not the issue they had with your status. Now everybody is calling you a racist too. You also became viral and had your status screen captured for other social media outlets :( ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Your black friends can't help you on the internet</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 14-->
		<argument>
			<text>Someone in your friends list made a status saying she made it out of surgery on the social media site MyFace. Usually you would ignore posts like these, but you saw her mother has the most liked comment; "Thank God you're okay. I love you." It's time to school a concerned mother with facts about religion. You replied to the mother's comment; "God doesn't exist. She made it because of the skill of the surgeon." Suddenly people started roasting you! The mother replies with "I was just grateful that my daughter was okay." You start to reply to these attacks against your belief with:</text>
			<choiceA>"I was just pointing your thanks towards the surgeons that deserve it"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"Please provide scientific proof that there is a God out there and I will take back what I said"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Your comment has been deleted by the girl's mother. You consider re-writing your comment, but you considered that she learned her lesson that God doesn't exist. ARGUMENT WIN++</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The mother replies with "We are all grateful for the surgeon, it was just a figure of speech." before your comment was bombarded with people calling you a moron. You just wanted to educate those less intelligent than you :( ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Nobody called for Captain Obvious</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 18-->
		<argument>
			<text>You found the MyFace profile of a woman you met in the real world. She was working at the mall and you asked her coworker for her full name. She's perfect; has colorful hair, is a girl, and didn't walk away while talking to you! You sent her some introductory messages, but she seemed lukewarm to your attempts; taking a long time to reply, one word answers, etc... You decide to go for broke; "Assuming you haven't blocked me or deleted your account, I take it that you weren't creeped out by me tracking you down. I think you are beautiful. I understand I'm not much, but I would worship you." After some waiting, she has not replied yet so you decide to give this last message your all:</text>
			<choiceA>Neg her: "You're not very talkative. If I had to rate your charisma, I'd give you a 0/10!"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Fish for a response: "Won't you talk to me? I am a nice guy and we have similar interests."</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>She seems to have deleted her MyFace profile. Her default picture is now a default image. Not sure what to make of it, she probably is going through some tough times and will contact you once she gets online again. ARGUMENT... I don't even know :\</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The girl ends up writing a large essay covering such topics such as how much of a creep you are for stalking her, her rejecting you, and how if you have to tell her that you are a nice guy, you probably are not. "By the way, I just moved here and didn't have internet so I couldn't reply fast enough. Good thing you spammed me with messages because it shows what kind of person you are." :( ARGUMENT AND GIRL OF YOUR DREAMS LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Use what your Pick-Up Artist training taught you!</hint>
			<accomplish>30</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 21-->
		<argument>
			<text>Scrolling through your news feed on the social media site MyFace, a pretty girl posted a sad status. You didn't actually read the contents of the post; you just saw that there was a sad girl and as a white knight, you took it upon yourself to make this girl happy. You blessed her eyes with a sonnet of words: "M'lady, your smile is the most beautiful part of you. Please stop frowning." However the harlot didn't reply to your reply in a timely fashion. Meanwhile, she is replying to the replies after yours. Is she ignoring you? You demand to be acknowledged for your thoughtful words!:</text>
			<choiceA>"Please let me in!"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"You are perfect the way you are"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>M'lady acknowledged you! He replied to your comment with a sincere "Haha, thank you." Her comment could carry you through the years as you mark off for another fair maiden saved from sadness! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The girl never replied to you despite replying to other people on her status. It seems like this white knight just got another scar on his armor :( ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Neediness is a massive turn-off</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 31-->
		<argument>
			<text>While on the social media site MyFace, you posted a picture of you and your newest pony figurine because the world needed to see it I guess. One of your like-minded friends from college commented on it saying "Cool! She's not my favorite pony, but the quality is excellent. Where did you buy it?" Not his favorite pony!?!?! Ever since college, this tool has always been a thorn in your side with your differences in opinions. From music to games and now ponies?! This pleb doesn't deserve the title of being your friend:</text>
			<choiceA>"You are dead to me" then unfriend the sucker!</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"Not your favorite pony!? You are the king of bad taste."</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>He replied with "Yeah, I guess. Where did you buy it?" You have the upper hand here so you hold on to the information and don't reply to him. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Your ex-friend sent you a text; "Dude, what the hell is wrong with you? You freak out every time we have a difference in opinion. Get over yourself" You received a new friend request from him and accepted because that's what you do. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>He's been your friend for a long time... he can take it</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 38-->
		<argument>
			<text>While on the social media site MyFace, you notice that a cherished actress has been arrested and people are making jokes about her. How cruel; somebody makes a mistake and now society throws them to the lions! You decide to defend this celebrity's honor by commenting on the article: "What is the matter with you lot? We all make mistakes, but the moment a famous person makes one, you're all quick to turn on them!" Somebody replied to your comment with a "What she did was unforgivable!" This actress is a national treasure, and you will not let this ignorant pleb sully the actress' name:</text>
			<choiceA>"That's bull! Everyone can be forgiven!"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"Calm down everyone! She's going through some hard times, and we should support her!"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The commenters start feeling pity for the actress because she was going through some stressful times before she ended up in prison. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<hint>Have you even read what this actress did?</hint>
			<responseWrong>"She took drugs then murdered 12 people! Did you even read the article?" That's what you get for just skipping to the comments section... ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 47-->
		<argument>
			<text>While on the social media site MyFace, you posted a selfie of yourself and a waifu body pillow. One of your fundie friends commented, "This is pretty weird, man. You're never going to find a girl with that." How dare he insults your game! This caused an eruption of emotions to burst out of you: "OF COURSE I KNOW WHAT AN ORGASM FEELS LIKE I PULL AT BARS, PLEB." After regaining your composure, you immediately delete your reply and start to put some thought into your next reply:</text>
			<choiceA>Talk about your numerous sexual exploits you have totally been a participant in</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Explain that people have different tastes and hobbies and that people need to be open</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"I still find it pretty weird, but whatever you want to do man. I recommend that you don't post these so everyone can it because it is a taste not everyone can understand." ...so he agrees with you? ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Wait, a bag of sand?" ...he immediately discovered that you do not know what you are talking about. A bag of sand, is that the best you could come up with? ARGUMENT LOST-FRAUD DETECTED</responseWrong>
			<hint>There's a time and place for showing off. The internet is not one of them</hint>
			<accomplish>30</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 52-->
		<argument>
			<text>While on the social media site MyFace, you got your mom to take a picture of you on one knee holding your katana out with both hands. Feeling more chivalrous than usual, you posted the photo onto m'lady's wall with the caption "With this blade I vow to take arms to those who sully your honor." However, after you posted your art on her wall you got a message from her asking you to never contact her again. Looking at her profile again, it seems that she deleted your photo. But why!?! The world needs to know that you are m'lady's white knight!:</text>
			<choiceA>Repost the picture on her wall with the same caption. Maybe second time's the charm</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Ask what she didn't like about the photo and say that you can improve for her standards</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"It's creepy. I don't even know who you are." So pretty much all you need to do is introduce yourself? Let the seduction begin! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The next time you viewed her profile, you noticed that there was an "Add Friend" button. She unfriended you from MyFace :( I mean it's totally her loss she doesn't want to be a part in your life, right? ARGUMENT AND PRINCESS LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Persistence is key... but not the key to winning anyone over</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 53-->
		<argument>
			<text>While on the social media site MyFace, you were mindlessly browsing through your news feed until you saw a friend you used to be madly in love with in high school get married to a Neanderthal-ish pleb. So you messaged this girl's new husband; "Hey congrats on the marriage! But you do realize it's not gonna work because you are not good enough for her." A moment passes by and he replies with "What the hell are you even talking about?" Quick! Let him know why he's a terrible fit for your high school crush while he's confused:</text>
			<choiceA>Ask if he even has a job. You do, and you can totally support her</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Say that nobody will ever love her and treat her right as you would</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"The hell does that matter? I make enough to support the both of us." You then blocked the pleb before he can send you another message. You know that he's just saving face and lying to feel better about himself. DELUSIONAL ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"So I asked about you. My wife said the last time you talked to her was in high school. You didn't even talk to her much, you just asked her to sign your yearbook. Are you so unhappy with your own life that you can't stand to see other people be happy?" You then blocked the pleb. That'll show him! You are happy with your life; how can you not be with an ARGUMENT LOST oh wait...</responseWrong>
			<hint>When was the last time you even talked to her?</hint>
			<accomplish>30</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 56-->
		<argument>
			<text>Feeling the need to let the world know of your intellectual superiority on the social media site MyFace, you fabricate a story where you outwitted a typical alpha male muscle headed chad. The story had many twists and turns, but it ended with you winning over the girl he was hitting on by speaking Latin. Despite how eloquently written your status was, people were quick to question your credibility: "I highly doubt any of this happened." That's no good! You worked hard making this fictional story sound real:</text>
			<choiceA>Describe your imaginary verbal assailant and the imaginary girl in greater detail</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Quickly translate an insult into Latin on www.translatestuff.com</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Nobody replies because nobody really cares about your work of fiction. Your status dropped off into MyFace obscurity. Eh... good enough. ARGUMENT WIN AND CREDIBILITY GAINED</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Did you just describe the two main characters from that Dragon Fight Z anime? Pathetic, man..." You couldn't come up with a more original description quick enough! You don't think well under pressure :( ARGUMENT AND CREDIBILITY LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Prove that you are superior in the head!</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 66-->
		<argument>
			<text>Skimming through the social media site MyFace, you found a damsel in distress! She made a post saying "My bf is out with friends right now so the house is all mine!" Triggered by the fact that a douchebag is leaving m'lady all by her lonesome, you decide to do the responsible thing and reply to her status; "I'm sure that's fun and all, but I would never leave if you were around." However, she hasn't replied to you after thirty minutes so you write "Just checking in, but I really hope he has enough time for you..." You decide that the third time is the charm:</text>
			<choiceA>Remain hopeful and optimistic "Guess he's back... I'm glad he's home now"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Express your concern over the dangers of being alone at home</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>A few moments after you commented, the status disappeared from her wall, so you know that m'damsel is safe because only she can delete her status. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>A rando commented on m'lady's status with "What the hell are you on about? You made a fun status and turned it creepy." Yeah, I guess you kind of are the creep maker... ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>I'm pretty sure she's fine at home alone. You on the other hand...</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 67-->
		<argument>
			<text>You noticed a trend on the social media website MyFace where people would add a flag filter to their profile picture in support of a tragedy struck in the world. You commented on one of these flag photos with "Do you guys honestly think updating your profile is helping these victims?" However, people take your life lesson as hostility; "What's wrong with showing support? We're just bringing visibility to a terrible tragedy." These sheeple don't genuinely care about the tragedy. These sheeple are asleep and you are the alarm clock:</text>
			<choiceA>Be blunt with "You guys are just doing this because everyone else is. You all are sheeple!"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Educate these plebs with "There are more deserving tragedies in other parts of the world. How come you're not supporting them?"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Well it's hard to know about everything going on in the world..." A FEEBLE ATTEMPT! Your knowledge in the entire world really helped you out here. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"At least we're staying positive. It's better than making fun of people for trying to show their support". THEY CAN'T WAKE UP ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Sometimes the truth hurts</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 73-->
		<argument>
			<text>Feeling proud of original art you drew of your favorite TV show Ponies in High School fused with your friends, you decide to post it to the social media website MyFace and tag your friends with their associated pony-fusion. Your hardwork only got one like from your mother, but you also received one comment; "Don't tag me in posts like these. I'm job hunting, and being tagged in pony photos don't help." You noticed that your friend took the liberty of untagging himself from the photo. This is the reason you don't have a job - you are a special snowflake and will not change yourself for the man, man:</text>
			<choiceA>Say that you are disappointed in him becoming a corporate sellout and a part of an irrelevant social construct</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Cut his pony fusion out of your drawing then unfriend that sucker! A one-two punch HAH!</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Nothing really happened. You friend never reached out to you, and there were no discussions on your art. Huh... NO BIG DEAL - ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"This is the reason why nobody likes you, man." His reply got twenty likes... People like you, right? ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Wanting a job shouldn't label someone as a sellout</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 76-->
		<argument>
			<text>Feeling oddly euphoric and very unsatisfied with how you look, you updated your profile picture to an anime character on the social media website MyFace. Feeling reinvigorated for some reason, you were thrilled when a notification popped up on your new anime photo! It was a comment from your grandmother; "I wish you'd put more photos of yourself... you're a handsome boy and I wish to see my grandson's face more." REEEEEE! How dare she rubs in your ugly by calling you handsome! You decide that you need to school your own grandmother:</text>
			<choiceA>Explain the entire story of the anime. Maybe that'll be enough to show her why you need this profile picture</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Tell her she's no longer invited to your house on Christmas</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Okay dear, that's great..." Maybe after all your exposition, she can finally understand why you need to have this anime character as your default picture! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Your mother posted on your picture; "Mother, don't listen to him. He's overreacting and will think more about the mean words he said while he's grounded." ARGUMENT LOST - GROUNDED FOR LIFE!</responseWrong>
			<hint>It's not your house. You have no power there</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 87-->
		<argument>
			<text>Feeling sexually frustrated on the social media website MyFace, you posted a multi-paragraphed thought diary; "Sex is the most basic, meaningless cry for help the universe ever screamed. You're born an OBJECTIVELY good looking member of the species and found a partner to have intercourse with? If you used a condom, you negated the entire purpose of the mating ritual!" Feeling like this was quality literature, someone commented; "You're jealous because you never had sex". WHOA! YOU'RE ALL ABOUT THAT SEX LIFE! It's time for you to prove that you know a thing or two about sex:</text>
			<choiceA>Tell this guy that you've had hundreds of partners and know what you're talking about when it comes to sex stuff</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Write your thesis - "As a non-attractive guy, what am I left to do to mate? What about me?"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>After half an hour, this commenter wrote back; "I don't know man, maybe you'll find someone to perform that mating ritual with. Keep trying." ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>After half an hour, this commenter wrote back; "I looked through your photos and MyFace timeline... I found no signs of human contact." Since when did they add that timeline? ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>If by partner, you mean NPC's in video games, then yes. You've had hundreds! Real life partners however...</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 92-->
		<argument>
			<text>Noticing a trend on the social media website MyFace - people that were popular in high school are posting memes from your favorite adult sci-fi cartoon show. That's not fair! You want to have something all to yourself for years of suffering as a not-popular kid in high school. "You need to have a high IQ to fully get the nuances in their jokes - I don't understand how these normies are posting memes from this show." Someone replied with "You don't need to understand everything about something to find enjoyment out of it." BLASPHEMY! You NEED to keep this show all to yourself:</text>
			<choiceA>Say that all the jokes about theoretical physics will go over a typical viewer's head</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Break apart the main character's existential catchphrase</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>After writing a paragraph linking the main character's catchphrase "Wubba lubba dub dub" to Russian folklore, nobody ended up commenting. However, you did get a lot of laughing reactions, so maybe some people learned a thing or two. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>After you commented your hypothesis on theoretical physics, an old classmate from high school asked "Didn't you fail physics in high school? I remember you had to retake the class in the summer." Ooof! ARGUMENT LOST - FRAUD DETECTED</responseWrong>
			<hint>Do you even know theoretical physics?</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 93-->
		<argument>
			<text>Habitually scrolling through your timeline on the social media website MyFace, a picture of a cute cat appears! Wanting to feel smart and quirky, you posted "This cat is quite hirsute!" Somebody took the bait and asked; "Hirsute?" Your plan to feel intellectually superior worked! You translated hirsute to this normie and gave a long winded multi-paragraphed explanation of its origins. You spent three hours researching this word to help you in writing up this essay. However, he never replied. Three hours of your life wasted! Unless you can craft up some way to get a response...:</text>
			<choiceA>Tell him that you chose to use this word in place of the standard drivel that normies would use</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Tell this clown that he can now use this word in his every day life</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>This commenter replied! I mean it was literally just a one word "k" but still... that's something? ARGUMENT ATTEMPTED</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>You waited for hours, but he never replied. You waited... TIME WASTED - ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>He can technically use this word now if he wants...</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
	</arguments>

	<!--Arg: OkNarcissus-->
	<arguments>
		<backgroundColor>bkgOkNarc</backgroundColor>
		<headerColor>hdrOkNarc</headerColor>
		<logo>logoOknarc</logo>
		<!--arg 1-->
		<argument>
			<text>While on the prowl for a hot Asian or white girlfriend on the online dating website OkNarcissus, you received a message from a girl calling you a creep. You look back into your hundreds of sent messages searching for her name to see that you sent this girl a harmless message: "Dear M'lady! I would love to make love to you underneath the sky, the sun, and the stars. Would you allow me to have that honor?" Obviously hurt at being called a creep you start to type a message back:</text>
			<choiceA>"I have no idea what I did wrong, but if you somehow felt offended by my harmless message, I apologize whole-heartedly, m'lady."</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"Nevermind. I shouldn't settle for dumb broads who are below me."</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The girl doesn't respond. In fact, you feel like she probably blocked you from ever contacting her again. It's her loss anyway; if she knew that you made $1K during the summer, maybe she would change her mind. You take this as an ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"How on Earth are you a human being? Your first message was asking if I would allow you to "make love to me"; how could I not be offended by that? I hope you don't talk to other girls on this website like this, you sexless weirdo". ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>How could you possibly not know what you did wrong?</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 4-->
		<argument>
			<text>You logged onto the online dating website OkNarcissus for the 20th time today and noticed that you received a message from a girl! Somebody actually is showing interest in you on the internet! Ecstatic, you open up her message: "Hey! I haven't seen many fans of the Bearsona series on this website. How are you today?" You clicked on her page and saw that despite having similar hobbies and tastes; she is quite homely. Curses! Why couldn't she be a smoking hot white/Asian girl with glasses!? Stroking your beard, you start to think of a way to respond:</text>
			<choiceA>"EW! GROSS! YOUR NOSE IS WHERE YOUR MOUTH SHOULD BE AND YOUR MOUTH IS WHERE YOUR NECK SHOULD BE AAAAAAHHHH!!!!"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"My apologies, but you are not within my league. I desire a fit classy Asian/white lady with glasses and bangs."</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The girl doesn't respond, but she did view your profile after you sent the message. She probably cried herself to sleep. Feels good to be such a heart breaker! It's her fault for being average looking anyway. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Okay, good luck with that. You should have no problem getting one of those." the homely girl replies. You can feel the sarcasm ooze from the computer screen. You just got rejected by a homely girl! It's not like you care or anything (but really, you do care). ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Sometimes you gotta go all in...</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 11-->
		<argument>
			<text>You logged onto the online dating website OkNarcissus to speak to a woman you have been messaging on and off for 3 days. So it's quite serious. You decide it's time to move your relationship to the next level; "M'lady! May I inquire you for your number? I would love to send you photos of my daily ritual". Your heart beat races while you wait patiently for her reply. However after many hours, she still hasn't rewarded you with a message. You even see that she is online, so you know she read it! Peeved off, you start to write a message to her letting her know how you feel:</text>
			<choiceA>"Way to throw away 3 days of getting to know each other, ya dumb broad!"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"C'mon, baby I'm good for iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiit!"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Still no response. It appears that she has deactivated her dating profile. You assumed that she realized she made a mistake for not prioritizing you and stepped out of the dating pool. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Don't call me a dumb broad! I just stepped out for a few hours. It's a good thing you messaged me though because it shows exactly what kind of child you are." Ouch! There's plenty of fish in the sea, man. RELATIONSHIP LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Was it even worth it in the end?</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 12-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were in a deep dive search for your future waifu on the online dating website OkNarcissus and stumbled upon a profile of a model-esque Goddess. She could be on magazines! However, her looks seem to be her only appeal as her profile reads "Don't message me if you do not meet these requirements" and proceeded to list off traits she finds attractive such as being physically fit, having a fulfilling career, etc... How dare she instantly rejects those based on superficial standards! If she gave you the chance, you would be able to woo her with your superior intellect:</text>
			<choiceA>"I believe it's wrong for you to filter out a large amount of men based on such narrow parameters."</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"Hey."</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The girl doesn't respond. She also mentioned in her profile that she wouldn't respond to one word first messages. Well uh... you weren't too emotionally attached, so it wasn't so bad I guess. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>She did view your profile, but never replied to your message. You almost had her :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>If you have standards, so can other people</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 30-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were desperately clicking through the online dating website OkNarcissus and read through a profile that said "I value a man's intelligence and personality over muscle". So pretty much, you're m'lady's dream guy! However before you can work up the words to woo her, you spot a typo in her profile. "Please us proper grammar in your message and we can get along!" US!?!?!?! Instead of being your usual suave self, something within you compels you to write "Don't you mean 'use'?" However after a few minutes of waiting, she still hasn't replied to you. You decided to fish for a message:</text>
			<choiceA>Be a bad-ass snarker: "You should reply to my message. You'll learn more about grammar if you do."</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Explain the joke: "Get it? Because you misspelled something in your profile! :P"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The girl doesn't respond. However, you looked at her profile and she fixed the spelling error. It seems like you passed on some knowledge and made the world a better place! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"No thank you. You kind of creep me out." Ouch :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Help the world with your superior intelligence!</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 34-->
		<argument>
			<text>Desperately clicking through the online dating website OkNarcissus, you stumbled upon the profile of an attractive fair-haired maiden. Reading through m'lady's profile, she seems to be flawless: is a girl, nerdy, colorful hair, no children... just like in your Japanese animes! However your elven eyes stumble onto m'lady's religious beliefs. Turns out that she is a devout Christian. You cannot fathom ever dating a woman who worships an imaginary cloud in the sky! Disgusted to the core, you made it your mission to win her over to the side of atheism:</text>
			<choiceA>"You do realize that God isn't real, right?"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"You would be more attractive if you weren't religious."</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The girl doesn't respond. However, you looked at her profile and she added a disclaimer: "Must love God." While you didn't sway her to the light side of atheism, you at least helped other men not waste their time. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"I could say that you would be more attractive if you were Christian." After that, she just kept on lecturing and lecturing... you called this a lost cause and gave up on trying to woo m'lady :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>You're one to talk about attractiveness...</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 48-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were desperately clicking through indexes of the online dating website OkNarcissus and stumbled upon the profile of an attractive fair-haired woman. You read in a PUA book that erotic first messages lead to more sex; so you tried it with this girl: "M'lady, I just thought of your perfect bare body as I caressed myself. I thought I should let you know." After a moment, she replied with "Creepy!" A one word reply!?!? Surely your message should've warranted more than that! You decide to not let that get to you and keep on seducing her. Make your second message really mean something:</text>
			<choiceA>"I would like you to know that I am caressing myself once more awaiting your reply."</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"Would you like to meet up one of these days?"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Never in a million years." So maybe you'll have a chance after the million years are up? ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Keep on caressing, weirdo." M'lady's profile then seemed to have been deactivated. When you were done with caressing yourself, you felt sad about being called a weirdo. It worked in the books, dammit! ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>#yolo</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 59-->
		<argument>
			<text>Sifting through the online dating website OkNarcissus, you found the profile of a goddess that you Super Liked on the dating app Cinder. Thinking it's odd to see her on a dating site after a guy like you Super Liked her, you concocted a message: "I saw you on Cinder and Super Liked you. Did you ever get it? I'm wondering why we never matched." After a while of waiting she replied with "Sorry dude. I'm pretty picky and I swipe left a lot." You dropped to your knees and wept. Not being used to rejection because you never get rejected, you decide to show her that you're worth the right swipe:</text>
			<choiceA>Talk yourself up: "You don't know what you're missing out on."</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Talk her down: "You weren't that pretty anyway. HARUMPH!"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Whatever." So she agrees with you. No argument from her side. You totally showed her I guess! ARGUMENT RECEIVED</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"After looking at your profile, it looks like I'm not missing out on much." I mean your profile did say you have no car, job, and apartment... She might just be correct. Also why would you keep that in your profile? ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Confidence is good to have, but don't be delusional about yourself</hint>
			<accomplish>30</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 62-->
		<argument>
			<text>Spending hour after hour on the dating website OkNarcissus, you skimmed m'lady's profile that read "I have no time for games. I'm tired of getting played." Feeling like you can solve all the problems going on in her life, you messaged her: "The only games I play are on the computer m'lady." Feeling like you nailed the first message, you were shocked when she didn't reply instantly. But you are on a mission for a reply: she wants an honest guy, and you are the answer to all of her problems:</text>
			<choiceA>Be patient and keep waiting...</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Roast her: "No reply? No wonder you keep on getting played!"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>You waited for a reply... and waited... until it's been a few days and you kinda just forgot about her. ARGUMENT FORGOTTEN ABOUT</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>After you roasted her, she replied with "What's wrong with you? I'm hardly on here, sorry for not being able to constantly message people. It's guys like you that make me want to deactivate my profile." But how..? YOU WERE THE ANSWER TO ALL HER PROBLEMS! YOU ARE A NICE GUY WHO ONLY WANTS TO BE HER EVERYTHING! ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Good things come to those who wait</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 63-->
		<argument>
			<text>Losing your mind and confidence on the dating website OkNarcissus, you found the love of your life! Well I mean you don't know her at all, but she is Asian. So you decide to seduce her with your superior seduction skills: "Ohayo anata wa kanari no akachan!" Thinking that knowing her native tongue was the key to making her tongue native to yours, she replied with: "I'm Korean." Damn! A slight miscalculation! You should've read the bottom part of her profile saying she was from Korea... You need to make this right and win over the woman of your dreams:</text>
			<choiceA>Apologize for being presumptuous. It won't happen again</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Hastily translate a pick-up line from English to Korean</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Nice try." LE GASP! M'LADY ACTUALLY MESSAGED YOU BACK! Not wanting to seem desperate, you are going to wait two weeks before you message her back. ARGUMENT WON</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Nothing happens - no message back, no profile view, no new like... I guess you were right in that it won't happen again ;D ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Apologies are for beta trash!</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 68-->
		<argument>
			<text>Feeling dead inside and sexually frustrated on the dating website OkNarcissus, you stumble upon an angel! She's exactly your type - fair hair, is a girl, and has a profile picture of her at the beach. Suppressing the blood gushing out of your nose like a waterfall, you type; "Pardon me, but I am curious as to what you look like underneath your fabrics. Perhaps you would do me the honor of photographing your bare body so I could gaze upon your beauty?" Keeping your eyes glued to your inbox you finally get a message from the love of your life; "Erm no WTF":</text>
			<choiceA>Show how alpha you are and say "PLEASE I BEG OF YOU!"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Start over and pretend the last few messages hasn't happened</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Still no." Well I mean at least you got a message back! BETTER THAN NOTHING - ARGUMENT WON</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Are you just going to pretend you weren't desperate to see me naked a few messages ago? It's guys like you that make me want to delete my profile here". Ouch... ARGUMENT AND WILL TO LIVE LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>These messages are stored in a database - you can't ignore what you said in the past</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 71-->
		<argument>
			<text>Searching for your future waifu on the dating website OkNarcissus, you stumble upon a maiden after adjusting your search parameters. Honestly she's young - not even reaching the 20 year mark, but as an older gentlesir, you can be her sugar daddy. You messaged her saying how you'd love to wake up naked next to her thinking it was a nice mixture of sexy and considerate. After a few moments, you got a message back from her; "Erm. You're over my age range. Did you not read my profile?" Of course you did skim over it! You're on thin ice - you need to succeed in seducing a younger woman:</text>
			<choiceA>Reiterate to m'lady the benefits of dating an older man</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Say that age is just a number - old enough to count, old enough to mount!</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>While m'lady never replied, she did end up looking at your profile. Maybe she regretted blowing you off and looked upon your profile picture in sadness. ARGUMENT WON</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>You actually got a warning from the OkNarcissus team for sexual harassment. You know you messed up when the OkNarcissus team personally messages you! ON THIN ICE - ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Just please do yourself a favor and don't be a creep</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 72-->
		<argument>
			<text>Longing for a woman's touch on the dating website OkNarcissus, you were actually able to convince a lovely lady to meet up with you for pizza! You exchanged numbers and she asked you for a picture. However, after you sent one she stopped messaging. You decide to start spamming her inbox with messages such as the classic "What? Am I not muscley enough for you?" and "We had such a nice thing going until you messed it up!" But she still never replied. You better put your all in this last message or you can kiss your pizza date good bye:</text>
			<choiceA>Ask about the pizza date</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Try to destroy her self esteem as payback for destroying your self esteem</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"I'll get back to you on that... so no need to message me." DATE ACHEIVED - ARGUMENT WON</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"I stopped messaging you because you were a catfish. You look nothing like in your photos. So not only do you lack confidence in what you look like, but you are a terrible human being!" Well I mean like... you're not the worst human being :( ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>C'mon. Just don't be a jerk</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 81-->
		<argument>
			<text>Seeking out your future waifu on the dating website OkNarcissus, you were shocked when you got messaged first! That has never happened before! Excited to see what the future Mrs. You has to say, you were shocked when she critiqued your profile - "I get that people have standards, but you are a choosing beggar! Some of the traits you want are impossible!" What's so impossible with wanting a 10/10 Asian girl that is under 5 feet and 120 pounds and into nerd culture and also a virgin and must know the harp? Prove to this crazy lady that it's not impossible:</text>
			<choiceA>"I'm allowed to seek out whatever qualities I want to seek out!"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"You're just jealous that you're not qualified to get a piece of me!"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Well good luck with that. You're going to need it." Oh hey! She gave you some luck in your goals. What a nice lady. ARGUMENT WON</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Jealous? Not at all. You look like a goblin." OUCH! LOOK IN THE MIRROR - ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Well I mean, you are a choosing beggar...</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 86-->
		<argument>
			<text>Spamming refresh on the dating website OkNarcissus in the new section, you clicked on a profile of a girl who's only looking for friends as she already has a boyfriend. OkNarcissus is not the place for friendship! You give this broad a piece of your mind; "Get out of here! OkNarcissus is for dating and sex only!" Expecting this thot would remove herself from the website, she actually messaged back; "Because what I do on this website is dictated by you, right?" Patting yourself on your back, you spat your beverage when you realized that was sarcasm. As an alpha male, you must retaliate:</text>
			<choiceA>Call her boyfriend a cuck and how she should date a real man like yourself</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Call her bluff and say that she's not satisfied with her relationship hence why she's on the website</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>M'lady never replied to you, but damn it feels good to call someone a cuck! ARGUMENT-kinda-WON</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"You will never find a meaningful connection with anybody in the world acting like this." That hurt! Right in the gibblets. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Don't assume something about someone else's relationship, man</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 94-->
		<argument>
			<text>Looking through the dating website OkNarcissus trying not to die inside, you were in a conversation with a girl talking about a date you had a while ago: "I tried impressing her by playing mind games with the waitress to show off my brilliance and she called me stuck up. Guess some women can't handle my brilliance..." Thinking m'lady was going to be understanding, she instead replied with "Have you considered not being a manipulative jerk?" Well that's rude! Make this girl understand that you are not manipulative by changing her mind one way or another:</text>
			<choiceA>Feign ignorance - "Me? Manipulative? Well I'd never..."</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Tell her she must have a low IQ if she can't understand your issues</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>After waiting for a few hours, you see that m'lady's dating profile doesn't exist any more. Thinking that she must have been harassed by awful guys on this site, she may have quit. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"You literally are trying to be manipulative now. How does that even happen?" ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Feigning ignorance is pretty manipulative...</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
	</arguments>

	<!--Arg: MGN-->
	<arguments>
		<backgroundColor>bkgMGN</backgroundColor>
		<headerColor>hdrMGN</headerColor>
		<logo>logoMgn</logo>

		<!--arg 5-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, they posted an article about the game Alive and Dead: Hardcore Beach Games. You looked over to your collector's edition on your bookshelf with a sense of pride and urgency! Scrolling through the comments of the article, one comment vexed you: "The only people who enjoy this game are perverts who can't get laid". This guy is misinformed; you enjoy these types of games AND you are totally sexually active. Yeah, your girlfriend visited from Canada over the summer and totally did things with her. Insulted, you type up a response to this commenter:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention your numerous sexual exploits that are totally numerous. Give juicy details such as positions and the dirty talks</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Mention the gameplay mechanics and the game's longevity. At the game's core, there is more than just fan service</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>You mention the game's merit, and the commenter apologizes. It's okay though; a pleb like him would've never been able to understand the quality of Alive and Dead: Hardcore Beach Games without your help. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The commenter called you out! He said that he found you on MyFace and said that you are one of those anti-social perverts! He then proceeds to post links that lead to pictures of you, and it really hurts your feelings. Surprisingly, the website doesn't have any anti-bullying rules :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>MGN always finds out...</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 10-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, they posted up a review for the thirteenth instalment of a popular JRPG series. Unfortunately the plebs running MGN gave the game a paltry score of 6/10 stating the sequel fails to capture the fantasy and the adventure of the games before it. I mean you haven't played the game yet, but you love the series and it deserves better. You look through the reviewer's past publications and note that he gave low scores to a lot of your cherished games. Now it's personal! You start to craft your words onto the comments section of the review:</text>
			<choiceA>Call the reviewer a troll who gives low reviews to games just to get extra hits on their review</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Mention the game's positive points. You haven't played it yet, but you know it's good! Look at those graphics and soundtrack!</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The commenters do mention that the reviewer is known to do that once in a while. They start to question if this review is legitimate or if the reviewer is trolling again. TURNING IT AROUND ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The commenters mention that while the music and graphics are good, that doesn't make up for the nonexistant gameplay. I mean you did have some holes in your argument... ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Games are more that what you can see and hear</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 20-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, you saw a review for a Plebstation 4 exclusive game get a measly 7/10. Typically you're a PC gamer, but if you had to side with either of the consoles, you'd choose the Bonebox. When you saw the review, it felt like the console war was over! You rush to the comments section and without a thought wrote "R.I.P Plebstation 4. No match for the mighty Bonebox!" However the Plebstation fanboys won't take this sitting down; all commenting that the Plebstation 4 is winning the console war. Being of a higher intellect, you decide to educate these fanboys:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention exclusives! The Plebstation 4 has a lot of mediocre exclusives; quantity is not equal to quality!</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Mention sales figures! The Plebstation 4 is nothing compared to the past consoles!</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The commenters pathetically try to defend their console saying that their killer app is coming out later in the year, but you know it will probably get another 7/10. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>They mention that Plebstation 4 is selling much more than the Bonebox. YOU GOT BONED AND ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>What does the past console generation have to do with anything?</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 24-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, there was a thread where the OP was asking for opinions on which console to buy between the Bonebox and the Plebstation 4. Obviously the better of these two choices is the PC. You reply to the thread with "PC Master Race; console plebs gon hate." This however put a target on your back from other commenters as they all flamed you saying "PC wasn't even an option" and asking you to learn how to read. You, an avid reader of pony fanfiction do know how to read and think that PC gaming is the best thing since underwear. You have two ways of replying to these dweebs:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention that the PC has a wider library, a mod support, and can upscale while the consoles can't</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Post a meme about the pathetic console plebs being too poor for the PC Master Race</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The commenters say that while they agree with you that the PC is wonderful, it still was not an option in the thread. They insult your intelligence, but at least they agree with you! PEOPLE AGREE WITH YOU ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The OP replied saying that he already has a gaming PC, they just want the console exclusives and the games that run better on console. So that's the reason he didn't list the PC :| ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Your mother bought your gaming PC for you!</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 27-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, there was a "Who would win in a fight?" thread between two famous video game characters: the portly plumber from down under versus the world's fastest porcupine. Being an aficionado of these debates, you open up the thread to see a fairly even poll. Personally you think that the plumber has no chance. I mean he's a plumber! What does he even do? The commenters in the discussion listing off feats from the games and how they give an advantage in the fight. However you have an ace in your sleeve that will tip the poll in your favor:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention that the world's fastest porcupine has a super form that makes him invincible</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Mention that the plumber has no super human feats that would give him an advantage</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The commenters state that there is no item in the plumber's arsenal that can counter the porcupine's super form. The poll tips in the favor of the porcupine. THE PORCUPINE AND THE ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Other commenters mention that the plumber was able to throw a giant turtle into space. I don't know about you, but that's a pretty solid feat of strength. The poll tips in the favor of the portly plumber from down under. THE PORCUPINE AND THE ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>What gives the porcupine the advantage?</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 28-->
		<argument>
			<text>There was an article about a robot piloting JRPG game from Japan getting censored upon its localization to North America on the gaming website MGN. Logically this makes sense because the main heroine is under 18 and has multiple risqu costumes getting removed. You don't know why, but this irks you! Probably because these costumes turn you on. One commented that this censorship is a good thing because it's creepy to sexualize digitally young women. How can anybody be against sexy costumes!? You decide to put this pleb in his place by informing him why his beliefs are wrong:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention that the risqu costumes are a selling point of the game. If they remove them, it's less money for the company</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Mention that this removes content from the game, meaning US gamers get less content than Japanese gamers</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The commenters agree with you that it is not fair that Americans get less costumes. They discuss that it would be a good idea to at least replace the removed costumes with something else. The one commenter doesn't reply after that. Probably feels like a loser. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Wait a minute. This is a robot piloting simulator. You only see the characters in costume in the HUB world. Why are these sexy costumes a selling point for you?" Now everyone thinks you are a pervert! DIGNITY LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Who would you be playing most in this type of game?</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 32-->
		<argument>
			<text>Perusing the forums of your favorite games on the gaming website MGN, you found one thread where the OP was asking for advice on how to beat a certain boss in the game. You noticed that the OP's user name was a reference to a female character in an anime. You deduce that OP is female! You comment with the classic "A girl gamer? I didn't know that girls played games ;D" But your comment sends everyone to an uproar! "Guys like you are why people thinks gaming is a hobby for man children." You just wanted to meet a nice woman with similar hobbies, is that so bad? Defend yourself from these flames:</text>
			<choiceA>Be honest. Mention that you wanted to get to know a girl with similar hobbies as you</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Blame society for making it weird to hit on women through a digital medium</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"...society has nothing to do with how creepy and inappropriate your comment was" The pleb doesn't even know how to give a good comeback. I guess that's why you are the one with the college degree. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>M'lady replies to you! But it's not a good reply. "This is not the place to do that though. You should try out OkNarcissus. You'll find somebody there." You've been signed up for OkNarcissus for 5 years though and found nobody :( ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Back in the good old days, people would meet their significant others in the weirdest places!</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 33-->
		<argument>
			<text>Browsing through the video game forums for an erotic Japanese visual novel on the gaming website MGN, there was a poll for which girl was pursued romantically most in the game. To your horror, your waifu is in second place: "You guys have terrible taste in women. My waifu should be first!" you commented as the thread spiralled into a Waifu War. One commenter replies with "Our tastes don't cover flat-chests and boring personalities like yours do." Your waifu doesn't have a boring personality - she loves gaming and is shy and so moe! She's completely different than the other girls in the game:</text>
			<choiceA>"My playthrough had more sex scenes then yours did and had a happier relationship overall"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"Breasts and personality aren't everything you perverts!"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The commenters start comparing how many sex scenes each branching path had and your waifu had the most! Last you looked, your waifu closed the gap between first place and second place in the poll! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"And that leaves your waifu with what again?" Damn, that was a good comeback. You can't think of another trait your waifu has! Last you looked, the gap between first and second place has gotten bigger in the poll. NO TROPHY FOR SECOND PLACE</responseWrong>
			<hint>You are one lewd dude</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 44-->
		<argument>
			<text>Aiming to improve your skills for a competitive online multiplayer game on the gaming website MGN, you found threads saying your main character is bottom tier. Like hell your character is the worst; you beat all of your casual friends all the time! You open up a random thread and left the comment "Don't blame the character for your suckiness; blame yourself." One commented saying that "This character is supposed to be aggressive, but has useless moves. There are much better options." You feel like this is a personal attack, so you NEED to defend your character:</text>
			<choiceA>"I've placed in tournaments with this character, scrub."</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"Stop clinging to tier lists; they change."</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Commenters have pointed out that the game still does get updated and tweaked, so the tiers are volatile. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>One commenter asked you "Who are you? I've played a lot tournament players too." You answered with a random name to which nobody believes you. YOU ARE A FRAUD-ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Keep in mind you main one of the worst characters in the game</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 45-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, you wanted to voice your opinions on an indie game. Lately it's been getting a lot of press, but you think it's just "meh". You created a thread titled, "Most over-rated game of the year, am I right?" which spurred some negative press from the forum. While you did receive a lot of comments making fun of your bad taste, one commenter directly asked for your input: "Care to explain? This game's in the running for game of the year." Not one to leave a question unanswered you start typing up your reply:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention that the game just feels generic. And boring</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Mention that everyone is following the hype train like sheeple</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Some like-minded commenters do agree with you that the gameplay is your standard slog, but the game does have some good narrative environments and well paced story-telling. Since you were able to get people to agree with you, it's an ARGUMENT INCREASE</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"So you don't like it because it's popular? It's gamers like you that are what's wrong with the gaming industry." Well... I mean... There's thousands of people like you around, right? ARGUMENT DECREASE</responseWrong>
			<hint>You like what you like I guess</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 49-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, you saw a thread titled "Top 100 Video Games of All Time". You spent hours upon hours reading through the games and their descriptions to search for your personal favorite game of all time, only to find out that it didn't even make it to the honorable mentions! This filled you with despair; if your favorite game is not good enough for this list, are you not good enough? Feeling like you need to correct something in the world you decide to try to sneak in your favorite game into the "Top 100 Video Games of All Time" list:</text>
			<choiceA>Question why certain games are on there; there are some questionable choices on there</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Mention your favorite game and how it should be on the list</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The other commenters start to mention the games that they think don't deserve to be on the list. After counting the games they mentioned, you counted enough for the honorable mentions to make it into the list. After the honorable mentions, your favorite game should be next... WON THE ARGUMENT</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"I haven't played that game recently, but I don't remember much of it. Must not have been that good of a game if I can't remember it..." NOT GOOD ENOUGH</responseWrong>
			<hint>It's impossible to have a bias-free opinion</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 54-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, you saw a thread titled "Favorite Character Poll" for your favorite Japanese video game. You know for a fact that your waifu is the best character - possibly of all time! However another poster beat you to the punch as he claims that his waifu, also yours, is superior. You don't think of yourself as a jealous person, but your waifu belongs only to you; "Change your waifu. I called dibs." The man with lesser intellect replied with "Why can't we both share? ;)" Sharing waifus? That's lewd, dude! You plot a reply to prove that m'waifu belongs only to you:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention a super specific fact from some obscure scene from the anime spinoff about your waifu</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Say that sharing a waifu is gross and how it would be out of character for her</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Huh... I didn't even know that. I haven't had the chance to watch the anime yet." Since you know more about your waifu, her heart belongs to only you! ARGUMENT + 1</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"I mean our waifu has no problem being with two guys at once... It's part of her personality." NO! YOUR WAIFU IS PURE AND INNOCENT AND AND it's an ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>There's a difference between canon and head-canon</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 61-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, you posted a picture of your poorly recolored OC you called "Murdermaster the Porcupine" with the caption of "Pretty neat, huh?" Taking pride in your hard work, you were shocked when people started to make fun of your creation. "Did you just poorly trace over the original character and made it edgier?" No! Murdermaster has a dark and troubled back story and the character design reflects the character's personality. You decide to defend your hard work from these vision-less plebs:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention it was mainly the concept of the character that you were selling rather than the design</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Hastily add the character's back story into the image to make your vision clearer</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The thread turns into a topic of how the developer has no problems with adding characters like yours into each new iteration of the game such as Boomerang the Raccoon and Chocolate the Floating Dog. So who knows, maybe your character will be in a future game in spirit! ARGUMENT WON</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>You kind of went too far with your description of Murdermaster's back story as you mentioned murder and violence. The game series is rated E for everyone. Somebody saved your image before it got modded and you are now a meme. BECAME A MEME AND ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>There's no denying it - your design was pretty bad. Adding words won't fix it unless you fix the image first</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 65-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, you saw a poll between two similar team based shooting games. One game has been out for almost 10 years, while the other has been recently released. Overall the thread appears to be a civil debate with the poll being relatively 50/50. Being a connoisseur of the classics, you had a bias for the older game. You decide to leave your opinion: "The new game is garbage - nothing can even come close to being better than the classics." Feeling like you covered your bases, a commenter asked you to back up your claims:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention that the older game has been out for a longer time, the game has more content</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Mention that the newer game is less balanced, making the game volatile while the developers try to patch it</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"I do agree - there are some useless characters in the game and the devs seem to like nerfing the good characters to make things balanced." You then saw the poll shift in favor of the classic game. ARGUMENT WON</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"The game CURRENTLY has more content. The devs are constantly patching the game with new skins and new characters so this will no longer be an issue." You then saw the poll shift in favor of the newer game. Barnacles. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Wouldn't it be a shame to master one character and the developers nerf the character to be useless?</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 85-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, you were checking the forums for a newly released game being released on PC and console. There was a discussion about what the ideal platform is to play this game and without reading a single pixel, you commented "PC is the way to go, pleb. #PCMASTERRACE4LYFE" As per usual, the commenters don't take to kindly to your kind saying "Nobody is talking about the PC version any more. It's a completely busted port." While that may be the case, you have to stick to your guns and prove that the PC is always number one, baby:</text>
			<choiceA>Blame consoles - if the devs focused on the making the game for PC only, these bugs wouldn't exist</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Mention that it's possible to mod the game to fix those game breaking issues</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Yeah... porting over from console to PC hardly ever works." You noticed that the discussion deviated to comparing to other console games that had really bad PC ports. ARGUMENT WON</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"So the modding community would have to do the job for the developers? How long would that take?" Well I mean... somebody has to do it... right? ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Modding is cool, but shouldn't basic functionality come with the game?</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 89-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, there was a poll as to which RPG is superior: the number-based Japanese RPG or the action-oriented Western RPG to which Western RPGs were leading the polls. As much as you enjoy WRPGs and their dating simulator mechanics and sex scenes, you must defend the honor of the glorious nippon! You decide to focus on one commenter that mentioned "JRPGs are archaic and have game design aspects from the nineties. WRPGs have evolved with the times". HOW DARE THIS COMMENTER! EVERYTHING IS BETTER IN JAPAN! Strike down this commenter FOR THE HONOR OF JRPGs:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention that they are both good for different purposes - JRPGs for story and WRPGs for gameplay</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Bring up two games; a WRPG made 10 years ago that they keep remaking and one new JRPG that boasts multiple 10/10 scores</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>After you mentioned relevant games in this debate, you see that the poll swings in favor of the Japanese RPG. Looks like that filthy gaijin goes home! ARGUMENT WON</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"There are WRGs with great storylines. I've yet to see a JRPG have truly great gameplay". You see the gap widen between the Western RPG and the Japanese RPG! Nooooooo... ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>I think having examples of games would be beneficial for your case...</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 90-->
		<argument>
			<text>On the gaming website MGN, there was a thread where someone asked for advice in a game touted as the hardest modern video game as they kept on dying at the same spot. You did died a lot while playing this game... but these chumps don't know that! "I didn't die at all here. But then again I did do a run through of the game without dying so..." Feeling superior to these unskilled noobs, one commenter made fun of your skills; "I bet you died on the tutorial level" Well, he's not wrong... but you now must prove your skills to random strangers on the internet:</text>
			<choiceA>Create a theoretical strategy for that portion of the game</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Record yourself playing the game and upload it on to LouTube cutting out any instance of you dying and paste the link</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"I'll be sure to try that strategy out." Holy cannoli, this guy is using your strategy! You did see a few hours later that after trying it out, the OP is still stuck, but you consider this an ARGUMENT WON</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>You spent an entire week on the video... But even after all that time spent working on it, you saw on your video that you have zero views. OH WASTE OF TIME! ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
			<hint>Making a video is a lot of hard work... is it even worth it to win an argument?</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
	</arguments>

	<!--Arg: LouTube-->
	<arguments>
		<backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
		<headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
		<logo>logoLoutube</logo>
		<!--arg 7-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a "Top 10 Breasts in Anime" video to further study the subject matter that you consider yourself to be an expert in. However, the video fails to mention your waifu! Scientifically your waifu has smaller breasts than the other women on the list, but you feel that personality should have importance. In a list that ranks breasts. You leave a comment mentioning how they forgot your girl! One commenter replied that your waifu is a flat-chested high school girl and makes fun of your taste in women. Nobody makes fun of your waifu or your taste in the ladies! You start to type up a reply to defend your waifu's honor:</text>
			<choiceA>Ask where his waifu is on the list! The best way to destroy your enemy is through careful study</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Defend your position! Your girl and your will shall not waiver to this troll!</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The troll replies saying that you are way too obsessive over some anime character that's probably going to be forgotten in a year. What others call obsessive, you call dedicated. Besides it's better to be dedicated to an anime girl than it is to be dedicated to drugs. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>He mentions that his favorite character was number 1 on the list. The worst part of it all is that her breasts are actually much bigger than your waifu's breasts :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>You just have to hope that his waifu is not on the list</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 12-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube raring to watch your favorite Let's Player. Their most recent upload is actually the start of a playthrough of one of your favorite games as a child! However after 5 minutes of the video, it is clear that they are having a bad time with the game. They constantly joke at the game's expense that it's hard to control, a buggy mess, and call the soundtrack obnoxious. It's been a while since you played the game, but the fact that the Let's Player is mocking your childhood really steams your veggies! You start warming up your typing fingers:</text>
			<choiceA>Blame their lack of enjoyment on their lack of skill. If he was any better at the game, he would be having fun</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Call your childhood game a national treasure and that they don't know what they're talking about</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Other viewers of the video do mention the number of shortcuts and items that they are missing. They all start to make fun of the Let's Player's skills rather than focusing on the flawed game. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The commenters tell you to clean off you nostalgia goggles. When it's your turn to reply to it, nothing comes to your head. Maybe the game actually isn't as good as you remembered :| ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>It seems that the audience likes to point out flaws in flawed things...</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 15-->
		<argument>
			<text>Binge watching anime AMVs on the video-sharing website LouTube, you found an AMV for your favorite anime. But to your horror it was an AMV for a ship you detest - your waifu with a supporting character instead of the main character. You support MC x waifu because you project yourself on to the main character. You pause the video and state your opinion; "This ship is garbage". The creator of the video replied to your comment with "You are garbage. I do what I want you scumbag". This really shoots your scooter! Nobody calls you a creep in public domain. You scheme your retort:</text>
			<choiceA>"This ship is garbage, this AMV is garbage, and so are you! Please delete this video so we can move on with our lives."</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Mention that your waifu has more screen time alone with the main character than the supporting character</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Other viewers of the video do mention that the creator's preferred ship is less likely than yours! Everybody is on your side and everyone loves you! ++ARGUMENT</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The creator has not replied to you. Other viewers of the video mention that the only one who's worked up about the offensiveness of this ship is you. --ARGUMENT</responseWrong>
			<hint>The creator must've spent hours on this thing. Be cool</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 19-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a "Worst 5 Games of the Year" video. Agreeing with the hoard of poorly made indie games on Vapor that made it to the list, your heart instantly got hit with despair as you saw one of your favorite games of the year made it to the list. The narrator of the list said that the game was buggy, poorly designed, and offensive to the ears with bad voice acting. Personally you enjoyed the game because it's a game in a series you grew up with. You feel the need to defend the game... you can feel it in your spleen:</text>
			<choiceA>Say that there are worse games that came out this year that that should be on the list in its place</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Attack the list maker's sense of taste. Just because they had a bad time with the game doesn't mean others did too</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The commenters all start listing off bad games that should also be on the list. You pat your own shoulder as your work here is done. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>People agree with the narrator of the video: the game simply is not that great. They start asking where your sense of taste is and it really hurts your feelings :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>The creator of the video doesn't have all the time in the world to play video games</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 23-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were watching a social-experiment video on the video-sharing website LouTube where a muscle-bound pranker asks random women for sexual intercourse. Surprisingly, the pranker gets a few numbers from this. This rustles your jimmies because you tried this last week and you got slapped, the cops called on you, and got no numbers. You decide to voice your own opinion; "If a soft-hearted beta male did this, the outcome would be different!" Surprisingly, your comment was hit with dislikes and mean comments; "Poor baby! Who hurt you?" You are not a baby! A baby does not have a high IQ like you:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention your superior intellect and call the commenter a moron who knows nothing about psychology and philosophy!</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Use psychological science! For the coup de grace, link to a legitimate article you found on the internet</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>You link to an article called "Why Nice Guys Finish Last" and people comment on how it's a satire article. You know for a fact that it's a legitimate source of information because you saw this link on your MyFace news feed. These guys don't know what they are talking about, further cementing your intellectual lead! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>After you compared the difference between your intelligence, other commenters start to attack your child-like behavior and overall bitterness towards the world. ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Words hurt - they sting like bullets. Hopefully they don't have a reflector</hint>
			<accomplish>30</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 25-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a tribute video to a popular celebrity who recently died. You were about to leave your regards to one of your favorite celebrities, but one comment caught your eye: "What kind of cruel God would take him away from us?!" Your atheism got the better of you and you replied to the comment with "A God that doesn't exist" Tipping your fedora, you imagined yourself as a bad-ass for leaving that comment. However people start calling you an insensitive prick for mocking the death of a celebrity:</text>
			<choiceA>Explain that your intentions were misinterpreted; you meant to leave your condolences to the celebrity</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Use science and logical thought to temper your argument that God does not exist</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The commenters mention that it's hard to interpret your comment as anything else, but hey, at least they are not yelling at you! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>They continue to call you a prick because they think this video is not a good forum for discussing beliefs. The fools don't know that it's always a good time to discuss atheism! ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>People are obviously distraught about this</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 29-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching video created by a popular female cosplayer. Reading through the comments, one caught your eye saying "So beautiful!" Using this comment, you had a plan of defending her honor so she could see it and inevitably fall in love with you; "Beautiful as in physically attractive? How typical of lesser men such as yourself. When I think of beauty, I think of a women's passion and their dreams." You wait for m'lady to respond, but the only responses were from bullies calling you a try-hard. Defend your honor from these louts:</text>
			<choiceA>"I'm just stating how I feel. I miss the days when beauty was the whole package"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Make an underscore line and underneath it, type in "Everybody above this line is a loser!"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>While your plan to win over the heart and body of the female cosplayer failed, but your comment has a total of two likes! Overall success! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The original commenter removed the entire conversation from the video. Nooooooo! M'lady will never love you now :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>You're 28. Act like it</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 36-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a viral video where people prank gold diggers. Most of the comments poked fun at the women getting pranked, but something about this video really boiled your brownies! This video solidifies why you don't date; money is everything! You commented; "This is why 2D girls > 3D girls. 2D girls are loyal and don't care about how much you make!" This raised some questions; "...so you're admitting to whacking it to pixels then?" Beep yeah you do! Why should you take shame in it? You decide to explain to this pleb the infinite pros of pixelated women:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention when one watches "3D" porn, the video is rendered as a 2D image so they enjoy pixels too!</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Mention that it is a fetish. People like feet, other people like getting stepped on. You like pixels</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The commenter replied with a "Yeah, I guess that's correct, but it still weirds me out." The pleb agrees with you! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The commenter replied with a "The output is 2D, but there are no pixels involved with real women. Don't try to lump me in with you." Ouch! It was turned around back at you :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Sometimes the best way to win an argument is to have a mutual understanding with one another</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 37-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching the best scenes of your favorite cartoon show "Ponies in High School". Laughing so hard your neighbors probably think you're a lunatic, you scroll through the comments section. One comment caught your eye; "Bronies are freaks!" Whoa whoa whoa... "Ponies in High School" is more than just a show about ponies, it's a way of life. It's smart wit and good characterization often gets misinterpreted due to the colorful exterior. You decide to educate this man about something he probably doesn't care too much about:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention that the show does have a lot of intelligent humor for people of all ages</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Summon your bronies to smite this man where he stands!</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The sad man replied with a pathetic "Whatever, loser. Have fun with your cartoon for children." It's a shame that his intellect wasn't up to snuff to enjoy the show. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>None of your fellow bronies answered the call to come and aid you. You stand alone in your shame. ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>It's like 9 in the morning - people are supposed to be working</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 41-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were watching a top 10 list video for "Anime That Needs to Die" on the video-sharing website LouTube. Agreeing with the garbage anime on the list so far, you were surprised when you saw your favorite anime at number two. Wiping away the tears, you show the list maker a piece of your mind; "Number 2 shouldn't be on there! It's a classic you Neanderthals!" Your response garnered some disagreeing comments with one stating "It was a great series in the beginning, but it devolved quickly after the lead writer left." What does that even mean? He should be more constructive with his feedback:</text>
			<choiceA>"The anime has evolved as a series. More sub plots, more characterization, and more fan service."</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"Care to elaborate more with your critique of the anime? Nothing worse than a critic who doesn't know anything."</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Not really... The anime is garbage because of those reasons you listed." Thinking long and hard about how to reply, you come up with a cool "Well that's like, your opinion, man." The commenter never replies back and you take this as an ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Sure thing. After the first arc, the series devolved into a harem anime. All characterization goes out the window, endless filler episodes, bad animation ..." The commenter continues on and on listing off negative traits about the anime. Maybe the anime hasn't aged as well as you thought... ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>What do we even know about the commenter? Maybe they even have their own top 10 LouTube channel</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 42-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube going from video to video like a digital flu. Eventually you stumbled onto a music video of a female rapper who was singing about women with big butts. While the video did arouse you, the music hurt your ears. You left your opinion on the video with a "This sounds like garbage!" A few moments later, somebody with a lower intelligence replied to your comment. "Why are you even here then if you don't even like the music?" This poster is missing the big picture. Ignoring the commenter's question you start typing up a reply with one hand:</text>
			<choiceA>Mention that the people who enjoy this musician have a low IQ</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Say that this musician writes music with no substance</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The commenters complain that the musician writes annoying music now and how she used to write music with more heart before she became popular. Since people agree with you, this is an ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Another commenter replies saying that you probably clicked on the video because of the provocative thumb nail. You are quick to defend yourself, but the damage was already done. Everyone thinks you're a pervert now. DIGNITY LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>As a human being with ears, you are allowed to critique music</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 50-->
		<argument>
			<text>Skimming through the comments of the world championship for a MOBA game on LouTube, you spot a maiden who needs a white knight! Her comment read "My boyfriend pays more attention to this game than he pays attention to me :( lol" A man is not treating a woman the way she needs to be treated?! You decide to save her; "Fear not m'lady! You boyfriend does not know what he is missing out on. If I was your boyfriend, I would pamper you with attention." You wait for a few hours, but she still has not replied:</text>
			<choiceA>"No response? Have fun with your emotionally distant simpleton of a boyfriend"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"So... want to grab coffee some time?"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Lol no." M'lady may have provided a short response, but you made her lol. It's a step in the right direction so it's an ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Don't call my boyfriend a simpleton, freak." Ouch. M'lady didn't even notice that you have a higher than average IQ... REJECTED ON THE INTERNET AND ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Never assume your you'll make an ass our of u and me</hint>
			<accomplish>30</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 55-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a newly released trailer for a highly anticipated movie. Despite how many likes and views the trailer has, it failed to peak your interest for some reason. You left your opinion on the video; "This movie is gonna blow. As an atheist, if you study any form of science, you would not stand for the logical fallacies of this movie such as I." Some commenter with no taste replied to your comment; "Logical fallacies? It's a science fiction movie, moron." ACK! Nobody insults your intelligence! Show this sheep that you know what you are talking about:</text>
			<choiceA>Assure this Neanderthal that you have the superior IQ</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Call everyone hyped up for the movie a sheeple</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"What are you even talking about? What does IQ have to do with enjoying a science fiction movie?" Is he daft!? IQ means everything to everything to everyone! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Care to explain why?" It was at that moment that you didn't have a good reason for not liking the trailer; you are just being a contrarian and everyone you called a sheeple knows this now. ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Focus-fire is a great strategy in FPS games... maybe it'll help here</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 57-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a make-up tutorial... for some reason. Feeling like natural beauty is the best kind of beauty, you left a comment for the creator of the video: "M'lady, please remove all that horrid paint from your face. You are beautiful as is! You need not cheapen your beauty." Thinking that maybe m'lady will reply to your comment with desire, you were honestly shocked when people started flaming you! "Do you tell people this in person? It's a really creepy thing to tell people." How can it be creepy? You're giving away free compliments:</text>
			<choiceA>Pontificate about how people like your attackers are the reason society has so many body image issues</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Say that you do approach women in real life on trains and malls and tell them they'd look better without make-up</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Nobody replies to your five paragraph essay, but it does garner a handful of likes. That must mean that people share your belief on beauty and the downfall of society! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"That is beyond creepy. We wear make up for ourselves. Nobody wants to hear that from a stranger." And thus you got lectured by everyone on the internet because of how creepy you are. ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>There are some things about you that strangers on the internet don't need to know...</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 58-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a music video where the lead singer was wearing a fedora. Enjoying the tunes, you noticed the comments about the singer: "I love his hat! He's so cute!" This hurts because when you wear a fedora in public people avoid you like the plague! You give the world a piece of your glorious mind: "How come when I wear a fedora nobody calls me cute?" One commented "Because you're not cute, fedora or not." Peeved off that this troll called you ugly, you start summoning words into the screen:</text>
			<choiceA>Bring down the lead singer's attractiveness</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Insist that you are a cute guy</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>After mentioning that the lead singer was arrested and jailed a few months ago, you noticed that a lot of the discussions surrounding him are now about him being in jail. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"Pics or it didn't happen." Feeling confident, you posted a picture of yourself, but everyone started laughing at you like it was middle school all over again. You removed the photo but the damage has already been done. ARGUMENT LOST AND FEELINGS HURT</responseWrong>
			<hint>There's a difference between being confident and delusional. Don't be a delusional Debbie</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 64-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a podcast with an attractive male guest. The comments focused on the handsome guest which ticked you off because you aren't attractive and need attention. You bitterly commented "I laugh when I see attractive people. If we lived in Aztec culture, they'd be sacrificed to the gods for their beauty." After all, what you lack in attractiveness you make up for in guile! Someone replied "That's a strange way of coping with not being attractive." Did they assume your attractiveness? The nerve of this guy! You won't stand for being called ugly:</text>
			<choiceA>Do an image search for "attractive male" and say that you are him</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Dare the commenter to post a picture of them self</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Sure thing." After they posted a link to their photo, it turns out the commenter was a lovely woman! Niiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiice... ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>After searching for a handsome man to call yourself, you got jealous and bitter. You didn't even get a chance to post the photo because of how unfair the world is. ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>You'd probably get pissed if you saw an image of an attractive person. That's the type of person you are</hint>
			<accomplish>30</accomplish>
		</argument>

		<!--arg 69-->
		<argument>
			<text>Watching a review for a science fiction romance movie on the video-sharing website LouTube, you noticed that the professional reviewers sang nothing but praise. You had different opinions however; "I'd give it a 2/10. It's too happy for my liking. It may be a good movie for people with morals and a respect for humanity, but I don't have either". However, your post is on the verge of being flagged for spam; "Oh look, somebody trying way too hard to be edgy". How dare they discount your credibility! They don't have the right to make fun of you for your opinion:</text>
			<choiceA>Post a link to another video review for the same movie where the reviewer has the same views you do</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Get edgy. "You laugh at me because I am not normal. I laugh at you because you're all the same."</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"A forty minute video? Yeah, I have more important things to do with my time". HA! They lost the internet argument by default. ARGUMENT WIN BY DEFAULT</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>So your reply got flagged for spam 0.5 seconds after you hit the enter button. Hell, it may even be the worst comment in LouTube history! ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Once you go full edge, you never go back</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 74-->
		<argument>
			<text>Watching a video titled "Top Ten Fantasy Series" on the video-sharing website LouTube, you noticed that it was a well-spoken and thought out compilation of fantasy books written throughout history. However, feeling the need to spread your belief on the internet, you decide to leave an enriching comment; "Solid top ten list. However the list creator forgot the Bible as number one!" This opened the flood gates for the flames headed your way! "Nobody asked for your opinion you troll." Being hurt after being called a troll, you decide that you have to stop these flames OR DIE TRYING:</text>
			<choiceA>Compare the violence between other fantasy novels and the Bible</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Mention how the end of the video asked viewers to leave their personal opinions</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Nobody replied. I'm guessing you stunned the religious plebs with your advanced intellect! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"You are trying way too hard, it's pathetic." Ouch, I mean trying hard can be good, right? ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Stretching is a bad thing</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 77-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were watching a video of a celebrity discussing their views on politics on the video-sharing website LouTube. This ticked you off because celebrities exist only to entertain you - not to preach their messed up views on politics. So you decided to preach your own views on their views of politics; "These celebrities only exist for our amusement. Nobody should care about their political views and they shant prattle on." Your comment was received in a mostly negative light mentioning that "Celebrities are people too.":</text>
			<choiceA>Focus on how celebrities are not people - they are entitled, whiny babies who got lucky</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Write a long rant to support your view by using the "Dancing monkey with a jar" as a metaphor</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The other commenters mentioned how this particular celebrity complains about politics all the time. You turned the pitchforks at the celebrity! Saved! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"You are borderline psychotic." I think you went a bit too overboard with the dancing monkey metaphor... ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Focusing your argument on celebrities would be a good idea...</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 82-->
		<argument>
			<text>For some reason you were watching a fitness video on the video-sharing website LouTube. Feeling the blood gushing out of your nose like in one of those animes, you commented "I'm flustered over here! Certain parts of this video are straight up erotic! I'm going to need to have a hard spank session after this." Your comment was downvoted to oblivion and people are calling you a creep! Even m'lady replied to your comment - "Christ, dude! I'm deleting this video because of you." Defend your boner:</text>
			<choiceA>Science your way out of this: "Arousal is perfectly normal. I see features I'm drawn to, I get aroused. Science."</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Download the video for future use</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>You were able to successfully download the fitness video before m'lady deleted it. Nobody can stop you from draining the spuds now! MWAHAHAHA! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Just as you hit submit, it brought you to an error page as the video no longer exists... CURSES! NOW NO ONE CAN SEE HOW SMART YOU ARE! ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>She did say that she way going to delete her video - you must be fast!</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 83-->
		<argument>
			<text>Watching a video of an artist create video game prop items for sale on the video-sharing website LouTube, you felt the need to put down this person's work to cover up the fact you have no marketable skills - "While you did work hard on it, the logo's dimensions are all wrong and are the wrong shade of red. No one in their right mind would buy these." However your comment got slammed: "These are actually pretty hard to make. I'd like to see you do better." Oh please! A brainless monkey can do art, you just need the perfect vision:</text>
			<choiceA>"Disrespect my favorite game? Get SLAMMED by my superior knowledge on the subject!"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Say that you wanted to see your favorite game get represented correctly</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>The artist that uploaded the video says that they'll keep your criticism in mind for the next one. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>"But the artist was making the logo for the previous game. That game is more popular and would sell more. So you're knowledge on the subject isn't much, I take it." OH MAN! Should have fact checked, buddy. ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Do you really even have superior knowledge?</hint>
			<accomplish>25</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 84-->
		<argument>
			<text>You were watching a video of a popular vlogger on the video-sharing website LouTube. The vlogger covered news and current trends, but they made a reference to a Bible passage in one of the segments. Feeling shocked, you commented "You could've done without the reference to the Bible you sheep." However one of the viewers unfortunate enough to see your comment replied "It was literally 2 seconds of the video." Yeah? Well... this video is now unwatchable because of the reference to the fairy-tale book offending you:</text>
			<choiceA>Type in a snarky response: "Well that's two seconds too much!"</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Drop a logic bomb: "12 Disciples, 4 Gospels - quit being ignorant to the facts, sheeple"</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>While nobody replied to your snarky response, you did get one upvote! Somebody out there liked it! :D ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Despite dropping a logic bomb on LouTube, your comment was ignored... It looks like you're the only one who knows just how smart you are! ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>That snarky response is actually a little... humorous</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 88-->
		<argument>
			<text>Perusing the trending music page on the video-sharing website LouTube, you were trying to find new music to listen to; but you struggling to find anything good! On one song, you left some criticism as to why it's bad; "As an enlightened individual with an IQ of 167, this simple 4/4 time signature doesn't stimulate my mind." Feeling intellectually superior, you nodded in agreement at your own wit. However, a person you envisioned with clown make up replied to your comment - "Stop trying so hard". Trying so hard!? You need to prove to this clown that this isn't even your final form:</text>
			<choiceA>Reply to this scrub's comment hours after they wrote their reply</choiceA>
			<choiceB>"Polyrhythmic synth jazz is the only genre that provides nourishment to a brain like mine."</choiceB>
			<answer>ansB</answer>
			<responseCorrect>Nobody replied to your comment, but you know FOR A FACT that it was because your superior taste intimidated everyone away from replying. FOR A FACT! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>Nobody replied to your comment after spending so much time trying to serve this scrub... it seems like you tried too hard.  Again. ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>Describing the genre isn't bad I guess...</hint>
			<accomplish>15</accomplish>
		</argument>
		
		<!--arg 91-->
		<argument>
			<text>Spending the entire day on the video-sharing website LouTube, you watched a review of one of your favorite FPS games of all time. However, minutes into the video it's clear the reviewer thinks the game is less than perfect. "It's no wonder you hate the game; you're using the worst weapon type and the worst class in your b-roll. So much for professional integrity." However, this LouTuber has a rabid fanbase - "The b-roll shows early game footage - he was probably playing around with the game." You must defend the honor of your favorite FPS game with all you got:</text>
			<choiceA>Pull up a timestamp from the video that showcases the reviewer in the late game using the same weapon type</choiceA>
			<choiceB>Call this entire video review fake news</choiceB>
			<answer>ansA</answer>
			<responseCorrect>"Maybe the reviewer just picked a random class and weapon type for the video." replied the pitiful commenter. "Why would you play through the game like that just for video footage?" CHECK AND MATE! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
			<responseWrong>The rabid fanbase swarmed your comment thread and downvoted it to oblivion. Now your favorite FPS game has a bad review on it that will never be washed away... ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
			<hint>You know what wins internet arguments? Hard facts. With numbers.</hint>
			<accomplish>20</accomplish>
		</argument>
	</arguments>
</doc>