<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<doc>
	<!--Arg: Creddit-->
	<!--arg 0-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the pick up artist subreddit, you gave some random AFC advice on how to pick up women: if you want to attract a girl at a bar, you need to dress like a true gentlesir and stay in the corner ignoring everybody while trying to look mysterious. Your advice was so euphoric, that the other pick up artists started to call you out! They said that method of pick up is outdated, and nobody would go up and approach you if you ignored them. In order to regain your PUA cred, you can either:</text>
        <choiceA>Post a fabricated story where you game on 2 Asian women and took both of them home in one night</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Call everyone unintelligent beta males and say that they will never understand how alpha you are</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The AFC acknowledges your superior game and comments that he aspires to be a man like you one day. He ended up buying a fedora and an untailored suit.</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>The other men in the thread all call you pathetic and you can feel the AFC shake his head at you in disappointment through the internet.</responseWrong>
        <accomplish>20</accomplish>
		<backgroundColor>bkgCreddit</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrCreddit</headerColor>
        <logo>logoCreddit</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 7-->
	<argument>
		<text>While perusing on the gonewild subcreddit, you saw an image of a lovely lady bent over her desk. She was naked as the day she was born, but you can tell this girl is special. Feeling the need to defend her honor from the horde of horny creeps leaving pervy comments, you write "These boys are quick to comment on your physical perfection. I'm not like them; your personality is the most breathtaking part of you." However, these pervs are downvoting your post! They are calling you a "chump knight" and say that you are missing the point of the subcreddit. As this fair maiden's white knight, you must lift up your shield:</text>
        <choiceA>Call all of the horny creeps who frequent gonewild virgins who can't get any</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"M'lady deserves a real man who can admire her beauty! I tip my fedora to her."</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>Your original post got downvoted into oblivion. It's almost as if it never even existed! ARGUMENT IGNORED</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>Your insult backfires as they start calling you a virgin who can't get any. How the hell did they figure that out? Are they stalking your MyFace page?! HEART BROKEN :(</responseWrong>
        <accomplish>25</accomplish>
		<backgroundColor>bkgCreddit</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrCreddit</headerColor>
        <logo>logoCreddit</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 16-->
	<argument>
		<text>While obsessively partaking in the social networking website creddit, you search for the answers to one of life's biggest questions: why do nice guys finish last? And by search I mean you wrote a whiny essay where you complain about how nice guys finish last, douchebags always win, and how the women are missing out for not choosing to date you. After submitting your soliloquy, you read the replies and they disagree with you! The average response was along the lines of "Nice guys don't finish last, boring guys do" and "Quit being so predictable". Wiping away your nice guy tears, you type your response:</text>
        <choiceA>Lie about yourself; "I am not a boring guy! I know kenjutsu and I am writing a book!"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"You guys are wrong. It's a scientific fact" and send them a link to an article that will augment your argument</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>You may have only learned kenjutsu through online videos and am writing a fanfiction about ponies, but they fall for your bluff. They suggest that rather than whine about your dateless life, you should focus on your passions. I mean... at least nobody is yelling at you? LIFE LESSONS FOR THE WIN</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>You linked to an outdated late 90's article written by a has-been pick up artist. It had sexy pop-ups, uses the Comic-sans font, and it hurt your argument more than it helped. Research more next time :| ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
        <accomplish>20</accomplish>
		<backgroundColor>bkgCreddit</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrCreddit</headerColor>
        <logo>logoCreddit</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 17-->
	<argument>
		<text>Browsing through the social networking site creddit, you stumbled upon the thread "European vs. Japanese Swords". You scoff at the morons who believe European swords stand a chance against the glorious Nippon blade, however it's actually a fairly even argument. A commenter posted a 4 paragraph essay explaining why European swords are stronger; the European design craft a more sturdy blade due to science and physics! Peeved that somebody on the internet brought great dishonor to your favorite weapon of warfare, you decide to educate this pleb on the art of Nippon sword fighting:</text>
        <choiceA>"I am an expert with the katana and let me learn you a little bit of something about the lightning fast Iai style..."</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"Nippon steel is the strongest steel. The blacksmiths fold it 1000 times. Do you even know what tempering is, filthy Gaijin?"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The commenter does mention that yes, a katana can strike much faster than a European blade. He mentioned that it's not gonna penetrate European armor, but at this point you don't care as it's a WIN OF AN ARGUMENT!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>The commenter linked you to a scientific experiment clip on LouTube of a European blade shattering a katana. When it was the katana's turn to strike the European blade, it actually cracked itself just like your heart did when you LOST THE ARGUMENT :(</responseWrong>
        <accomplish>15</accomplish>
		<backgroundColor>bkgCreddit</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrCreddit</headerColor>
        <logo>logoCreddit</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 22-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social networking site creddit, you were looking at images of lovely ladies on the gonewild subcreddit. You saw one picture of a woman of Asian descent and instantly fell in love. You started to type a personal message to M'lady to woo her. "I'd love to get to know you better :)" After a few minutes, she still hasn't replied to which you started messaging her reasons why she should date you. Finally she replies to you with: "I'm busy." Clearly you deserve a better response than that! You start to put in everything you have into a last ditch effort to win her over:</text>
        <choiceA>Demonstrate higher value! "I am a hardworking man who can provide for you, m'lady."</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Neg her; lower her defense then sweep her off her feet! "I'd talk to you you, but you're not into nice guys!"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>"I am. I just have no interest in you." Did m'lady just confirm she likes nice guys?! Maybe one of these days, she will have interest in you! ARGUMENT STRETCHED TO A WIN</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"What the hell is wrong with you? Do you try that line on girls in person? Creep." I don't know what you were thinking please stop this. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
        <accomplish>15</accomplish>
		<backgroundColor>bkgCreddit</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrCreddit</headerColor>
        <logo>logoCreddit</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 35-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social networking site creddit, you were feeling more entitled than usual and made a post: "I am sick of being a nice guy! I helped a girl pass a class in college and she didn't even go on a date with me! I'm going to be an alpha male because that's what girls are into!" Immediately your post was hit with negative feedback with people bashing your so-called skewed views; "Just because you helped a girl doesn't mean she owes you anything. The fact she didn't like you doesn't have anything to being an alpha male." Such an ignorant thing to say. Being an alpha male means everything:</text>
        <choiceA>"I'll show you... I'll show all of you!" then create a new account with the word Alpha in the name</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"You guys don't know what you are talking about! Why am I single then?"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>Well I mean they don't know your new account and you avoided the original thread. Your quest to being an alpha male has begun with your new creddit account! You're feeling really good about yourself now! ARGUMENT AVOIDED</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"You are single because you are a bitter passive-aggressive beta male. I suggest speaking to a therapist because clearly you have some issues you need to sort through." You don't need to go to a therapist... alpha males don't believe in that! ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
        <accomplish>25</accomplish>
		<backgroundColor>bkgCreddit</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrCreddit</headerColor>
        <logo>logoCreddit</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 39-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social networking site creddit, you uploaded a photo that you've been working hard on! You took four photos of yourself and created a four panel comic. In the comic, you added the text "Hai girls! Umm... did you know that when you wear make up nice guys think you're ugly?" You wanted to make a statement that natural beauty is the best beauty and a four-paneled comic was the best way to do so. Thinking that this was your key to fame, you were shocked when it was hit with negative criticism! "This must be a joke! Please tell me this guy's not for real." You didn't mean for it to be a joke so you decide to defend yourself:</text>
        <choiceA>Flip flop. Say that this was all just a joke and then promptly delete the thread</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Stand your ground! Mention that this is a statement about society and their views of beauty</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>Nothing really happened after you deleted your post which may have been the best option. Nobody has ever seen your four-paneled comic again. AVOIDED BECOMING A MEME</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>Somebody made a response comic to counter yours! She made a comic that shows her reacting to your comic then applying a dubious amount of make up on her face. You have become a poster boy for cringe pictures. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
        <accomplish>30</accomplish>
		<backgroundColor>bkgCreddit</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrCreddit</headerColor>
        <logo>logoCreddit</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 40-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social networking site creddit, you were indulging yourself with information on the atheism subcreddit. One topic asked "Hi all, I was wondering what age you were when you found out you were atheist. I need the information for one of my religion classes." You smirked as you commented with "I've been atheist straight out of the womb! Do us all a favor and enroll in some atheism classes." One person commented "Why are you having such a hissy fit, man? He just needs data for his class." If being scientifically correct is wrong, then you don't want to be right! You just wanted to spread knowledge to the ignorant:</text>
        <choiceA>Post an image of a meme titled "U mad, bro?"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"I wasn't having a hissy fit! The topic was tame until you commented!"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>Your verbal assailant does not reply after a while. Maybe you scared him away with your higher intelligence and clever usage of comedic memes! ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"You are literally having a hissy fit now!" They also mention that you are just as pushy and annoying as those pushy annoying religious people you think you're better than. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
        <accomplish>15</accomplish>
		<backgroundColor>bkgCreddit</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrCreddit</headerColor>
        <logo>logoCreddit</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 43-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social networking site creddit, you were indulging yourself with information on the atheism subcreddit. One topic was titled "Do you capitalize the letter G in god?"  You replied with a "Do you want to be wrong and grammatically incorrect all the time? If the answer is yes, capitalize the G." Patting yourself on the back because your wit is A+, you were peeved when one commenter ignored your wit and replied with "Typically if you use God as a name then you have to capitalize it. If you're talking about higher beings, then it stays lower-cased." How dare this pleb spread this slander! Kill him with information before the slander spreads:</text>
        <choiceA>Shift the focus of the debate: "That's stupid. What kind of name is God anyway?"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Bring up a professionally written article where the word god is lower-cased</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>Other like-minded individuals did comment talking about the origin of the name God. Not what you intended, but you completely de-railed the conversation. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"The article is talking about polytheistic gods. It's supposed to be lower-cased..." What did I tell you about reading the article you are referencing before you post it? ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
        <accomplish>15</accomplish>
		<backgroundColor>bkgCreddit</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrCreddit</headerColor>
        <logo>logoCreddit</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 46-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social networking site creddit, you were indulging yourself with information on the atheism subcreddit. One question shows up on the front page: "Does religion technically count as a cult?" Willing to share your wisdom, you provide an enlightening answer: "Of course. Religion turns it's followers into mindless sheep, and is entirely useless." However, not many other people can handle your wisdom: "Do you even know what the definition of cult is? The adults are having a discussion here." What a pleb! You're probably even older than this guy! You decide to prepare your thesis:</text>
        <choiceA>Quickly acquire the definition of the word cult from the encyclopedia</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Pull out a lengthy article where the author uses the word cult to describe religion</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>"Yeah, I'm not reading that." Wow,what a bum! Due to the participant dropping out of the debate, you count this as an ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"Did you just copy and paste the first sentence from the online encyclopedia?" Next time, take your time with research. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
        <accomplish>15</accomplish>
		<backgroundColor>bkgCreddit</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrCreddit</headerColor>
        <logo>logoCreddit</logo>
	</argument>

	<!--Arg: MyFace-->
	<!--arg 1-->
    <argument>
		<text>Earlier on in the day, you commented on an attractive woman's MyFace profile picture by saying that she looks rather ravishing. Later on, you signed back on to see one new notification. Maybe she likes your genuine compliment and would like to go on a date with you! But a wild boyfriend appears! M'lady's boyfriend looks like a stupid meathead jock, and he replied to you on the girl's picture: "Who is this dweeb? Dont talk to my girlfriend, you creep." It appears that he is asking her, but you decided to cut the middle-man out and inform this pleb of who you really are:</text>
        <choiceA>Tell the girl's boyfriend how much better you are than him. He's a stupid muscle bound jock who just HAS to be a bum!</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Write a one word reply with the correct way to spell the word "don't"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The girl ends up unfriending you from MyFace. Now your euphoric online presence won't bless her news feed. It's her fault she's dating a meatheaded bum. ARGUMENTWIN++</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>Despite his jock-ish looks; he has a solid career in political science and generally has his life together. Your ego takes a huge blow to the nads :(</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>30</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMyFace</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMyFace</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMyface</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 3-->
	<argument>
		<text>While you were scrolling through your news feed on the social media website MyFace, you saw that you got a notification! Filled to the brim with excitement, you see that it's just your mother commenting on your wall: "There's more to life than video games and the Internet. You are rotting your life away." The rest of your family agrees with her by liking her comment and replying to it. You suddenly became more introspective. You thought that you were doing fine in life; nice room, great sense of style, combat skills, etc. Have you been distracting yourself from the truth? You start to think of a way to reply to your own mother:</text>
        <choiceA>Ignore the post and delete it from your wall. What's she going to do? Ground you? Psh, you're an adult!</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Blame your failures on your upbringing. You only never accomplished anything in life because of her!</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>After writing multiple paragraphs on how everything is her fault, she replies "You're absolutely right. I not only gave you everything growing up, but I spoiled you." You're life may be hollow and you may be a spoiled-brat, but she still agreed with you! LIFE IN SHAMBLES BUT ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>Your family members who liked your mom's post all started posting on your wall with posts like "I saw what your mom said, you should listen to her" and started lecturing you. Can't run away from family. They'll find you. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>30</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMyFace</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMyFace</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMyface</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 9-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social media site MyFace, a relationship status update popped up on your wall. To your horror it is your best friend that you've been in love with since high school. You felt your will to live start to waiver. After a few minutes of deep despair and crying into your pillow, you regain your composure and try to fight for her! You stalked her new boyfriend's MyFace wall for research. He appears to be a typical muscle bound pleb and she can do much better! Like for a man who has a superior intellect. Somebody like you! Armed with a keyboard and your gifted way with words you start to craft up a private MyFace message with the intent of winning her over:</text>
        <choiceA>Profess your love for her!</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Badmouth her new boyfriend, telling her she deserves much better</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>She replies to your message: "Sorry, I don't think I will ever see you in that way. But I still want to be friends with you." She did say that she doesn't THINK she will ever see you that way, so there may still be a chance! DELUSIONAL BUT ARGUMENT WIN I GUESS</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>She replies to your message: "You haven't even met him! You do this every time I date somebody new; you freak out and tell me how stupid I am. Just stop talking to me; you're a toxic friend." ARGUMENT AND FRIENDSHIP LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>30</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMyFace</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMyFace</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMyface</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 13-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social media site MyFace, everyone seems to be posting about a tragedy that struck in a city in Africa. You decide to let the world know that you care about the tragedy and make a status post about it. After thinking long and hard on how to formulate your words, you come up with "Is the culprit African? Because they are A-frican bitch! My heart goes out to the victims." However a few minutes after writing the status, people on your friends list started calling you an insensitive prick! You just wanted to spice up all the gloom with a joke! You try to come up with a response to all of the people that misinterpreted your status:</text>
        <choiceA>Apologise profusely. They misinterpreted your concern as insensitivity</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Say that you have a bunch of black friends</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>They accept your apology and urge you to delete your status. You never did, but people stopped calling you a prick at least. ARGUMENT WIN I GUESS</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>They comment saying that was not the issue they had with your status. Now everybody is calling you a racist too. You also became viral and had your status screen captured for other social media outlets :( ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMyFace</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMyFace</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMyface</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 14-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social media site MyFace, someone in your friends list made a status saying she made it out of surgery just fine. Usually you would ignore this type of post, but you saw that the most liked comment on her post was from her mother; "Thank God you're okay. I love you." It's time to school a concerned mother with facts about religion. You replied to the mother's comment saying "God doesn't exist. She made it because of the skill of the surgeon." Suddenly people started flaming you asking what the hell is wrong with you. The mother replies with "I was just being grateful that my daughter was okay." You start to reply to these attacks against your belief with:</text>
        <choiceA>"I was just pointing your thanks towards the surgeons that deserve it"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"Please provide scientific proof that there is a God out there and I will take back what I said"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>Your comment has been deleted by the girl's mother. You consider re-writing your comment, but you considered that she learned her lesson that God doesn't exist. ARGUMENT WIN++</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>The mother replies with "We are all grateful for the surgeon, it was just a figure of speech." before your comment was bombarded with people calling you a moron. You just wanted to educate those less intelligent than you :( ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>20</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMyFace</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMyFace</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMyface</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 18-->
	<argument>
		<text>You recently found the MyFace profile of a woman you met in the real world. She was working at the mall and you asked her coworker for her full name. She's perfect; has colorful hair, is a girl, and didn't walk away while talking to you! You sent her a few introductory messages. However she seemed lukewarm to your woo-ing attempts; taking a long time to reply, one word answers, etc... You decide to go for broke; "Assuming you haven't blocked me or deleted your account, I take it that you weren't creeped out by me tracking you down. I think you are beautiful. I understand I'm not much, but I would worship you." After some waiting, she has not replied yet so you decide to give this last message your all:</text>
        <choiceA>Neg her: "You're not very talkative. If I had to rate your charisma, I'd give you a 0/10!"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Fish for a response: "Won't you talk to me? I am a nice guy and we have similar interests."</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>She seems to have deleted her MyFace profile. Her default picture is now a default image. Not sure what to make of it, she probably is going through some tough times and will contact you once she gets online again. ARGUMENT... I don't even know :\</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>The girl ends up writing a large essay covering such topics such as how much of a creep you are for stalking her, her rejecting you, and how if you have to tell her that you are a nice guy, you probably are not. "By the way, I just moved here and didn't have internet so I couldn't reply fast enough. Good thing you spammed me with messages because it shows what kind of person you are." :( ARGUMENT AND GIRL OF YOUR DREAMS LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>30</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMyFace</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMyFace</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMyface</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 21-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social media site MyFace, you were scrolling through your news feed until you spotted a sad MyFace post from a pretty girl. You don't actually pay attention to the contents of the sad post, you just saw that there was a sad girl and as a white knight, you took it upon yourself to make this girl happy. You decide to bless her eyes with a sonnet of words: "M'lady, your smile is the most beautiful part of you. Please stop frowning." However the harlot did not reply to your reply in a timely fashion. Meanwhile, she is replying to the replies after yours. Is she ignoring you? You demand to be thanked for your thoughtful words!:</text>
        <choiceA>"Please let me in!"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"You are perfect the way you are"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>M'lady acknowledged you! He replied to your comment with a sincere "Haha, thank you" Her comment could carry you through the years as you mark off for another fair maiden saved and an ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>The girl never replied to you despite replying to other people on her status. It seems like this white knight just got another scar on his armor :( ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>25</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMyFace</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMyFace</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMyface</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 31-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social media site MyFace, you posted a picture of you and your newest pony figurine because the world needed to see it I guess. One of your like-minded friends from college commented on it saying "That's pretty cool, man! Not my favorite pony, but the quality is excellent! Where did you buy it? I'd like to buy a few" Not his favorite pony!?!?! Ever since college, this tool has always been a thorn in your side with your differences in opinions. From music to games and now ponies?! This pleb doesn't deserve the title of your friend:</text>
        <choiceA>"You are dead to me" then unfriend the sucker!</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"Not your favorite pony!? You are the king of bad taste."</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>He replied with "Yeah, I guess. Where did you buy it?" You have the upper hand here so you hold on to the information and don't reply to him. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>Your ex-friend sent you a text; "Dude, what the hell is wrong with you? You freak out every time we have a difference in opinion. Get over yourself" You received a new friend request from him and accepted because that's what you do. ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>25</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMyFace</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMyFace</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMyface</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 38-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social media site MyFace, you notice that a cherished actress is now in jail and people are making mean jokes about her. How cruel; somebody makes a mistake and now society throws them to the lions! Everybody makes mistakes! You decide to defend this celebrity's honor by commenting on the article: "What is the matter with you lot? We all make mistakes, but the moment a famous person makes one, you're all quick to turn on them!" Somebody replied to your comment with a "What she did was unforgivable!" This actress is a national treasure, and you will not let this ignorant pleb sully the actress' name:</text>
        <choiceA>"That's bull! Everyone can be forgiven!"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"Calm down everyone! She's going through some hard times, and we should support her!"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The commenters start feeling pity for the actress because she was going through some stressful times before she ended up in prison. ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"She took drugs then murdered 12 people! Did you even read the article?" That's what you get for just skipping to the comments section... ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMyFace</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMyFace</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMyface</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 47-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the social media site MyFace, you posted a selfie of yourself and a waifu body pillow. One of your "normal" friends commented, "This is pretty weird, man. You're never going to find a girl with that." How dare he insults your game! This caused an eruption of emotions to burst out of you: "OF COURSE I KNOW WHAT AN ORGASM FEELS LIKE I PULL AT BARS, PLEB." After regaining your composure, you immediately delete your reply and start to put some thought into your next reply:</text>
        <choiceA>Talk about your numerous sexual exploits you have totally been a participant in</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Explain that people have different tastes and hobbies and that people need to be open</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>"I still find it pretty weird, but whatever you want to do man. I recommend that you don't post these so everyone can it because it is a taste not everyone can understand." ...so he agrees with you? ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"Wait, a bag of sand?" ...he immediately discovered that you do not know what you are talking about. A bag of sand, is that the best you could come up with? ARGUMENT LOST-FRAUD DETECTED</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>30</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMyFace</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMyFace</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMyface</logo>
	</argument>

	<!--Arg: OkNarcissus-->
	<!--arg 1-->
	<argument>
		<text>While on the prowl for a hot Asian or white girlfriend on the online dating website OkNarcissus, you received a message from a girl calling you a creep. You look back into your hundreds of sent messages searching for her name to see that you sent this girl a harmless message: "Dear M'lady! I would love to make love to you underneath the sky, the sun, and the stars. Would you allow me to have that honor?" Obviously hurt at being called a creep you start to type a message back:</text>
		<choiceA>"I have no idea what I did wrong, but if you somehow felt offended by my harmless message, I apologize whole-heartedly, m'lady."</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"Nevermind. I shouldn't settle for dumb broads who are below me."</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The girl doesn't respond. In fact, you feel like she probably blocked you from ever contacting her again. It's her loss anyway; if she knew that you made $1K during the summer, maybe she would change her mind. You take this as an ARGUMENT WIN</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"How on Earth are you a human being? Your first message was asking if I would allow you to "make love to me"; how could I not be offended by that? I hope you don't talk to other girls on this website like this, you sexless weirdo". ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgOkNarc</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrOkNarc</headerColor>
        <logo>logoOknarc</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 4-->
	<argument>
		<text>You logged onto the online dating website OkNarcissus for the 20th time today and noticed that you received a message from a girl! Somebody actually is showing interest in you on the internet! Ecstatic, you open up her message: "Hey! I haven't seen many fans of the Bearsona series on this website. How are you today?" You clicked on her page and saw that despite having similar hobbies and tastes; she is quite homely. Curses! Why couldn't she be a smoking hot white/Asian girl with glasses!? Stroking your beard, you start to think of a way to respond:</text>
		<choiceA>"EW! GROSS! YOUR NOSE IS WHERE YOUR MOUTH SHOULD BE AND YOUR MOUTH IS WHERE YOUR NECK SHOULD BE AAAAAAHHHH!!!!"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"My apologies, but you are not within my league. I desire a fit classy Asian/white lady with glasses and bangs."</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The girl doesn't respond, but she did view your profile after you sent the message. She probably cried herself to sleep. Feels good to be such a heart breaker! It's her fault for being average looking anyway. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"Okay, good luck with that. You should have no problem getting one of those." the homely girl replies. You can feel the sarcasm ooze from the computer screen. You just got rejected by a homely girl! It's not like you care or anything (but really, you do care). ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>25</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgOkNarc</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrOkNarc</headerColor>
        <logo>logoOknarc</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 11-->
	<argument>
		<text>You logged onto the online dating website OkNarcissus to speak to a woman you have been messaging on and off for 3 days. So it's quite serious. You decide it's time to move your relationship to the next level! You send her a message: "M'lady! May I inquire you for your number? I would love to send you photos of my daily ritual!" Your heart beat races while you wait patiently for her reply. However after many hours, she still hasn't rewarded you with a message. You even see that she is online, so you know she read it! Peeved off, you start to write a message to her letting her know how you feel:</text>
		<choiceA>"Way to throw away 3 days of getting to know each other, ya dumb broad!"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"C'mon, baby I'm good for iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiit!"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>Still no response. It appears that she has deactivated her dating profile. You assumed that she realized she made a mistake for not prioritizing you and stepped out of the dating pool. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"Don't call me a dumb broad! I just stepped out for a few hours. It's a good thing you messaged me though because it shows exactly what kind of child you are." Ouch! There's plenty of fish in the sea, man. RELATIONSHIP LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>20</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgOkNarc</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrOkNarc</headerColor>
        <logo>logoOknarc</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 12-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were in a deep dive search for your future waifu on the online dating website OkNarcissus and stumbled upon a profile of a model-esque Goddess. She could be on magazines or something! However, her looks seem to be her only appeal; her profile reads "Do not message me if you do not meet any of these requirements" and proceeded to list off traits in men she finds attractive such as being physically fit, having fulfilling career, etc... How dare she instantly rejects those based on such superficial standards! If she gave you the chance, you would be able to woo her with your superior intellect. You decide to try your luck by talking to her anyway:</text>
		<choiceA>"I believe it's wrong for you to filter out a large amount of men based on such narrow parameters."</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"Hey."</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The girl doesn't respond. She also mentioned in her profile that she wouldn't respond to one word first messages. Well uh... you weren't too emotionally attached, so it wasn't so bad I guess. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>She did view your profile, but never replied to your message. You almost had her :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>10</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgOkNarc</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrOkNarc</headerColor>
        <logo>logoOknarc</logo>
	</argument>

	<!--arg 30-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were desperately clicking through the online dating website OkNarcissus and stumbled upon a profile of an attractive woman. Reading through m'lady's profile, she appears to value a man's intelligence and personality over muscle. So pretty much, you're her dream guy! However before you can work up the words to woo her, you spot a typo in her profile. "Please us proper grammar in your message and we can get along!" US!?!?!?! Such irony! Instead of being your usual suave self, something within you compels you to write "Don't you mean 'use'?" However after a few minutes of waiting, she still hasn't replied to you. You decided to fish for a message:</text>
		<choiceA>Be a bad ass snarker: "You should reply to my message. You'll learn more about grammar if you do."</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Explain the joke: "Get it? Because you misspelled something in your profile! :P"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The girl doesn't respond. However, you looked at her profile and she fixed the spelling error. It seems like you passed on some knowledge and made the world a better place! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"No thank you. You kind of creep me out." Ouch :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgOkNarc</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrOkNarc</headerColor>
        <logo>logoOknarc</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 34-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were desperately clicking through the online dating website OkNarcissus and stumbled upon the profile of an attractive fair-haired maiden. Reading through m'lady's profile, she seems to be flawless: is a girl, nerdy, colorful hair, no children... just like in your Japanese animes! However your elven eyes stumble onto m'lady's religious beliefs. Turns out that she is a devout Christian. You cannot fathom ever dating a woman who worships an imaginary cloud in the sky! Disgusted to the core, you made it your mission to win her over to the side of atheism:</text>
		<choiceA>"You do realize that God isn't real, right?"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"You would be more attractive if you weren't religious."</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The girl doesn't respond. However, you looked at her profile and she added a disclaimer: "Must love God." While you didn't sway her to the light side of atheism, you at least helped other men not waste their time. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"I could say that you would be more attractive if you were Christian." After that, she just kept on lecturing and lecturing... you called this a lost cause and gave up on trying to woo m'lady :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgOkNarc</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrOkNarc</headerColor>
        <logo>logoOknarc</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 48-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were desperately clicking through indexes of the online dating website OkNarcissus and stumbled upon the profile of an attractive fair-haired woman. You read in a PUA book that erotic first messages lead to more sex; so you tried it with this girl: "M'lady, I just thought of your perfect bare body as I caressed myself. I thought I should let you know." After a moment, she replied with "Creepy!" A one word reply!?!? Surely your message should've warranted more than that! You decide to not let that get to you and keep on seducing her. Make your second message really mean something:</text>
		<choiceA>"I would like you to know that I am caressing myself once more awaiting your reply."</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"Would you like to meet up one of these days?"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>"Never in a million years." So maybe you'll have a chance after the million years are up? ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"Keep on caressing, weirdo." M'lady's profile then seemed to have been deactivated. When you were done with caressing yourself, you felt sad about being called a weirdo. It worked in the books, dammit! ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgOkNarc</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrOkNarc</headerColor>
        <logo>logoOknarc</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--Arg: MGN-->
	<!--arg 5-->
	<argument>
		<text>On the gaming website MGN, they posted up an article about the game Alive and Dead: Hardcore Beach Games Edition. You looked over to your collector's edition on your bookshelf with a sense of pride and urgency! After scrolling through the comments of the article, one person commented: "The only people who enjoy this game are anti-social perverts who can't get laid." This guy is highly misinformed! You enjoy these types of games AND you are totally sexually active. Yeah, you had your girlfriend visit from Canada over the summer that you totally had relations with. Insulted, you type up a response to this commenter:</text>
		<choiceA>Mention your numerous sexual exploits that are totally numerous. Give juicy details such as positions and the dirty talks</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Mention the gameplay mechanics and the game's longevity. At the game's core, there is more than just fan service</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>You mention the game's merit, and the commenter apologizes. It's okay though; a pleb like him would've never been able to understand the quality of Alive and Dead: Hardcore Beach Games Edition without your help. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>The commenter called you out! He said that he found you on MyFace and said that you are one of those anti-social perverts! He then proceeds to post links that lead to pictures of you, and it really hurts your feelings. Surprisingly, the website doesn't have any anti-bullying rules :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>20</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMGN</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMGN</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMgn</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 10-->
	<argument>
		<text>On the gaming website MGN, they posted up a review for the thirteenth instalment of a popular JRPG series. Unfortunately the plebs running MGN gave the game a paltry score of 6/10 stating the sequel fails to capture the fantasy and the adventure of the games before it. They say that the game is too linear, the characters are unlikable, and the gameplay is nonexistant. You haven't played the game yet, but you love the series and it deserves better! You look through the reviewer's past publications and note that he gave low scores to a lot of your cherished games. Now this jerk made it personal! You start to craft your words onto the comments section of the review:</text>
		<choiceA>Call the reviewer a troll who gives low reviews to games just to get extra hits on the review</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Mention the game's positive points. You haven't played it yet, but you know it's good! Look at those graphics and soundtrack!</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The commenters do mention that the reviewer is known to do that once in a while. They start to question if this review is legitimate or if the reviewer is trolling again. TURNING IT AROUND ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>The commenters mention that while the music and graphics are good, that doesn't make up for the nonexistant gameplay. I mean you did have some holes in your argument... ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMGN</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMGN</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMgn</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 20-->
	<argument>
		<text>On the gaming website MGN, you saw a review for a Plebstation 4 exclusive game that got a measly 7/10. Typically you're a PC gamer, but if you had to side with either of the consoles, you would choose the Bonebox. When you saw the review, it felt like your team won and that the console war was over! You rush to the comments section and without a thought wrote "R.I.P Plebstation 4. No match for the mighty Bonebox!" However the Plebstation fanboys won't take this sitting down; they all comment saying that the Plebstation 4 is winning the console war, but you are more educated than these plebs. You decide to educate these fanboys:</text>
		<choiceA>Mention exclusives! The Plebstation 4 has a lot of mediocre exclusives; quantity is not equal to quality!</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Mention sales figures! The Plebstation 4 is nothing compared to the past consoles!</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The commenters pathetically try to defend their console saying that their killer app is coming out later in the year, but you know it will probably get another 7/10. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>They mention that Plebstation 4 is selling much more than the Bonebox. YOU GOT BONED AND ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMGN</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMGN</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMgn</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 24-->
	<argument>
		<text>On the gaming website MGN, there was a thread where OP was asking for opinions on which console to buy between the Bonebox and the Plebstation 4. Obviously the better of these two choices is the PC as it has modding support and is not limited by the laws of the universe. You reply to the thread with "PC Master Race; console plebs gonna hate." This however put a target on your back from the other commenters as they all started to flame you saying "PC wasn't even an option." and asking you to learn how to read. You, an avid reader of pony fanfiction do know how to read and think that PC gaming is the best thing since underwear. You have two ways of replying to these console dweebs:</text>
		<choiceA>Mention that the PC has a wider library, a mod support, and can upscale while the consoles can't</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Post a meme about the pathetic console plebs being too poor for the PC Master Race</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The commenters say that while they agree with you that the PC is wonderful, it still was not an option in the thread. They insult your intelligence, but at least they agree with you! PEOPLE AGREE WITH YOU ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>The OP replied saying that he already has a gaming PC, they just want the console exclusives and the games that run better on console. So that's the reason he didn't list the PC :| ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>20</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMGN</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMGN</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMgn</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 27-->
	<argument>
		<text>On the gaming website MGN, there was a "Who would win in a fight?" thread between two famous video game characters: the portly plumber from down under and the world's fastest porcupine. Being an aficionado of these discussions, you open up the thread to see a fairly even poll. Personally you think that the plumber has no chance. I mean he's a plumber! What does he even do? And the porcupine can run around at the speed of sound! The commenters in the discussion listing off feats from the games and how they give an advantage in the fight. However you have an ace in your sleeve that will tip the poll in your favor:</text>
		<choiceA>Mention that the world's fastest porcupine has a super form that makes him invincible</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Mention that the plumber has no super human feats that would give him an advantage</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The commenters state that there is no item in the plumber's arsenal that can counter the porcupine's super form. The poll tips in the favor of the porcupine. THE PORCUPINE AND THE ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>Other commenters mention that the plumber was able to throw a giant turtle into space. I don't know about you, but that's a pretty solid feat of strength. The poll tips in the favor of the portly plumber from down under. THE PORCUPINE AND THE ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>10</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMGN</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMGN</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMgn</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 28-->
	<argument>
		<text>On the gaming website MGN, there was an article about a robot piloting JRPG game from Japan getting heavily censored upon its localization to North America. Logically this makes sense because the main heroine was under 18 and had multiple risqué costumes that they are getting completely removed from the game. You don't really know why, but this really irks you! Probably because these costumes turn you on. One commenter mentioned that this censorship is a good thing because it's creepy to fantasize about digitally youthful women. How can anybody be against sexy costumes!? Is he even human? You decide to put this pleb in his place by informing him why his beliefs are wrong:</text>
		<choiceA>Mention that the risque costumes are a selling point of the game. If they remove them, it's less money for the company</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Mention that this removes content from the game, meaning US gamers get less content than Japanese gamers</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The commenters agree with you that it is not fair that Americans get less costumes. They discuss that it would be a good idea to at least replace the removed costumes with something else. The one commenter doesn't reply after that. Probably feels like a loser. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"Wait a minute. This is a robot piloting simulator. You only see the characters in costume in the HUB world. Why are these sexy costumes a selling point for you?" Now everyone thinks you are a pervert! DIGNITY LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>20</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMGN</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMGN</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMgn</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 32-->
	<argument>
		<text>On the gaming website MGN, you were perusing the forums of your favorite games. In one thread, the OP was asking for advice on how to beat one of the bosses in the game. You noticed that the OP's user name was a reference to a character in an anime. A female character. You deduce that OP is a girl gamer! You comment with the classic: "A girl gamer? I didn't know that girls played games... ;D" Unfortunately, your comment sends everyone to an uproar! "Guys like you are why everyone thinks gaming is a hobby for man children." You just wanted to meet a nice woman with similar hobbies, is that so bad? You need to defend yourself from these flames:</text>
		<choiceA>Be honest. Mention that you wanted to get to know a girl with similar hobbies as you</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Blame society for making it weird to hit on women through a digital medium</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>"...society has nothing to do with how creepy and inappropriate your comment was" The pleb doesn't even know how to give a good comeback. I guess that's why you are the one with the college degree. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>M'lady replies to you! But it's not a good reply. "This is not the place to do that though. You should try out OkNarcissus. You'll find somebody there." You've been signed up for OkNarcissus for 5 years though and found nobody :( ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMGN</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMGN</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMgn</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 33-->
	<argument>
		<text>On the gaming website MGN, you were browsing through the video game forums for an erotic Japanese visual novel. There was a poll for which girl was pursued romantically most in the game. To your horror, your waifu was only in second place: "You guys have terrible taste in women. My waifu should be in first place!" you commented as the thread spiralled into a heated debate. One commenter replies to you directly with a "Sorry, our tastes don't cover flat-chests and boring personalities like yours do." Your waifu does not have a boring personality! She loves gaming and is a shy kawaii-desu girl! She is completely different than the other girls in the game:</text>
		<choiceA>"My play through had more sex scenes then yours did and had a happier relationship overall"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"Breasts and personality aren't everything you perverts!"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The commenters start comparing how many sex scenes each branching path had and your waifu had the most! Last you looked, your waifu closed the gap between first place and second place in the poll! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"And that leaves your waifu with what again?" Damn, that was a good comeback. You can't think of another trait your waifu has! Last you looked, the gap between first and second place has gotten bigger in the poll. NO TROPHY FOR SECOND PLACE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>20</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMGN</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMGN</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMgn</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 44-->
	<argument>
		<text>On the gaming website MGN, you were looking through the forums for a popular competitive multiplayer game. Aiming  to improve your skills, you found threads saying your main character is bottom tier. Like hell your character is the worst; you beat all of your casual friends at this game! You open up a random thread and left the comment "Don't blame the character for your suckiness; blame yourself." One commented saying that "This character is supposed to be aggressive, but has useless moves. There are much better options." You feel like this is a personal attack, so you NEED to defend your character:</text>
		<choiceA>"I've placed in tournaments with this character, scrub."</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"Stop clinging to tier lists; they change."</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>Commenters have pointed out that the game still does get updated and tweaked, so the tiers are volatile. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>One commenter asked you "Who are you? I've played a lot tournament players too." You answered with a random name to which nobody believes you. YOU ARE A FRAUD-ARGUMENT LOST</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMGN</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMGN</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMgn</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 45-->
	<argument>
		<text>On the gaming website MGN, you wanted to voice your opinions on an indie game. Lately it's been getting a lot of press, but you think it's just "meh". You created a thread titled, "Most over-rated game of the year, am I right?" which spurred some negative press from the forum. While you did receive a lot of comments making fun of your bad taste, one commenter directly asked for your input: "Care to explain? This game's in the running for game of the year." Not one to leave a question unanswered you start typing up your reply:</text>
		<choiceA>Mention that the game just feels generic. And boring</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Mention that everyone is following the hype train like sheeple</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>Some like-minded commenters do agree with you that the gameplay is your standard slog, but the game does have some good narrative environments and well paced story-telling. Since you were able to get people to agree with you, it's an ARGUMENT INCREASE</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"So you don't like it because it's popular? It's gamers like you that are what's wrong with the gaming industry." Well... I mean... There's thousands of people like you around, right? ARGUMENT DECREASE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>25</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMGN</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMGN</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMgn</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 49-->
	<argument>
		<text>On the gaming website MGN, you saw a thread titled "Top 100 Video Games of All Time". You spent hours upon hours reading through the games and their descriptions to search for your personal favorite game of all time, only to find out that it didn't even make it to the honorable mentions! This filled you with despair; if your favorite game is not good enough for this list, are you not good enough? Feeling like you need to correct something in the world you decide to try to sneak in your favorite game into the "Top 100 Video Games of All Time" list:</text>
		<choiceA>Question why certain games are on there; there are some questionable choices on there</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Mention your favorite game and how it should be on the list</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The other commenters start to mention the games that they think don't deserve to be on the list. After counting the games they mentioned, you counted enough for the honorable mentions to make it into the list. After the honorable mentions, your favorite game should be next... WON THE ARGUMENT</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"I haven't played that game recently, but I don't remember much of it. Must not have been that good of a game if I can't remember it..." NOT GOOD ENOUGH</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>20</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgMGN</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrMGN</headerColor>
        <logo>logoMgn</logo>
	</argument>

	<!--Arg: LouTube-->
	<!--arg 7-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a "Top 10 Breasts in Anime" video to further study the subject matter that you consider yourself to be an expert in. However, the video fails to mention your waifu! Scientifically your waifu has smaller breasts than the other women on the list, but you feel that personality should have importance. In a list that ranks breasts. You leave a comment mentioning how they forgot your girl! One commenter replied that your waifu is a flat-chested high school girl and makes fun of your taste in women. Nobody makes fun of your waifu or your taste in the ladies! You start to type up a reply to defend your waifu's honor:</text>
		<choiceA>Ask where his waifu is on the list! The best way to destroy your enemy is through careful study</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Defend your position! Your girl and your will shall not waiver to this troll!</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The troll replies saying that you are way too obsessive over some anime character that's probably going to be forgotten in a year. What others call obsessive, you call dedicated. Besides it's better to be dedicated to an anime girl than it is to be dedicated to drugs. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>He mentions that his favorite character was number 1 on the list. The worst part of it all is that her breasts are actually much bigger than your waifu's breasts :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>10</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
        <logo>logoLoutube</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 12-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube raring to watch your favorite Let's Player. Their most recent upload is actually the start of a playthrough of one of your favorite games as a child! However after 5 minutes of the video, it is clear that they are having a bad time with the game. They constantly joke at the game's expense that it's hard to control, a buggy mess, and call the soundtrack obnoxious. It's been a while since you played the game, but the fact that the Let's Player is mocking your childhood really steams your veggies! You start warming up your typing fingers:</text>
		<choiceA>Blame their lack of enjoyment on their lack of skill. If he was any better at the game, he would be having fun</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Call your childhood game a national treasure and that they don't know what they're talking about</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>Other viewers of the video do mention the number of shortcuts and items that they are missing. They all start to make fun of the Let's Player's skills rather than focusing on the flawed game. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>The commenters tell you to clean off you nostalgia goggles. When it's your turn to reply to it, nothing comes to your head. Maybe the game actually isn't as good as you remembered :| ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>10</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
        <logo>logoLoutube</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 15-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were binge watching anime AMVs on the video-sharing website LouTube. After a while, an AMV for your favorite anime started to play, but to your horror it was an AMV for a ship that you detest. The video paired your waifu with a supporting character rather than the main character. You support MC x waifu because you project yourself on to the main character. You pause the video and state your opinion; "This ship is garbage." The creator of the video replied to your comment with "You are garbage. Don't make fun of my video you creep." This really shoots your scooter! Nobody calls you a creep in public domain. You scheme your retort:</text>
		<choiceA>"This ship is garbage, this AMV is garbage, and so are you! Please delete this video so we can move on with our lives."</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Mention that your waifu has more screen time alone with the main character than the supporting character</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>Other viewers of the video do mention that the creator's preferred ship is less likely than yours! Everybody is on your side and everyone loves you! ++ARGUMENT</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>The creator has not replied to you. Other viewers of the video mention that the only one who's worked up about the offensiveness of this ship is you. --ARGUMENT</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
        <logo>logoLoutube</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 19-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a "Worst 5 Games of the Year" video. Agreeing with the hoard of poorly made indie games on Vapor that made it to the list, your heart instantly got hit with despair as you saw one of your favorite games of the year made it to the list. The narrator of the list said that the game was buggy, poorly designed, and offensive to the ears with bad voice acting. Personally you enjoyed the game because it's a game in a series you grew up with. You feel the need to defend the game... you can feel it in your spleen:</text>
		<choiceA>Say that there are worse games that came out this year that that should be on the list in its place</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Attack the list maker's sense of taste. Just because they had a bad time with the game doesn't mean others did too</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The commenters all start listing off bad games that should also be on the list. You pat your own shoulder as your work here is done. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>People agree with the narrator of the video: the game simply is not that great. They start asking where your sense of taste is and it really hurts your feelings :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
        <logo>logoLoutube</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 23-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a social-experiment video where a muscle-bound pranker goes around asking women for sexual intercourse. Surprisingly, the pranker gets a few numbers from this. This rustles your jimmies because you tried this just last week and you got slapped, the cops called on you, and got zero numbers. You decide to voice your own opinion: "If they got a soft-hearted beta male to do this, the outcome would be different!" To your surprise, this comment was hit with many dislikes! One commented "Poor baby! Who hurt you?" You are not a baby! A baby does not have a high IQ like you:</text>
		<choiceA>Mention your superior intellect and call the commenter a moron who knows nothing about psychology and philosophy!</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Use psychological science! For the coup de grace, link to a legitimate article you found on the internet</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>You link to an article called "Why Nice Guys Finish Last" and people comment on how it's a satire article. You know for a fact that it's a legitimate source of information because you saw this link on your MyFace news feed. These guys don't know what they are talking about, further cementing your intellectual lead! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>After you compared the difference between your intelligence, other commenters start to attack your child-like behavior and overall bitterness towards the world. ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>30</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
        <logo>logoLoutube</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 25-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a tribute video to a popular celebrity who recently died. You were about to leave your regards to one of your favorite celebrities, but one comment caught your eye: "What kind of cruel God would take him away from us?!" Your atheism got the better of you and you replied to the comment with "A God that doesn't exist" Tipping your fedora, you imagined yourself as a bad ass for leaving that comment. However people start calling you an insensitive prick for mocking the death of a celebrity:</text>
		<choiceA>Explain that your intentions were misinterpreted; you meant to leave your condolences to the celebrity</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Use science and logical thought to temper your argument that God does not exist</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The commenters mention that it's hard to interpret your comment as anything else, but hey, at least they are not yelling at you! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>They continue to call you a prick because they think this video is not a good forum for discussing beliefs. The fools don't know that it's always a good time to discuss atheism! ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>15</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
        <logo>logoLoutube</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 29-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching video created by a popular female cosplayer. Reading through the comments, one caught your eye saying "So beautiful!" This comment doesn't really bother you, but you really wanted the attention of m'lady. So you had a plan of defending her honor so she could see it and inevitably fall in love! You replied to the commenter, "Beautiful as in physically attractive? How typical of lesser men such as yourself. When I think of beauty, I think of a women's passion and their dreams." You wait for m'lady to respond, but the only responses were from bullies calling you a try-hard. Defend your honor from these louts:</text>
		<choiceA>"I'm just stating how I feel. I miss the days when beauty was the whole package"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Make an underscore line and underneath it, type in "Everybody above this line is a loser!"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>While your plan to win over the heart and body of the female cosplayer failed, but your comment has a total of two likes! Overall success! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>The original commenter removed the entire conversation from the video. Nooooooo! M'lady will never love you now :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>20</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
        <logo>logoLoutube</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 36-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching viral video where people prank gold diggers. Most of the comments were poking fun at the women getting pranked, but something within this video really boiled your brownies! This video solidifies why you're not in the dating scene; money means everything! You left a comment on the video, "This is why 2D girls > 3D girls. 2D girls are loyal and don't care about how much you make!" This raised some questions from some commenters "...so you're admitting to whacking it to pixels then?" Beep yeah you do! Why should you take shame in that fact? You decide to explain to this pleb the infinite pros of pixelated women:</text>
		<choiceA>Mention when one watches "3D" porn, the video is rendered as a 2D image so they enjoy pixels too!</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Mention that it is a fetish. People like feet, other people like getting stepped on. You like pixels</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The commenter replied with a "Yeah, I guess that's correct, but it still weirds me out." The pleb agrees with you! ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>The commenter replied with a "The output is 2D, but there are no pixels involved with real women. Don't try to lump me in with you." Ouch! It was turned around back at you :( ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>20</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
        <logo>logoLoutube</logo>
	</argument>

	<!--arg 37-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching the best scenes of your favorite cartoon show "Ponies in High School". Laughing so hard your neighbors probably think you're a lunatic, you scroll through the comments section. One comment caught your eye; "Bronies are freaks!" Whoa whoa whoa... "Ponies in High School" is more than just a show about ponies, it's a way of life. It's smart wit and good characterization often gets misinterpreted due to the colorful exterior. You decide to educate this man about something he probably doesn't care too much about:</text>
		<choiceA>Mention that the show does have a lot of intelligent humor for people of all ages</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Summon your bronies to smite this man where he stands!</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The sad man replied with a pathetic "Whatever, loser. Have fun with your cartoon for children." It's a shame that his intellect wasn't up to snuff to enjoy the show. ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>None of your fellow bronies answered the call to come and aid you. You stand alone in your shame. ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>20</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
        <logo>logoLoutube</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 41-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching a top 10 list video for "Anime That Needs to Die". Agreeing with the garbage anime on the list so far, you lost control of your tear glands when you saw your favorite anime at number two. Wiping away the tears, you show the list maker a piece of your mind: "Number 2 shouldn't be on there! It's a bloody classic you Neanderthals!" Your response garnered some disagreeing comments. One stated "It was a great series in the beginning, but it devolved quickly after the lead writer left." What does that even mean? He should be more constructive with his feedback:</text>
		<choiceA>"The anime has evolved as a series. More sub plots, more characterization, and more fan service."</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"Care to elaborate more with your critique of the anime? Nothing worse than a critic who doesn't know anything."</choiceB>
		<answer>ansA</answer>
		<responseCorrect>"Not really... The anime is garbage because of those reasons you listed." Thinking long and hard about how to reply, you come up with a cool "Well that's like, your opinion, man." The commenter never replies back and you take this as an ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"Sure thing. After the first arc, the series devolved into a harem anime. All characterization goes out the window, endless filler episodes, bad animation ..." The commenter continues on and on listing off negative traits about the anime. Maybe the anime hasn't aged as well as you thought... ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>20</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
        <logo>logoLoutube</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 42-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube going from video to video like a digital flu. Eventually you stumbled onto a music video of a female rapper who was singing about women with big butts. While the video did arouse you, the music hurt your ears. You left your opinion on the video with a "This sounds like garbage!" A few moments later, somebody with a lower intelligence replied to your comment. "Why are you even here then if you don't even like the music?" This poster is missing the big picture. Ignoring the commenter's question you start typing up a reply with one hand:</text>
		<choiceA>Mention that the people who enjoy this musician have a low IQ</choiceA>
        <choiceB>Say that this musician writes music with no substance</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>The commenters complain that the musician writes annoying music now and how she used to write music with more heart before she became popular. Since people agree with you, this is an ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>Another commenter replies saying that you probably clicked on the video because of the provocative thumb nail. You are quick to defend yourself, but the damage was already done. Everyone thinks you're a pervert now. DIGNITY LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>20</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
        <logo>logoLoutube</logo>
	</argument>
	
	<!--arg 50-->
	<argument>
		<text>You were on the video-sharing website LouTube watching the world championship for a MOBA game. During one of the quiet parts of the bout, you skimmed through the comments and spotted a maiden who needs a white knight! Her comment read "My boyfriend pays more attention to this game than he pays attention to me :( lol" A man is not treating a woman the way she needs to be treated?! You decide to save her; "Fear not m'lady! You boyfriend is a simpleton who does not know what he is missing out on. If I was your boyfriend, I would pamper you with attention." You wait for a few hours, but she still has not replied:</text>
		<choiceA>"No response? Have fun with your emotionally distant simpleton of a boyfriend"</choiceA>
        <choiceB>"So... want to grab coffee some time?"</choiceB>
		<answer>ansB</answer>
		<responseCorrect>"Lol no." M'lady may have provided a short response, but you made her lol. It's a step in the right direction so it's an ARGUMENT WIN!</responseCorrect>
		<responseWrong>"Don't call my boyfriend a simpleton, freak." Ouch. You pulled out the "Higher IQ card" way too soon. REJECTED ON THE INTERNET ARGUMENT LOSE</responseWrong>
		<accomplish>30</accomplish>
        <backgroundColor>bkgLouTube</backgroundColor>
        <headerColor>hdrLouTube</headerColor>
        <logo>logoLoutube</logo>
	</argument>
</doc>