<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<doc>
	<events>
		<!--Quest 1 - Grocery Shopping-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Can you please go to the store and pick up some groceries? I left some money for you to use and the shopping list on the counter."</text>
			<complete>Getting back home, you put the groceries away and let your mother know of your success. She told you to keep the leftover money.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will satisfy her needs. You pocket the money and head outside.</response>
					<effect>moneyUpL</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy climbing the ladder in a MOBA game go grocery shopping for her.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>You notice that with all this money, you have the option to take the bus. The nearest grocery isn't too far, but options are always good!</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Walk to the store</text>
					<response>Deciding to walk to the store, you burned a few calories.</response>
					<effect>workOut</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Take the bus</text>
					<response>Spending $10 for the fare, you sat in comfort on the bus to the store.</response>
					<effect>transport</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After gathering everything on the shopping list, you realize you have some money left over. You see some magazines about games, PUAs, and anime in the magazine isle...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Buy all the things!</text>
					<response>You place some of the most interesting magazines in your basket.</response>
					<effect>buyMags</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Restrain yourself</text>
					<response>Not caving in to your desires, you decide to walk away from the magazine isle.</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Making your way to the checkout line, you decide to make conversation with the cute cashier...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Compliment her jewelry</text>
					<response>Taking note of the cashier's accessories, you complimented her style as the two of you talked about that while she was checking out your items.</response>
					<effect>compliment</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Talk about the weather</text>
					<response>"Crazy weather, huh?" The conversation died as silence fell upon the two of you. Nice try though!</response>
					<effect>socialUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>You noticed that the bagger was putting the groceries in plastic bags. Normally this would be fine, but having ONE BIG PAPER BAG would be much more convenient for you.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Stay silent and deal with the plastic bags later</text>
					<response>Not wanting to inconvenience the bagger you stayed silent. Now you have to deal with a lot of plastic bags on the way home!</response>
					<effect>plasticBag</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Ask the bagger to re-bag the items</text>
					<response>You stopped the bagger mid-bag and asked them for a plastic bag. While you did feel embarrassed, at least you made it easier for yourself!</response>
					<effect>paperBag</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>WIth your groceries bagged and acquired, on your way out you noticed someone asking for money outside of the store...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Ignore the pan handler</text>
					<response>You looked at your phone trying to seem busy as you walked past the pan handler. You feel the judging stares of everyone around you, but at least you didn't spend your money.</response>
					<effect>paranoid</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Donate some money</text>
					<response>After donating $20, you stopped and talked with the beggar. They had a family to feed, and you're glad that you were able to help someone in need.</response>
					<effect>donate</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 2 - Chores Around The House-->
		<quest>
			<text>"I couldn't do the daily household chores before I left for work today. Could you please finish them before I get back home?"</text>
			<complete>Completing all of the household chores asked of your mother, you looked upon your hard work with pride! You texted her saying you have completed the chores.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will accomplish everything she requires of you.</response>
					<effect>excitementUpL</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy level grinding in a 20 year old JRPG for an ultimate weapon.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Remembering that your mother's plants needed to be watered every morning, you fill up a spray bottle and start spraying away! You saw a lone bee fly out of the plant.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Swat at the bee</text>
					<response>Pulling out a fly swatter, you were able to sack that sucker! Feeling proud of yourself, you feel like you have vanquished a foe! Like in your anime.</response>
					<effect>swatAway</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Lead it outside</text>
					<response>Taking the passive route, you lead the bee outside.</response>
					<effect>leadOut</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Noticing that the sink was full of dishes, you figured that the kitchen sink was the next stop.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Load up the dishwasher and try to figure it out</text>
					<response>You place the dishes into the machine and fiddle around with the control panel until it started to rumble. Great success!</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Wash the dishes manually</text>
					<response>There's something relaxing about washing dishes. It may have taken longer, but you feel oddly content after emptying the sink from dirty dishes.</response>
					<effect>excitementUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>While you were in the kitchen, you noticed that the stove and counter tops could use some cleaning, but you couldn't find the cleaning supplies.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Check under the sink</text>
					<response>Looking under the sink, you found out that it was not there. You spent a long time searching for the cleaning supplies, only to find them in the laundry room.</response>
					<effect>searchClean</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Check in the laundry room</text>
					<response>Making your way to the laundry room, you found some cloth and some cleaning chemicals. It was the first place you looked! Go you!</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After finishing up in the kitchen, you noticed that the garbage was overflowing. You brought the garbage outside and ran into the neighbor walking their dog.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Play with their dog</text>
					<response>You knelt down and pet the dog. You then look up at the owner and start talking them questions about the dog. After a few minutes of talking, they continued on with their walk.</response>
					<effect>petDog</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Talk about upcoming events</text>
					<response>"So uh... there are some events going on in town, yeah?" Your neighbor was stunned at first but was a good sport making small talk with you.</response>
					<effect>socialUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>While outside, you noticed that the lawn hasn't been trimmed in a while. You go to the shed and saw two different lawn-mowers. You remembered that the ridable lawn mower had trouble starting up.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Use the push-blade mower</text>
					<response>You pull out the push-blade mower and decided to mow the lawn manually. It was exhausting, but you feel like you got a good workout from this.</response>
					<effect>workOut</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Figure out how to work the ridable lawn mower</text>
					<response>Spending a good 10 minutes trying to get the lawn mower running, you finally got a response from the engine! You had fun while mowing the lawn because it was like driving a car.</response>
					<effect>ridable</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 3 - Returning Library Books-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Hey, I have some overdue library books that I haven't been able to return. Can you please return it to the library for me? I left $20 just in case the books are overdue."</text>
			<complete>Making your way back home from the library, you texted your mother saying you have accomplished the task! She told you to pocket the money left over.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will make the library your new kingdom.</response>
					<effect>excitementUpL</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy proving your intellectual superiority on plebs on the internet.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>The library is within walking distance, but you see your folded up scooter in the corner of your room. It has been a while since you used that bad boy...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Scoot scoot!</text>
					<response>Unfolding your scooter, you rode that baby all around doing stunts and having a great time!</response>
					<effect>scootAround</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Walk in the heat</text>
					<response>Walking around in the heat proved to be a good training session! You felt like you really burned your buns.</response>
					<effect>workOut</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Making it to the library with the books in hand, you bring them to the front desk. The librarian seems to be new and asks how long ago you borrowed these books.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Guess the check out date</text>
					<response>Guessing the check out date, the librarian told you that there were late fees totalling up to $5.</response>
					<effect>lateFees</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Say that you don't know the date</text>
					<response>Being honest, you affirmed that you were doing this for your mother and had no idea. The new librarian gave you a pass and you got away with not paying any late fees. However, you felt like you got away with a crime...</response>
					<effect>paranoid</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Deciding that while you were at the library, why not enjoy your time there? Walking further into the building, you passed a vending machine with some really tasty snacks.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Ignore the tasty treats</text>
					<response>You ignored the vending machine and felt good about choosing the healthier option.</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Indulge yourself in snacks</text>
					<response>You spent $5 on a bunch of vending machine snacks.</response>
					<effect>buySnack</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Now in the center of the library, you decide to take a book and read it on a comfortable chair. Which type of book do you feel like reading?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>A book about self improvement</text>
					<response>Feeling the need to improve your life, you grab a self improvement book that teaches readers how to become more social. Once you completed the book, you put the book back where you found it.</response>
					<effect>socialUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Some vintage comic books</text>
					<response>You decided to read up on some old school comics, reading the original origins of some of your favorite heroes. Once you finished a handful of stories, you put the comics back where you found them.</response>
					<effect>vintageComics</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>You noticed that there was a board game room in the library. Noticing another person your age, you decide to talk to them and was challenged to a chess match! How do you play?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Play defensive</text>
					<response>After a very close match, you were able to sneak a victory! Feeling good about yourself, your opponent congratulated you for your victory.</response>
					<effect>chessWin</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Play offensive</text>
					<response>After a very close match, you ended up losing. Speaking with your opponent after the game, they ended up giving you some tips for the next time you two play against each other.</response>
					<effect>chessLose</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>

		<!--Quest 4 - Gift Giving-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Tomorrow is your uncle's birthday and I ordered a gift for him in the mall. Would you be able to go to the store in the mall and pick it up? I left some money on the dining table."</text>
			<complete>After a fun-filled day of malling around, you texted your mother saying you have accomplished the task! She told you to pocket the money left over.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will make her happy. OR DIE TRYING! You pocket the money and walk to the mall.</response>
					<effect>moneyUpL</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy grooming and tending to your ponies to do such a menial task.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Making your way to the gift shop, you asked if they had the order for your mother. The cashier went to the back of the store to search. What do you do to entertain yourself?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Spin the globe around</text>
					<response>Spinning the globe, you stopped it with your finger and said that you would rule that country first. You continued to do this for a while...</response>
					<effect>spinGlobe</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Look at stock photos in picture frames</text>
					<response>Looking at the stock photos in the picture frame, you started to get introspective about life... thinking about the past, present, and the future...</response>
					<effect>photoLook</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>When the cashier comes back from the storage room, you pay for the gift then head out. Now that you've accomplished what you set out to do, you decide to spend some more time at the mall. What do you want to do?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Go to the arcade</text>
					<response>Deciding to go to the arcade, you played a handful of arcade games even bonding with other arcade patrons in the co-op games.</response>
					<effect>arcadePlay</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Go to the katana store</text>
					<response>Deciding to go to the katana store, you look in awe at the immaculate craftsmanship of the mall blades almost being brought to tears.</response>
					<effect>katanaShop</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Having more time to kill, you stopped by a popular clothing store specializing in gothic clothing and trendy knick knacks. Looking at Ponies in High School T-shirts, an employee starts talking to you about the show.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Tell her that you're a huge Brony</text>
					<response>She laughed and told you that she's a fan too. The two of you talked about the show some more before she had to help someone else.</response>
					<effect>confidentBoost</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her that you're shopping for your... neice</text>
					<response>The employee gave you some shopping advice for Ponies in High School. Honestly, it's not bad advice, but you know everything about the show already. She then had to leave to hep another customer.</response>
					<effect>lieBrony</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After some window shopping you decide to make your way to the food court. Being overwhelmed by all of the food choices, you narrow it down between a coffee shop and a burger place. Which one do you want to go for?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Coffee shop</text>
					<response>You grabbed a coffee and grabbed a seat at the coffee shop. You enjoyed the taste of the coffee upon your lips and people watched for a bit. Somebody brought their desktop and their guitar... weird...</response>
					<effect>coffeeShop</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Burger place</text>
					<response>You ordered a massive speciality burger and devoured it in less than 2 minutes. That was impressive if not a bit scary!</response>
					<effect>burgerPlace</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Deciding that your time at the mall has to end, you head outside. However with you elven eyes, you saw a group of teenagers smoking a cigarette in the distance. However you may be able to change their ways...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Intervene and give them a life lesson</text>
					<response>Not standing by for this, you walk over to the group and gave an anti-drug PSA. Confused at your presence, they asked you to go away. Feeling like you made a fool of yourself, you saw the silver linings - maybe you convinced just one of them to quit smoking.</response>
					<effect>dontDoDrugs</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Let them walk down the dark path that they are heading towards</text>
					<response>Turning the other way, you ignore these troubled youths. Your imagination went wild - what if they started doing harder drugs? You could have saved a life. If only you weren't socially awkward!</response>
					<effect>doDrugs</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 5 - Mail Package-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Hey, I am unable to mail some letters out throughout the day due to work. Would you be able to stop by the post office for me? I left the letters and some pocket money on the table for you."</text>
			<complete>Making your way back home from the strip mall, you texted your mother saying you have accomplished the task! She told you to pocket the money left over.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will mail the package out SO HARD.</response>
					<effect>moneyUpM</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy feasting upon some tendies and potato chips to help her with her task.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Walking to post office with letters in hand, you suddenly realize that you need to prepare the letters. Mailing letters is one of the many things you're not experienced with but you do know stamps are involved...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Ask the person behind the counter for assistance</text>
					<response>You gave all of the letters to the person behind the counter. They were able to do all the work for you even recommending the cheapest stamps that you needed. Stress free!</response>
					<effect>askForHelp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Pick up some entertaining stamps and do it yourself</text>
					<response>Your eyes were drawn to these colorful stamps from a beloved cartoon show. They were a bit pricy, but at least your letters looked good! You put two stamps on each letter and threw them in the outgoing box.</response>
					<effect>buyStamps</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Deciding that while you were out and about, why not enjoy the fresh air? After all, the comic book store that you work at is in the same strip mall. Stopping by, you see that the store got a handful of new items in stock...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Buy an action figure</text>
					<response>You spent $25 on a cool looking action figure to decorate your room with.</response>
					<effect>buyFig</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Buy a handful of new comic books</text>
					<response>You spent $10 on a handful of newly released comic books.</response>
					<effect>buyBooks</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After making a purchase, a customer thought you were working and asks you for some comic book suggestions. What do you do?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Tell the customer you are not working</text>
					<response>You awkwardly dismissed the customer's request saying that you were not working. However that gave you some extra time to look at all the cool nerd memorabilia your store has!</response>
					<effect>excitementUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Give the customer a list of suggestions</text>
					<response>Choosing to help this customer out, you gave a list of modern comics that focused on one character and gave a list of comic book characters to avoid. It turned out you helped this customer out for an hour and it counted as an hour of work!</response>
					<effect>workDo</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After dealing with the customer, you decided to hang out in the employee's only room. Checking in the fridge, you see that there's an unopened energy drink...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Leave the energy drink as is</text>
					<response>Thinking that it was another person's drink, you would've felt bad if you took it for yourself. So you closed the fridge and never looked back.</response>
					<effect>ngpUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Take it! Why not?</text>
					<response>You grabbed the can and downed it in one big gulp. You'd feel terrible if you weren't having caffeine twitches!</response>
					<effect>takeDrink</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Leaving the comic book store you hear a cheap sounding music jingle nearby. You realize there's an ice cream truck driving by! Should you indulge your desire for sugar?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Signal for the ice cream truck</text>
					<response>Signalling for the ice cream truck, you bought a popsicle the shape of your favorite pony from your favorite cartoon "Ponies in High School" with gumballs for eyes. You felt guilty, but she tastes so good!</response>
					<effect>iceCream</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Ignore the ice cream truck</text>
					<response>Despite wanting a popsicle the shape of your favorite pony from your favorite cartoon "Ponies in High School" with gumballs for eyes, you were able to resist the temptation. Feels good to have control over yourself like that!</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 6 - Oil Change-->
		<quest>
			<text>"I need to get the oil changed for the car, but I'm stuck at work. Can you please take the car to the mechanic and take care of that for me? I left the keys and some money on the counter."</text>
			<complete>Making your way back home after a few hours of driving a car, you texted your mother saying you have accomplished the task! She told you to pocket the money left over.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will change her oil. You grab the keys and the money and head to the garage.</response>
					<effect>moneyUpL</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy combing your pony figurines to help her out.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>You hardly ever drive due to your lack of money, so you always cherish every time your mom lets you drive. Backing out of the driveway you realize that you can go to the mechanic one of two ways... the scenic route or the more direct route.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Go the scenic route</text>
					<response>Diving the scenic route, puts your mind at ease.</response>
					<effect>relaxed</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Go the direct route</text>
					<response>Driving for the mechanic, you had to deal with the traffic. Luckily for you, you have a samurai's patience and was able to keep a steady mind like a true warrior.</response>
					<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Dropping the car off at the mechanic's, they took the car to the garage and came back to ring you up. The mechanic suggests that you change your windshield wipers...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Pay for the windshield wipers replacement</text>
					<response>Your total for the wipers and the oil change rang up to $30. Helping your mother out with her wipers brought you a sense of accomplishment and niceness.</response>
					<effect>buyWiper</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Don't change the windshield wipers and keep the money</text>
					<response>Your total for the oil change came out to be $15. Since you didn't buy the wipers, you saved $15 all to yourself!</response>
					<effect>buyOil</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Now that you finished paying, you need to waiting for the services to be complete. Coming prepared, you brought your designated handheld device. However, you also got a text from your equally euphoric friend...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Play video games</text>
					<response>You put away your phone and started playing with the handheld you brought with you.</response>
					<effect>excitementUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Text your friend</text>
					<response>You texted back and forth with your friend for a bit while the service was being done to the car.</response>
					<effect>socialUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After getting service done to your mother's car, you decide to make a quick stop at a donut shop. Feeling like consuming one of two things, you can choose to buy a cup of donuts or a cup of coffee.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Buy some donuts</text>
					<response>Chowing down on donut balls never felt so good! Once you completed your donut eating task, you stepped outside.</response>
					<effect>buyDonuts</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Buy some coffee</text>
					<response>Drinking some coffee never felt so good! Once you completed your coffee drinking task, you stepped outside.</response>
					<effect>buyCoffee</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After you left the donut shop, you saw somebody you used to go to high school with. He was a chad on the football team, but you can see he's gained some weight.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Talk to him</text>
					<response>Thinking you had one up on him, you talked with him for a bit. The chad was getting married! Freaking chad got one over on you again!</response>
					<effect>chadTalk</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Ignore him</text>
					<response>Freaking chads... at least you got one up on him! He's fat now!</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 7 - Prepare House Guests-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Howdy, I'm having house guests over later today for the book club. Could you please prepare some accommodations for our guests in the living room before I get home?"</text>
			<complete>Looking at the living room, you pat yourself on the back for a job well done! This may just be your finest work yet.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will clean the living room so hard until it becomes the dead room.</response>
					<effect>excitementUpL</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy writing your erotic fan fiction series based on an anime from the 1990's.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Starting off, you would like to clean up the living room. After mopping the floors and cleaning the tables, you need to mask the chemical smell with some nice smelling chemicals. You can choose between the two flavors of chemicals - Spring Night Breeze or Beaches and Shores?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Spring Night Breeze</text>
					<response>Taking a wiff of the Spring Night Breeze you just sprayed reminded you of your youth and how you'd spend your spring breaks immersed in anime, gaming, and sleeping...</response>
					<effect>relaxed</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Beaches and Shores</text>
					<response>Taking a wiff of the Beaches and Shores you just sprayed reminded you of your youth and your summers spent at anime conventions...</response>
					<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After getting the place cleaned up, you noticed that there was a massive pile of unread mail on the dining table... how do you handle this pile?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Sort through the mail</text>
					<response>While sorting through the mail, you found a video game that you preordered a while ago. You forgot about ordering this!</response>
					<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Throw it on your mom's bed</text>
					<response>There's no time to deal with mail! You grabbed the mountain of mail, piled them up, then placed it on your mom's bed neatly.</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Thinking about what else needs to be done, you figure that guests need food and drinks. Focusing on food first, your mother baked a pie for the meeing. However, you love your mother's pies! You can swap out the pie with another snack and keep it for yourself...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Put some cookies out on a plate and keep the pie to yourself</text>
					<response>You brought out some cookies for snacks then stealthfully snuck the fresh pie into your room for consumption! Being bad never felt so good.</response>
					<effect>hungerUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Put the pie on the coffee table with knives and forks</text>
					<response>With tears in your eyes, you figure that it's for the best you use the pie for its intended purpose. You set up the pie in the living room and never looked back... until you had to go into the living room again.</response>
					<effect>givePie</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Now to make some actual food! Actually you can't cook to save your life, but you can microwave! You can let loose your inner chef and microwave some chips or just set up a box of taquitos...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Microwave some nacho chips</text>
					<response>Feeling like a gourmet cook, you created a bowl of nachos and placed the out in the living room for the guests.</response>
					<effect>makeNachos</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Microwave some taquitos</text>
					<response>You microwaved some taquitos and placed them out in the living room for the guests.</response>
					<effect>makeTaquitos</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Now focusing on beverages, you looked in the fridge. Admittedly mother dropped the ball and hasn't gone for groceries so all you have in terms of drinks are water and your euphoric Fountain Dew. You can sacrifice your own Fountain Dew or make the guests drink water...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Sacrifice the dew</text>
					<response>With great sadness, you sacrificed the dew. But with great sacrifice comes great retribution...</response>
					<effect>sacDew</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Keep the dew to yourself</text>
					<response>Not wanting to part ways with the dew, you brought out some water for the guests.</response>
					<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 8 - Pick up Food-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Hello there, I'll be up at work until late. Can you please get dinner from the Italian restaurant down the street? I left some money on the counter for you to use."</text>
			<complete>When you got home, you texted your mother saying you left your mother's food on the counter. She thanked you and told you to keep the leftover money.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will pick up the food like you pick up the ladies.</response>
					<effect>moneyUpM</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy trying to improve your luck with the ladies by playing dating simulators to be able to help her.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>The Italian restaurant is down the street, but it's a few blocks away. Not feeling like walking there, you look for your bike... however walking there would be a good training routine.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Bike to the restaurant</text>
					<response>After finding your bike, you got to the Italian restaurant in no time. It was fun going fast!</response>
					<effect>excitementUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Walk to the restaurant</text>
					<response>Deciding to walk to the restaurant, you were left admittedly winded at the door. But you know what they say: no pain, no gain!</response>
					<effect>workOut</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After arriving at the restaurant, you placed an order for your mother and some chicken tenders for yourself. You saw on display some packaged cannoli's - your mother's favorite snack.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Buy your mother a cannoli</text>
					<response>Deciding to do something nice for the woman who spawned you, you picked up a cannoli for $5.</response>
					<effect>buyCannoli</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Don't buy her one</text>
					<response>Feeling frugal, you decide to not purchase the cannoli. It's just empty calories anyway.</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>The waiter came back and asked if you'd like to upgrade your order to super chicken tenders.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Upgrade those tenders to become super tenders!</text>
					<response>Not wanting to miss an opportunity to try new tenders, you placed the order! You can't wait to have it in and or around your mouth!</response>
					<effect>upTenders</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Reject the super tenders</text>
					<response>Not wanting to risk money on something you may or may not like, you replied with no. But now, you may never know what makes those tenders super...</response>
					<effect>rejectTenders</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After ordering the food, you need to wait for the food to get prepared. You pull out your phone and are faced with a dilemma: you are in the mood to view memes, but there's this new popular mobile game that came out recently too...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>View those dank memes</text>
					<response>You decide to look at some memes on the front page of the Creddit app. You are impressed with some of the memes and jokes these guys create!</response>
					<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Play the new mobile game</text>
					<response>You decide to play the new game. It's really well made, and you can see yourself playing this game  again in the future.</response>
					<effect>excitementUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After a few minutes of goofing off on your phone, the staff comes out with your food and the bill. In total, the bill was $12 meaning the tip should be around $3. You can also round up to a total of $20 just for convenience.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Tip the waiter $8</text>
					<response>Rounding up to a $5, your total for the food order comes up to $20. You took the paper bag of food and headed back home.</response>
					<effect>payHigh</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tip the waiter $3</text>
					<response>Wanting to keep some money for yourself, the total for the food order comes up to $15. You took the paper bag of food and headed back home.</response>
					<effect>payLow</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 9 - Walk Neighbor's Dog-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Hola mi hijo. I promised to help take care of the neighbor's dog for the day but I got called in to work. Could you please take care of it?"</text>
			<complete>After your fun-filled day of playing with the pup, you put the dog back in its cage and said your good byes.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will clean the living room so hard until it becomes the dead room.</response>
					<effect>excitementUpL</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy trying to find true, fetishized, oriental love on OkNarcissus to be able to help her.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Starting off, you took the tiny puppy out of its cage and looked around at what was left near it - there's some toys left near the cage, but it's so soft and fluffy!</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Play with its toys</text>
					<response>You took a squeaky chicken toy and a rope and watched as the dog went to town on them. To be that tiny and innocent...</response>
					<effect>excitementUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Pet the hell out of it</text>
					<response>You picked up the puppy and sat it on your lap. Petting the soft energetic puppy relaxed you...</response>
					<effect>relaxed</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>You noticed its bowl was empty, so you poured some food into it. However, when you stopped to put the food away, the dog started whimpering for more food.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Give it more food</text>
					<response>Giving into the dog's pleas, you poured some more food. You just couldn't say no, and it looks so happy!</response>
					<effect>excitementUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Put the bag of food away</text>
					<response>Saying no to the dog was one of the hardest things you had to do... but at least you have the power to say no to it.</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After feeding the puppy, you put on its walking harness and went to the park. There, a cute girl started to talk to you - thinking this was a good way to pick up chicks, do you fake it as your own dog?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Fake it until you make it</text>
					<response>Faking this dog as your own, you told her fake stories that you and the dog had together. She seemed to believe the stories, and you had fun getting her to laugh.</response>
					<effect>dogLie</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her it's the neighbor's dog</text>
					<response>You told her that you were watching your neighbor's dog for the day, but she thought it was cool. The two of you talked for a while.</response>
					<effect>tellTruth</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After your talk with the nice girl, you continued your walk around the park. You found a nice bench to sit on and decided to use this time to play with the dog.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>See if you could get it to sit</text>
					<response>At first, you had trouble getting it to sit... but after some hard work and dedication you were able to get it to follow your command!</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Play fetch</text>
					<response>You had a blast playing fetch, and you got a nice little workout running around with the energetic ball of fur.</response>
					<effect>playFetch</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Feeling tired after playing with the dog, you see that there was a food truck in the distance. You bought yourself a snack, but the dog looks at you expecting a bite...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Give it a bite of your food</text>
					<response>Caving in to the puppy dog eyes, you gave the puppy a bite. Admittedly, you're not entirely sure if it was good for the dog, but you made the puppy happy!</response>
					<effect>feedDog</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Don't give in to the puppy dog eyes!</text>
					<response>Not sure if the food was good for the puppy, you resisted those hypnotizing eyes!</response>
					<effect>dontFeed</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 10 - Laundry Work-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Arigato! I didn't have the chance to do the laundry over the weekend. Could you please take care of the laundry while I'm at work? If you don't we'll be running low on clothes."</text>
			<complete>After your clothes were taken care of, you texted your mother that you have completed the quest!</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying you'll make sure the Laundry Complete achievement has been unlocked by the time she arrives.</response>
					<effect>excitementUpL</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy stalking some girl you had a crush on in high school on MyFace.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Thinking about how to start off the laundry, you spent some time sorting the clothes into categories. Your first batch of laundry was full of jeans and towels, but you are unsure of if you should use fabric softener with these types of clothing...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Throw caution to the wind!</text>
					<response>Wanting to live dangerously, you decide to throw fabric softener in there. You feel good about being so confident about something!</response>
					<effect>confident</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Research when to use fabric softener</text>
					<response>After a few minutes of researching fabric softener, you found out not only do you need to use fabric softener for this batch of laundry, but you now know more about the history of fabric softener. Maybe you can use this information in future conversations...</response>
					<effect>researchStuff</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Once the first batch of laundry was complete, you open up the dryer to see that there were some clothes left in there from the last time you did laundry. All of the clothes left in were wrinkled.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Iron them out and place it on your mom's bed</text>
					<response>While ironing your mother's clothes, you actually hit a moment of zen with quick bursts of adrenaline when you would spray water on for steam. Once done, you folded the clothes up and placed it neatly on your mother's bed.</response>
					<effect>ironClothes</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Throw it in to a pile on to the couch</text>
					<response>Not wanting to deal with this old batch of clothing right now, you just throw it in a pile on the couch in the living room so you can work on it later.</response>
					<effect>leavePile</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>With the dryer cleared and cleaned, you threw the wet clothes in and set it to run for an hour. While waiting for the dryer, you think of ways to entertain yourself...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Microwave yourself some food</text>
					<response>After preparing yourself a snack, you caught up on some of your favorite Let's Play videos on LouTube. Those guys can always make you laugh!</response>
					<effect>eatWatch</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Walk around the block</text>
					<response>You decided to walk around the block for a few minutes. You really burned your buns!</response>
					<effect>workOut</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After spending some time to yourself, you notice that the first batch of clothes were done drying. You decide to put the dry clothes away, but you're not entirely sure how to organize them...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Hang the dry clothes on the coat rack</text>
					<response>You walked back and forth between the laundry room and the closet multiple times for hangers and hanging. Who knew hanging clothes into a closet would be so tiring?</response>
					<effect>coatRack</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Fold the dry clothes and put the clothes into the dressers</text>
					<response>Admittedly you weren't good at folding clothes at the beginning... but you got better with every pair of female suit pants you had folded.</response>
					<effect>clothesDresser</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After putting your mom's clothes away, the second batch of clothes were finished drying. Thinking you had some extra time, you could do the laundry for all the towels in the kitchen.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Save those towels for a rainy day</text>
					<response>Not feeling like taking more time with this task, you were able to rest up.</response>
					<effect>energyUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Do some extra laundry</text>
					<response>Since you had some extra time, you got the towels cleaned up. I'm sure your mom would appreciate the effort.</response>
					<effect>moreLaundry</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 11 - Internet Repairman-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Ciao figlio! The TV is playing static, so I called the company to send someone to fix it today. Can you make sure they're able to get into the house? I left some money on the coffee table for a tip."</text>
			<complete>Now that the repairman left, you turned the channel on to your mother's favorite channel and sent her a text saying the TV has been fixed.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying you'll make sure the TV will be able to play her normie television shows.</response>
					<effect>moneyUpM</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy writing Vapor reviews to games that you've play 30 minutes of to help her out.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>The repairman was supposed to come to the house some time in the afternoon with a 4 hour window. Since you had some time to wait, you you get to entertain yourself!</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Goof off on the dating app Cinder</text>
					<response>After swiping left and right on the dating app Cinder (But mostly left because you have high standards for some reason) for what seems like hours, you got a match! You sent her a message with your best untested opener.</response>
					<effect>datingApp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Play some video games</text>
					<response>You decided to play a long-winded open world game. You ended up getting through a decent amount of the game after hours of play!</response>
					<effect>openWorld</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>You noticed that the repairman still wasn't there! This worried you as there was only 30 minutes left in the window of repair.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Call the internet company with your concerns</text>
					<response>You called the internet company to ask on the status update. They said he just finished his last job and is on his way to your house. You felt like a businessman with how you handled that situation...</response>
					<effect>callISP</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Keep waiting! This happens from time to time</text>
					<response>Feeling confident that the repairman will come, you just keep waiting by the window...</response>
					<effect>confident</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Finally, the doorbell rang! You opened the door and let the repairman into your house. He told you that he was caught up in the last job. Thinking he was tired, you offer him a drink.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Offer a bottle of soda</text>
					<response>You offer the repairman a nice refreshing bottle of soda to which he graciously accepts! You feel more refreshed after watching him drink the bottle!</response>
					<effect>offerSoda</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Offer a glass of water</text>
					<response>You offer the repairman a glass of water to which he graciously... declines. I guess he was looking for something more refreshing.</response>
					<effect>offerWater</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>The repairman gets straight to work! He mentions that it shouldn't be too long, they just need to replace and program the cable box. But still, the two of you are in the same room together...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Talk to him about his day</text>
					<response>You made some small talk about his day which switched to a conversation about the places he's been to throughout the day. Being a cable repairman must be tough!</response>
					<effect>socialUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Look at memes on your phone</text>
					<response>Since you are not the best with other people, you save both of you the embarrassment and look at funny memes on your phone. That frog always gets you...</response>
					<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Remembering that your mother gave you some money to tip the repairman. Or you could keep the tip to yourself...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Tip the repairman $20</text>
					<response>You tipped the repairman $20. The repairman thanked you and did all of his tests and signatures then went on to the rest of his day. You felt like a good kid for the hearty tip!</response>
					<effect>tipRepairman</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Keep the money all to yourself</text>
					<response>You decided to keep the money. The repairman did all of his tests and signatures then went on to the rest of his day. You felt bad, but you're $30 richer!</response>
					<effect>dontTip</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 12 - Tend Garden-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Bonjour! I had to leave early today and couldn't water the garden before I left. Could you please take care of that while I'm at work? I left a note with instructions on the fridge."</text>
			<complete>Your mother's plants and vegetables look green and vibrant! It seems like you did a good job today.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying you got this under control - you've played enough gardening simulators.</response>
					<effect>excitementUpL</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're busy spending the day watching 4-year old LouTube videos that you still find hilarious.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>making your way to the fridge for the instructions, why not look at what's inside? You see a bunch of gross vegetables, but you also see some cold leftover pizza and an energy drink...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Grab the energy drink can</text>
					<response>You grab an energy drink and down that bad boy in one massive gulp!</response>
					<effect>takeDrink</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Grab the leftover pizza</text>
					<response>You grab the leftover pizza and eat it in one massive bite... without microwaving it... huh...</response>
					<effect>hungerUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Grabbing the gardening instructions, you head outside. You mother has 3 sections: flowers, fruits, and vegetables. You start off with the flowers. The instructions say spray the flowers 3 times, but you don't know where you're supposed to spray...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Spray the leaves and stem</text>
					<response>After spraying the leaves and stem, you back up and notice how much greener the plants are.</response>
					<effect>content</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Spray the soil</text>
					<response>After spraying the soil, you're not entirely sure if you're doing this correctly, but at least you're having fun!</response>
					<effect>excitementUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Once all of your mother's plants were watered, you read the instructions again and was told to use the hose for the rest. Going to the hose, it was actually stuck under a log. You can try to move it, or get water another way...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Move the log yourself</text>
					<response>You grip the log from the bottom and heaved the log off of the hose. Damn, it feels good to be buff!</response>
					<effect>moveLog</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Fill a bucket with water</text>
					<response>Not wanting to deal with a heavy log, you grab a bucket and fill it with water. It was still pretty tiring, but you are satisfied with your solution.</response>
					<effect>fillBucket</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Once you got around to tomatoes, you were stopped in your tracks. Are tomatoes vegetables or fruit? Since this will probably keep you up at night, you guessed before you pulled out your phone for the answer.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>It has to be a fruit</text>
					<response>After searching far and wide on the internet... tomatoes are actually a fruit! You are a smart man!</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>It has to be a vegetable</text>
					<response>After searching far and wide on the internet... tomatoes are not a vegetable. You bring great dishonor to your family...</response>
					<effect>soaDown</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Thinking you were done with all the watering, you look at the garden from a distance. Maybe you can give them all another spray to make it look greener...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Leave everything as is</text>
					<response>Not wanting to put in the effort, you sat down on the couch to catch your breath.</response>
					<effect>energyUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Give the garden an extra spray</text>
					<response>You decided to give gardening another go and provided a few extra sprays. The garden looks extra green and lively now!</response>
					<effect>secondSpray</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
	</events>
</doc>

<!--
Dismantle and throw old furniture
Fix mom's slow computer
Pick up pills from Pharmacy
-->