<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<doc>
	<events>
		<!--Quest 1 - Grocery Shopping-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Can you please go to the store and pick up some groceries? I left some money for you to use and the shopping list on the counter."</text>
			<complete>Getting back home, you put the groceries away and let your mother know of your success. She told you to keep the leftover money.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will satisfy her needs. You pocket the money and head outside.</response>
					<effect>groceryStart</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy climbing the ladder in a MOBA game go grocery shopping for her.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>You notice that with all this money, you have the option to take the bus. The nearest grocery isn't too far, but options are always good!</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Walk to the store</text>
					<response>Deciding to walk to the store, you burned a few calories.</response>
					<effect>workOut</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Take the bus</text>
					<response>Spending $10 for the fare, you sat in comfort on the bus to the store.</response>
					<effect>transport</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After gathering everything on the shopping list, you realize you have some money left over. You see some magazines about games, PUAs, and anime in the magazine isle...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Buy all the things!</text>
					<response>You place some of the most interesting magazines in your basket.</response>
					<effect>buyMags</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Restrain yourself</text>
					<response>Not caving in to your desires, you decide to walk away from the magazine isle.</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Making your way to the checkout line, you decide to make conversation with the cute cashier...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Compliment her jewelry</text>
					<response>Taking note of the cashier's accessories, you complimented her style as the two of you talked about that while she was checking out your items.</response>
					<effect>compliment</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Talk about the weather</text>
					<response>"Crazy weather, huh?" The conversation died as silence fell upon the two of you. Nice try though!</response>
					<effect>socialUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>On your way out, you notice someone asking for money outside of the store...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Ignore the pan handler</text>
					<response>You looked at your phone trying to seem busy as you walked past the pan handler. You feel the judging stares of everyone around you, but at least you didn't spend your money.</response>
					<effect>paranoid</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Donate some money</text>
					<response>After donating $20, you stopped and talked with the beggar. They had a family to feed, and you're glad that you were able to help someone in need.</response>
					<effect>donate</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 2 - Chores Around The House-->
		<quest>
			<text>"I couldn't do the daily household chores before I left for work today. Could you please finish them before I get back home?"</text>
			<complete>Completing all of the household chores asked of your mother, you looked upon your hard work with pride! You texted her saying you have completed the chores.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will accomplish everything she requires of you.</response>
					<effect>choresStart</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy level grinding in a 20 year old JRPG for an ultimate weapon.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Remembering that your mother's plants needed to be watered every morning, you fill up a spray bottle and start spraying away! You saw a lone bee fly out of the plant.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Swat at the bee</text>
					<response>Pulling out a fly swatter, you were able to sack that sucker! Feeling proud of yourself, you feel like you have vanquished a foe! Like in your anime.</response>
					<effect>swatAway</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Lead it outside</text>
					<response>Taking the passive route, you lead the bee outside.</response>
					<effect>leadOut</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Noticing that the sink was full of dishes, you figured that the kitchen sink was the next stop.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Load up the dishwasher and try to figure it out</text>
					<response>You place the dishes into the machine and fiddle around with the control panel until it started to rumble. Great success!</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Wash the dishes manually</text>
					<response>There's something relaxing about washing dishes. It may have taken longer, but you feel oddly content after emptying the sink from dirty dishes.</response>
					<effect>excitementUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After finishing up with the dishes, you noticed that the garbage was overflowing. You brought the garbage outside and ran into the neighbor walking their dog.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Play with their dog</text>
					<response>You knelt down and pet the dog. You then look up at the owner and start talking them questions about the dog. After a few minutes of talking, they continued on with their walk.</response>
					<effect>petDog</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Talk about upcoming events</text>
					<response>"So uh... there are some events going on in town, yeah?" Your neighbor was stunned at first but was a good sport making small talk with you.</response>
					<effect>socialUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>While outside, you noticed that the lawn hasn't been trimmed in a while. You go to the shed and saw two different lawn-mowers. You remembered that the ridable lawn mower had trouble starting up.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Use the push-blade mower</text>
					<response>You pull out the push-blade mower and decided to mow the lawn manually. It was exhausting, but you feel like you got a good workout from this.</response>
					<effect>workOut</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Figure out how to work the ridable lawn mower</text>
					<response>Spending a good 10 minutes trying to get the lawn mower running, you finally got a response from the engine! You had fun while mowing the lawn because it was like driving a car.</response>
					<effect>ridable</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 3 - Returning Library Books-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Hey, I have some overdue library books that I haven't been able to return. Can you please return it to the library for me? I left $20 just in case the books are overdue."</text>
			<complete>Making your way back home from the library, you texted your mother saying you have accomplished the task! She told you to pocket the money left over.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will make the library your new kingdom.</response>
					<effect>libStart</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy proving your intellectual superiority on plebs on the internet.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Walking to the library with the books in hand, you bring them to the front desk. The librarian seems to be new and asks how long ago you borrowed these books.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Guess the check out date</text>
					<response>Guessing the check out date, the librarian told you that there were late fees totalling up to $5.</response>
					<effect>lateFees</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Say that you don't know the date</text>
					<response>Being honest, you affirmed that you were doing this for your mother and had no idea. The new librarian gave you a pass and you got away with not paying any late fees. However, you felt like you got away with a crime...</response>
					<effect>paranoid</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Deciding that while you were at the library, why not enjoy your time there? Walking further into the building, you passed a vending machine with some really tasty snacks.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Ignore the tasty treats</text>
					<response>You ignored the vending machine and felt good about choosing the healthier option.</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Indulge yourself in snacks</text>
					<response>You spent $5 on a bunch of vending machine snacks.</response>
					<effect>buySnack</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Now in the center of the library, you decide to take a book and read it on a comfortable chair. Which type of book do you feel like reading?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>A book about self improvement</text>
					<response>Feeling the need to improve your life, you grab a self improvement book that teaches readers how to become more social. Once you completed the book, you put the book back where you found it.</response>
					<effect>socialUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Some vintage comic books</text>
					<response>You decided to read up on some old school comics, reading the original origins of some of your favorite heroes. Once you finished a handful of stories, you put the comics back where you found them.</response>
					<effect>vintageComics</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>You noticed that there was a board game room in the library. Noticing another person your age, you decide to talk to them and was challenged to a chess match! How do you play?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Play defensive</text>
					<response>After a very close match, you were able to sneak a victory! Feeling good about yourself, your opponent congratulated you for your victory.</response>
					<effect>chessWin</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Play offensive</text>
					<response>After a very close match, you ended up losing. Speaking with your opponent after the game, they ended up giving you some tips for the next time you two play against each other.</response>
					<effect>chessLose</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>

		<!--Quest 4 - Gift Giving-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Tomorrow is your uncle's birthday and I ordered a gift for him in the mall. Would you be able to go to the store in the mall and pick it up? I left some money on the dining table."</text>
			<complete>After a fun-filled day of malling around, you texted your mother saying you have accomplished the task! She told you to pocket the money left over.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will make her happy. OR DIE TRYING! You pocket the money and walk to the mall.</response>
					<effect>mallStart</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy grooming and tending to your ponies to do such a menial task.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Making your way to the gift shop, you asked if they had the order for your mother. The cashier went to the back of the store to search. What do you do to entertain yourself?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Spin the globe around</text>
					<response>Spinning the globe, you stopped it with your finger and said that you would rule that country first. You continued to do this for a while...</response>
					<effect>spinGlobe</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Look at stock photos in picture frames</text>
					<response>Looking at the stock photos in the picture frame, you started to get introspective about life... thinking about the past, present, and the future...</response>
					<effect>photoLook</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>When the cashier comes back from the storage room, you pay for the gift then head out. Now that you've accomplished what you set out to do, you decide to spend some more time at the mall. What do you want to do?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Go to the arcade</text>
					<response>Deciding to go to the arcade, you played a handful of arcade games even bonding with other arcade patrons in the co-op games.</response>
					<effect>arcadePlay</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Go to the katana store</text>
					<response>Deciding to go to the katana store, you look in awe at the immaculate craftsmanship of the mall blades almost being brought to tears.</response>
					<effect>katanaShop</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After some window shopping you decide to make your way to the food court. Being overwhelmed by all of the food choices, you narrow it down between a coffee shop and a burger place. Which one do you want to go for?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Coffee shop</text>
					<response>You grabbed a coffee and grabbed a seat at the coffee shop. You enjoyed the taste of the coffee upon your lips and people watched for a bit. Somebody brought their desktop and their guitar... weird...</response>
					<effect>coffeeShop</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Burger place</text>
					<response>You ordered a massive speciality burger and devoured it in less than 2 minutes. That was impressive if not a bit scary!</response>
					<effect>burgerPlace</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Deciding that your time at the mall has to end, you head outside. However with you elven eyes, you saw a group of teenagers smoking a cigarette in the distance. However you may be able to change their ways...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Intervene and give them a life lesson</text>
					<response>Not standing by for this, you walk over to the group and gave an anti-drug PSA. Confused at your presence, they asked you to go away. Feeling like you made a fool of yourself, you saw the silver linings - maybe you convinced just one of them to quit smoking.</response>
					<effect>dontDoDrugs</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Let them walk down the dark path that they are heading towards</text>
					<response>Turning the other way, you ignore these troubled youths. Your imagination went wild - what if they started doing harder drugs? You could have saved a life. If only you weren't socially awkward!</response>
					<effect>doDrugs</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 5 - Mail Package-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Hey, I am unable to mail some letters out throughout the day due to work. Would you be able to stop by the post office for me? I left the letters and some pocket money on the table for you."</text>
			<complete>Making your way back home from the strip mall, you texted your mother saying you have accomplished the task! She told you to pocket the money left over.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will mail the package out SO HARD.</response>
					<effect>mailStart</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy feasting upon some tendies and potato chips to help her with her task.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Walking to post office with letters in hand, you suddenly realize that you need to prepare the letters. Mailing letters is one of the many things you're not experienced with but you do know stamps are involved...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Ask the person behind the counter for assistance</text>
					<response>You gave all of the letters to the person behind the counter. They were able to do all the work for you even recommending the cheapest stamps that you needed. Stress free!</response>
					<effect>askForHelp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Pick up some entertaining stamps and do it yourself</text>
					<response>Your eyes were drawn to these colorful stamps from a beloved cartoon show. They were a bit pricy, but at least your letters looked good! You put two stamps on each letter and threw them in the outgoing box.</response>
					<effect>buyStamps</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Deciding that while you were out and about, why not enjoy the fresh air? After all, the comic book store that you work at is in the same strip mall. Stopping by, you see that the store got a handful of new items in stock...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Buy an action figure</text>
					<response>You spent $25 on a cool looking action figure to decorate your room with.</response>
					<effect>buyFig</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Buy a handful of new comic books</text>
					<response>You spent $10 on a handful of newly released comic books.</response>
					<effect>buyBooks</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After making a purchase, a customer thought you were working and asks you for some comic book suggestions. What do you do?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Tell the customer you are not working</text>
					<response>You awkwardly dismissed the customer's request saying that you were not working. However that gave you some extra time to look at all the cool nerd memorabilia your store has!</response>
					<effect>excitementUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Give the customer a list of suggestions</text>
					<response>Choosing to help this customer out, you gave a list of modern comics that focused on one character and gave a list of comic book characters to avoid. It turned out you helped this customer out for an hour and it counted as an hour of work!</response>
					<effect>workDo</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Leaving the comic book store you hear a cheap sounding music jingle nearby. You realize there's an ice cream truck driving by! Should you indulge your desire for sugar?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Signal for the ice cream truck</text>
					<response>Signalling for the ice cream truck, you bought a popsicle the shape of your favorite pony from your favorite cartoon "Ponies in High School" with gumballs for eyes. You felt guilty, but she tastes so good!</response>
					<effect>iceCream</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Ignore the ice cream truck</text>
					<response>Despite wanting a popsicle the shape of your favorite pony from your favorite cartoon "Ponies in High School" with gumballs for eyes, you were able to resist the temptation. Feels good to have control over yourself like that!</response>
					<effect>soaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 6 - Oil Change-->
		<quest>
			<text>"I need to get the oil changed for the car, but I'm stuck at work. Can you please take the car to the mechanic and take care of that for me? I left the keys and some money on the counter."</text>
			<complete>Making your way back home after a few hours of driving a car, you texted your mother saying you have accomplished the task! She told you to pocket the money left over.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will change her oil. You grab the keys and the money and head to the garage.</response>
					<effect>oilStart</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy combing your pony figurines to help her out.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>You hardly ever drive due to your lack of money, so you always cherish every time your mom lets you drive. Backing out of the driveway you realize that you can go to the mechanic one of two ways... the scenic route or the more direct route.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Go the scenic route</text>
					<response>Diving the scenic route, puts your mind at ease.</response>
					<effect>relaxed</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Go the direct route</text>
					<response>Driving for the mechanic, you had to deal with the traffic. Luckily for you, you have a samurai's patience and was able to keep a steady mind like a true warrior.</response>
					<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Dropping the car off at the mechanic's, they took the car to the garage and came back to ring you up. The mechanic suggests that you change your windshield wipers...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Pay for the windshield wipers replacement</text>
					<response>Your total for the wipers and the oil change rang up to $30. Helping your mother out with her wipers brought you a sense of accomplishment and niceness.</response>
					<effect>buyWiper</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Don't change the windshield wipers and keep the money</text>
					<response>Your total for the oil change came out to be $15. Since you didn't buy the wipers, you saved $15 all to yourself!</response>
					<effect>buyOil</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Now that you finished paying, you need to waiting for the services to be complete. Coming prepared, you brought your designated handheld device. However, you also got a text from your equally euphoric friend...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Play video games</text>
					<response>You put away your phone and started playing with the handheld you brought with you.</response>
					<effect>excitementUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Text your friend</text>
					<response>You texted back and forth with your friend for a bit while the service was being done to the car.</response>
					<effect>socialUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>After getting service done to your mother's car, you decide to make a quick stop at a donut shop. Feeling like consuming one of two things, you can choose to buy a cup of donuts or a cup of coffee.</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Buy some donuts</text>
					<response>Chowing down on donut balls never felt so good! Once you completed your donut eating task, you went back home.</response>
					<effect>buyDonuts</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Buy some coffee</text>
					<response>Drinking some coffee never felt so good! Once you completed your coffee drinking task, you went back home.</response>
					<effect>buyCoffee</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
		
		<!--Quest 7 - Prepare House Guests-->
		<quest>
			<text>"Howdy, I'm having house guests over later today for the book club. Could you please prepare some accommodations for our guests in the living room before I get home?"</text>
			<complete>Looking at the living room, you pat yourself on the back for a job well done! This may just be your finest work yet.</complete>
			<step>
				<text>What should you text your mother?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Accept the quest!</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you will clean the living room so hard until it becomes the dead room.</response>
					<effect>houseStart</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Tell her you're busy</text>
					<response>You texted back saying that you're too busy writing your erotic fan fiction series based on an anime from the 1990's.</response>
					<effect>quit</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Starting off, you would like to clean up the living room. After mopping the floors and cleaning the tables, you need to mask the chemical smell with some nice smelling chemicals. You can choose between the two flavors of chemicals - Spring Night Breeze or Beaches and Shores?</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Spring Night Breeze</text>
					<response>Taking a wiff of the Spring Night Breeze you just sprayed reminded you of your youth and how you'd spend your spring breaks immersed in anime, gaming, and sleeping...</response>
					<effect>relaxed</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Beaches and Shores</text>
					<response>Taking a wiff of the Beaches and Shores you just sprayed reminded you of your youth and your summers spent at anime conventions...</response>
					<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Thinking about what needs to be done, you figure that guests need food and drinks. Focusing on food first, your mother baked a pie for the meeing. However, you love your mother's pies! You can swap out the pie with another snack and keep it for yourself...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Put some cookies out on a plate and keep the pie to yourself</text>
					<response>You brought out some cookies for snacks then stealthfully snuck the fresh pie into your room for consumption! Being bad never felt so good.</response>
					<effect>hungerUp</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Put the pie on the coffee table with knives and forks</text>
					<response>With tears in your eyes, you figure that it's for the best you use the pie for its intended purpose. You set up the pie in the living room and never looked back... until you had to go into the living room again.</response>
					<effect>givePie</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Now to make some actual food! Actually you can't cook to save your life, but you can microwave! You can let loose your inner chef and microwave some chips or just set up a box of taquitos...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Microwave some nacho chips</text>
					<response>Feeling like a gourmet cook, you created a bowl of nachos and placed the out in the living room for the guests.</response>
					<effect>makeNachos</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Microwave some taquitos</text>
					<response>You microwaved some taquitos and placed them out in the living room for the guests.</response>
					<effect>makeTaquitos</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
			<step>
				<text>Now focusing on beverages, you looked in the fridge. Admittedly mother dropped the ball and hasn't gone for groceries so all you have in terms of drinks are water and your euphoric Fountain Dew. You can sacrifice your own Fountain Dew or make the guests drink water...</text>
				<choice1>
					<text>Sacrifice the dew</text>
					<response>With great sadness, you sacrificed the dew. But with great sacrifice comes great retribution...</response>
					<effect>sacDew</effect>
				</choice1>
				<choice2>
					<text>Keep the dew to yourself</text>
					<response>Not wanting to part ways with the dew, you brought out some water for the guests.</response>
					<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
				</choice2>
			</step>
		</quest>
	</events>
</doc>
<!--
-Go get some fast food
-buy ingredients for dinner
-->