<doc>
	<random>
		<job1>
			<event>
				<title>Excellent Customer Service</title>
				<text>Taking note of a lost-looking customer, you asked if they needed help finding something. You spent some time helping them with what they needed as well as gave comic book suggestions.</text>
				<effect>ngpUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Chatty Customer</title>
				<text>Ringing a customer up for their order, the customer just kept on talking and talking and talking...</text>
				<effect>socialUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Visit From A Friend</title>
				<text>While slaving away at work, one of your buddies from high school stopped by to purchase some comics. The two of you talked for a little bit.</text>
				<effect>socialUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Overtime</title>
				<text>Before leaving for the day, you noticed a mess in the storage room. You decided to spend some extra time cleaning the room up. You got paid more working overtime.</text>
				<effect>moneyUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Overtime</title>
				<text>Before leaving for the day, you noticed the new shipment of comic books came in. You decided to spend some extra time stocking up the shelves in the store. You got paid more working overtime.</text>
				<effect>moneyUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Office Pizza Party</title>
				<text>Somebody brought in pizza for an office pizza party and left it in the storage room. You took a few slices for yourself.</text>
				<effect>hungerUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Coworker Birthday Party</title>
				<text>A coworker was celebrating their birthday, so the entire store took some time off during a quiet time to celebrate.</text>				<effect>excitementUp</effect>
			</event>
		</job1>
		<job2>
			<event>
				<title>Office Hours</title>
				<text>A struggling student came into your office during office hours. Knowing how difficult the topic could be, you decided to help them out to the best of your ability.</text>
				<effect>ngpUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Office Hours</title>
				<text>One of your favorite students stopped by your office during office hours to just talk about fun, nerdy topics.</text>
				<effect>socialUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Office Hours</title>
				<text>Nobody came in to your office during office hours. Taking this as a good sign, you took a quick nap.</text>
				<effect>energyUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Office Hours</title>
				<text>Nobody came in to your office during office hours. You figured that you did really well explaining the subject matter during the lecture.</text>
				<effect>soaUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Exam Time</title>
				<text>During exam time, you brought a handheld device with you to help alleviate your boredom. After all, you have TA's to prevent the students from cheating!</text>
				<effect>excitementUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Difficult Question</title>
				<text>During a lecture, one of your students asked a difficult question... however you were able to answer their question with confidence!</text>				
				<effect>soaUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Culture Day</title>
				<text>On campus, you noticed that there was some sort of culture event going on. You grabbed some free food at the event.</text>				<effect>hungerUp</effect>
			</event>
		</job2>
		<eat>
			<event>
				<title>Extra Food</title>
				<text>When your chicken tenders came out from the kitchen, you counted two extra tenders! Sweet!</text>
				<effect>hungerUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Socializing</title>
				<text>Minding your own business, somebody asked if they could join you. As it turns out, there was nowhere else to sit.</text>
				<effect>socialUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Free Energy Drink</title>
				<text>While eating your food, you were given a free energy drink in error of the waitress. You did let the waitress know, but she wasn't allowed to take it back. Why not, right?</text>
				<effect>energyUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Chatty Bartender</title>
				<text>While eating your food, the bartender started to talk to you - asking about your day, who you are, what you do... It was a nice conversation.</text>
				<effect>socialUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Hidden Onion Ring</title>
				<text>Digging through your basket of fries, you found a single onion ring. Accidental onion rings are the best onion rings!</text>
				<effect>hungerUp</effect>
			</event>
		</eat>
		<drink>
			<event>
				<title>Drink Special</title>
				<text>After you ordered your drink, the bartender informed you of a 2-for-1 drink special! You made sure you hopped on that sweet deal!</text>
				<effect>excitementUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Socializing</title>
				<text>Minding your own business, somebody asked if they could join you. As it turns out, there was nowhere else to sit.</text>
				<effect>socialUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Chatty Bartender</title>
				<text>While drinking by the bar, the bartender started to talk to you - asking about your day, who you are, what you do... It was a nice conversation.</text>
				<effect>socialUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Extra Cherries</title>
				<text>When your drink was finished being made, you counted a total of three extra cherries!</text>
				<effect>hungerUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Text Message</title>
				<text>While sipping on your drink, you received a text from your friend! It feels good that somebody was thinking about you.</text>
				<effect>socialUp</effect>
			</event>
		</drink>
		<booth>
			<event>
				<title>Socializing</title>
				<text>You got into a conversation about anime with someone at looking through the booth.</text>
				<effect>socialUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Internet Celebrity</title>
				<text>While browsing the booth, you accidentally brushed shoulders with a popular LouTube personality. You can die happy now...</text>
				<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Cosplay</title>
				<text>You saw somebody cosplay one of your favorite fictional characters in the distance.</text>
				<effect>excitementUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Cosplay Selfie</title>
				<text>While looking through the booth, you noticed someone cosplaying as one of your favorite anime characters. You requested a selfie with them.</text>
				<effect>photoUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Free Merchandise</title>
				<text>While looking through the booth, the person running the booth gave you a free pin. That's something you can put on your fedora!</text>
				<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
			</event>
		</booth>
		<photo>
			<event>
				<title>Socializing</title>
				<text>You got into a conversation with the people you were taking a photo of.</text>
				<effect>socialUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Internet Celebrity</title>
				<text>You took a photo of one of your favorite famous cosplayers... You can die happy now...</text>
				<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Cosplay</title>
				<text>You took a picture of somebody cosplaying one of your favorite fictional characters.</text>
				<effect>excitementUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Pretty Girl</title>
				<text>Noticing an attractive woman in a cosplay, you were able to convince her for a photo without acting like a fool!</text>
				<effect>soaUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Free Merchandise</title>
				<text>After taking the photo, one of the cosplayers approached you and gave you a business card to like their MyFace page.</text>
				<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
			</event>
		</photo>
		<travel>
			<event>
				<title>Random Text</title>
				<text>While in transit, you received a text from a friend. The two of you messaged each other back and forth until you reached your destination.</text>
				<effect>socialUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Handheld Gaming</title>
				<text>While in transit, you pulled out your handheld gaming device and did some level grinding while travelling.</text>
				<effect>excitementUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Snacks</title>
				<text>Your mom brought a bag of chips for you to munch on while in transit. They were cool ranch flavored - your favorite!</text>
				<effect>hungerUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Radio Music</title>
				<text>Sitting in the back seat of your mom's car, a catchy song started playing on the radio. You couldn't stop thinking about it!</text>
				<effect>euphoriaUp</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Coffee Run</title>
				<text>Your mother asked if you wanted to stop for coffee. You allowed her to make the stop... if she got you some coffee too.</text>
				<effect>energyUp</effect>
			</event>
		</travel>
		<game1>
			<event>
				<title>Winning Bet</title>
				<text>While playing pool, a group of friends asked if they could join you. To make things interesting, they placed a bet; whoever wins takes home some extra money. After a close match, you came out on top and made some extra money!</text>
				<effect>moneyUpL</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Joined Pool</title>
				<text>While playing pool, a group of friends asked if they could join you as there were no other available tables to play on. You made friends with them as you all played pool together.</text>
				<effect>socialUpL</effect>
			</event>
		</game1>
		<game2>
			<event>
				<title>First Place</title>
				<text>You enrolled in a video game tournament hosted at the convention. Due to your superior skill in gaming, you easily reigned victorious and won $150 as a result. Good work!</text>
				<effect>winner</effect>
			</event>
			<event>
				<title>Semi Finals</title>
				<text>You enrolled in a video game tournament hosted at the convention. You fought your hardest, but you lost in the semi finals. You did win $50 as a result though. Good work!</text>
				<effect>semiFinals</effect>
			</event>
		</game2>
	</random>
</doc>