<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<doc>
	<good>
		<event>
			<text>A group of friends called you over asking you to take a photo of their group. After taking the photo, you then asked them to do a silly one. They enjoyed the photos you took and bought you a free drink as thanks!
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Playing darts on your own, you were challenged to a game of cricket. Wanting to make things interesting, they wager $10. After an intense battle, you came out on top and won the money!
			</text>
			<effect>moneyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting at the bar, a distressed couple left the bar abruptly. A waitress carrying a plate of nachos asks if you saw where they went. After you told her they left, she offers you the plate of nachos instead!
			</text>
			<effect>hungerUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting at a table outside, a drunk girl sat down with you. Since she was new in town, the two of you talked for a long time about places to visit. She ended up adding you on MyFace :D
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Walking through the bar you slipped on a piece of paper. When you got up off the ground, you looked back down to see that it was a $10 bill. You pocketed the money while nobody was looking.
			</text>
			<effect>moneyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Noticing a girl wearing a shirt of your favorite anime, you make your way over and make small talk with her. She opened up to you, and you guys had a blast talking about anime. Before she left she gave you her MyFace information you casanova ;D
			</text>
			<effect>inLove</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You overheard two people in the midst of a heated debate about a popular science fiction movie series. As a huge fan, you couldn't help get a piece of that argument. You ended up settling the argument between the two! 
			</text>
			<effect>content</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>An older bar patron asked you why you're carrying a sword which incidentally led to a more personal conversation. After talking for a while, he gave you some fatherly advice about love, life, and dreams before he vanished into the night.
			</text>
			<effect>motivated</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The TVs in the bar were on a kid's channel playing your favorite show "Ponies in High School"...for some strange reason. After watching it for a few minutes, the bartender changes it. You talked to her and convinced her to leave one TV on your show.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Standing outside, the bouncer stood next to you and made some small talk. He complained about how boring his job is and liked making new friends when he got the chance. I guess that means he's a new friend!
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>There was a bachelorette party in the bar, so you bought the bride-to-be a drink. They asked you for pictures and they gave you a phallic party favor as a reward. Before they left for the night, you wished her luck in the wedding.
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>There was a birthday party at a table near you and you bought a pitcher for the birthday celebrant. You got to meet new people and had a blast drinking celebrating with the celebrant.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>On karaoke night, you chose to do a popular 90's song that everyone was excited for. During the chorus, you got down on your knees and played air guitar during the solo. Once you got off the stage, everyone was cheering you on!
			</text>
			<effect>confident</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting down at the bar, you noticed a bouncer on their night off. He got a pitcher for free, but he didn't want to drink it. He noticed you as a regular and offered to give you the entire pitcher!
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Finding a wallet on a bench outside, you gave it to the bartender saying somebody lost it. Later on, a young man approached you asking if you were the one who gave the bartender his wallet. He was incredibly thankful to you and bought you a drink.
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Being a slow night, the bartender ended up talking to you whenever she wasn't busy serving a customer. You two talked about life, death, and everything in between. You even added her on MyFace! You said good night once the bar got more busy.
			</text>
			<effect>content</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>On karaoke night, you saw a hesitant girl who was struggling to get on stage. Assuring that karaoke is a blast, you offered to perform with her as a back up singer. After the song ended, the two of you bonded over drinks.
			</text>
			<effect>confident</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You joined a team on trivia night and somehow lead your team to second place! It didn't matter much because you had fun with a bunch of new people and even made a little bit of money out of it.
			</text>
			<effect>moneyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You scheduled a date at the bar with a lovely lady on the dating app Cinder. A woman introduced herself to you and the two of you enjoyed getting to know each other over a few drinks.
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, a woman sat down next to you to order her drink. The two of you talked for a while until she went back to her friends. It feels good being approachable! 
			</text>
			<effect>confident</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Working on your dart skills, you noticed that the group using the board next to you were missing the board completely. You gave them tips on how to aim and throw darts. They thanked you as their next throw actually stuck on the board.
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Standing by the pool tables, you saw a group constantly scratching and not hitting anything on the table. You gave them tips on how to properly hit the ball and they started to do better! They offered some of their fries as a reward!
			</text>
			<effect>hungerUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You were minding your own business at the bar until a lady sat down next to you. She asked how you were doing, and you two had a pleasant conversation for a few minutes until her drink was finished.
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The bartender mixed your order up with another customer by giving you an energy drink on the side When the bartender noticed, they let you keep the energy drink for free.
			</text>
			<effect>energyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The bar had an "all your can eat wings" food special. Not one to miss out on such a sweet deal, you took advantage of it and ate wings until you could no longer feel your stomach.
			</text>
			<effect>hungerUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Happy hour just ended but your bartender brought out an extra drink for you despite it being a few minutes after last call. She said that she got your back as she brought it out.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Your eyes were drawn to the sports game on the screen and the blue team scored a point. Everyone cheered as that was the game winning point. A sports fan sitting next to you gave you an unopened beer assuming you were a fan of the blue team. Go blue team!
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Walking to the other side of the bar, you were stopped by a girl thinking you were somebody else. Instead of being weird, you introduced yourself and talked for a few minutes. Hopefully she won't mix you up next time you run into her!
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting at a table outside, a couple asked you to take a photograph for them. Being a photographer, the photos turned out well! The couple looked at your photos and seemed genuinely surprised at how good they turned out!
			</text>
			<effect>confident</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>On karaoke night, you joined a group of friends! Overall the performance was terrible but you guys had fun. Once the song was over, you hung out with them for a bit, talking and drinking some beers.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Talking with the bouncer, he remembered that there was a fedora in the lost and found bin. He offered it to you saying that usually nobody goes to the lost and found anyway. You're not one to turn down free things!
			</text>
			<effect>hatPlus</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting at a table outside, you heard a bark. Filled to the brim with excitement, you found out that somebody brought their dog to the bar. You socialized with the dog's owner as you got to pet the hell out of that dog!
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>In the distance you noticed an old lost-looking lady signalling her over, she asked for directions to a nearby mall. Being as informative as you could be, she thanked you for your help and gave you a tip for helping her.
			</text>
			<effect>moneyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the outside bar, somebody carrying a box of pizza offered you a slice. He was from the pizzeria from next door and was giving some away at the bar to promote his business. Free pizza is the best pizza!
			</text>
			<effect>hungerUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Wanting to play fooseball, you stood by the machine and invited a stranger to join you. The two of you bonded as the fooseball competition heated up!
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>While playing darts, you somehow got your three darts on bulls-eye consecutively. The people around you who witnessed the skilful feat praised you for your talent.
			</text>
			<effect>confident</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You saw a large group at a table with a hookah set in the center. You made your way over and asked if you could have a puff or two. They allowed you to join in as you socialized with them.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The TV over the bar went out. The bartender tried multiple things to fix the issue, but to no avail. You suggested an action the bartender could try to fix it which ended up working! You are a smart man!
			</text>
			<effect>content</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, a man sat down next to you to order his drink. He took note of your shirt and you two started talking about your personal favorite parts of the show.
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>One of your favorite nostalgic songs started playing from the jukebox. You jammed out to it getting others to join in with you.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>A girl with a unique hair color enters the bar. You had to double take because she looked like a character from an anime. You asked if she knew of the anime to which she surprisingly did! Bonding with this girl, you asked to take a selfie with her.
			</text>
			<effect>photoUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You spotted a group in cosplay costumes at the bar. Being curious as to why they were costumed, you discover that there was a convention a few miles away. You asked to take a photo of the group.
			</text>
			<effect>photoUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You noticed a group of people looking up at the ceiling. Looking up, you noticed that somebody accidentally got a dart stuck on the ceiling. Using your sword, you were able to dislodge the dart and returned it to the person playing the game.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Seeing a girl playing pool by herself, you noticed that she was a waitress on her day off. You joked saying it was weird seeing her in civilian clothes. You guys talked about her work and her personal life.
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You were minding your own business at the bar until you felt a hug from behind. The girl was shocked when you turned around: she thought you were somebody else. You said it was fine and how this happens to you a lot.
			</text>
			<effect>inLove</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Reading a comic book at the bar, a girl asked you what you were reading. Briefly describing the comic's story and main character, she seemed interested. You talked about comic books for a while until she returned to her group of friends.
			</text>
			<effect>inLove</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting outside, you noticed somebody looking distressed. Asking what was wrong, they mentioned they misplaced their phone. You asked for the number and called them. Turns out the phone was on a chair by the darts!
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, an older woman sat next to you. She bought you a drink in exchange for conversation. She's going through tough times and just needed to talk to somebody. You're glad to listen!
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You noticed somebody leaving the bar with their keys in hand. Wanting to avoid a potential disaster, you called for a taxi for them. They thanked you before they left in the taxi.
			</text>
			<effect>content</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You saw a girl at the bar with tears in her eyes. Concerned, you asked if she was okay. She vented for a while until she started to feel better to the point that she gave you a hug! You were just glad to help someone in need.
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You ran into a group of coworkers at the bar and chatted with them for a while, mainly venting about work and making fun of people. They bought you a drink before they went on their way.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You ran into your philosophy professor from college and chatted for a while. He asked you how you were doing, even offering to help you find a philosophy job. Before he left, he asked you to keep in touch. You started feeling more motivated!
			</text>
			<effect>motivated</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You ran into someone you knew from high school that you used to have a crush on. You bought her a drink as the two of you caught up for a while. Before she left, she asked you to keep in touch.
			</text>
			<effect>inLove</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>There was a live musician playing at the bar as you walked in. Liking the music she was playing, you gave the musician a decent tip. While she was taking a break, she talked for a bit before she had to get back to performing.
			</text>
			<effect>inLove</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>A professional celebrity look-a-like walked into the bar dressed up as one of your favorite childhood heroes. You had to double take to make sure it wasn't the real actor! Walking over, you were able to get a photo with them.
			</text>
			<effect>photoUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>It was trivia night at the bar. Unfortunately you joined in too late, but you enjoyed answering the questions to yourself. Somebody playing by themselves offered you a beer in exchange for some answers!
			</text>
			<effect>content</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>There was an announcement for bingo night at the bar. Since you were interested in fun things and secretly wanted the prize money, you signed up to play. Half an hour later, you were able to steal the win!
			</text>
			<effect>moneyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Suddenly, you heard the theme song to an anime burst out of your pocket. It was your mother calling you. After your conversation with mom, a girl asked where your ringtone was from because she thought it was really catchy!
			</text>
			<effect>inLove</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting at the bar, you noticed that the person next to you had their glass close to the edge of the bar. They turned around and accidentally elbowed the glass. Being aware of the situation, you caught it without spilling a drop!
			</text>
			<effect>content</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, some drunk business man sat down next to you. He ended up ranting for a long time giving you life and business advice.
			</text>
			<effect>motivated</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting by the bar, the person next to you ordered some mouth-watering food. You asked what they ordered, which turned out to be a good bargain as they let you have a small portion to try out!
			</text>
			<effect>hungerUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Wanting to test out the new jukebox app on your phone, you get one free song for a first time customer. You put on one of your favorite songs for free!
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The bar was playing a highly anticipated boxing match on most of the bar TV's. Not one for sports, you found yourself getting into the fight, even feeling invigorated when there was a good round.
			</text>
			<effect>energyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting by the bar, you noticed two girls with colorful backpacks and logos all over their clothes. They were giving away energy drinks for a new flavor that just came out. Not one to turn down free things, you picked up a can.
			</text>
			<effect>energyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>There was a local rock band performing at the bar. Throughout the show, they had people throw free merch in to the crowd. You won the jackpot as you were able to catch a new hat!
			</text>
			<effect>hatPlus</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The bar was pretty empty so the bartenders played whatever they wanted on the televisions. One of the televisions was playing your favorite movie of all time!
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Standing outside of the bar, someone walking passed smelled the apple cinnamon flavor from your vape. The two of you talked about getting into vaping as you gave him suggestions.
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting at a table outside vaping by yourself, a group of vapers joined your table and made some friendly conversation with you. 
			</text>
			<effect>content</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The bar had a special on food: extra cheap pizza slices. Frugality is one of your best traits as you partook in cheap pizza night!
			</text>
			<effect>hungerUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Somebody noticed you vaping outside and gave you a new flavor. When you tried it out, you started to feel more awake! Just what flavor did they give you?
			</text>
			<effect>energyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting on your own at the bar, you ordered a bizarre cocktail that the bartender never heard of before so she gave you a cute pet name related to it :D
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You walked passed the bouncer and said good evening. The two of you talked for a bit and you were able to make him laugh with some quality jokes you got from the internet.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Walking passed the pool table rental girl, you noticed she looked incredibly bored. So you decided to talk with her to kill some time. However, she started to get really flirty with you :O
			</text>
			<effect>inLove</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Noticing one of your favorite bartenders at the bar on her off day, you offered to buy her a drink. Talking for a while amongst yourselves, the two of you took a selfie together before her coworkers joined in to talk to her.
			</text>
			<effect>photoUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>During karaoke night, you were filled with excitement when you heard the intro to your favorite song! You started jamming out and singing along with the singer on stage.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting outside the bar minding your own business, a girl walked passed you and dropped a rose on your table. You then noticed a rejected looking man follow her only to stop and let her go. Not sure what to make of that, at least you got a free rose!
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>It was open mic night at the bar and there was a comedian going through their act. The comedian was surprisingly hilarious and you enjoyed all of the jokes said that night.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Around the entrance of the bar, there was a table set up where they were giving samples of food and hot sauce that the bar was trying to sell. Feeling the need to feed yourself, you took a few samples.
			</text>
			<effect>hungerUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The bartender offered you to try out their new hot sauce for chicken wings. Not one to turn down a challenge, you partook in the extra spicy wings and felt your heart beat faster. The wings were so hot it's almost like you ran a marathon!
			</text>
			<effect>energyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The bartender told you about an app the bar is trying to sell. Initially being dissuaded, the bartender sealed the deal by telling you that by downloading the app, you get credits for your next purchase at the bar. Free money, woo!
			</text>
			<effect>moneyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, you overheard a drunk patron sitting next to you complained about how hungry they were. Thinking nothing of it, you offered some of yours. They ended up thanking you for your generosity!
			</text>
			<effect>ngpUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You noticed a someone working on their homework at the bar. Noticing that you had knowledge on some of the subject matter, you approached them and offered assistance. They thanked you for your time!
			</text>
			<effect>ngpUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting by the bar, you noticed a waitress walking through the kitchen doors with a massive tray of food. Being quick, you went over and held the door open for her. They thanked you for your kindness.
			</text>
			<effect>ngpUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sipping on some fancy cocktail, somebody sitting next to you noticed how delicious your drink looked and commented on it. Thinking nothing of it, you offered them a taste of your drink. They ended up really liking the drink!
			</text>
			<effect>ngpUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, someone asked if they could take the seat next to you for their group of friends. Offering them the seat next to you, they thanked you for your generosity!
			</text>
			<effect>ngpUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Making your way around the bar, you noticed money sticking out of the jukebox. Somebody must have left it accidentally... so you sneakily grab the bill and walk off before anyone could notice.
			</text>
			<effect>moneyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Standing around outside with your e-cigarette in hand, a random person asked you for a light. You explained that you don't smoke, but the stranger turned the misunderstanding into a pleasant conversation.
			</text>
			<effect>content</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Standing around outside with your e-cigarette, somebody walking by got a wiff of your vape and asked for a taste. Why not? He enjoyed the taste and the two of you talked for a little while.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting by yourself outside, your hat mysteriously vanished. You looked back and saw a girl jokingly wearing fedora. You said that it looks better on her and the two of you talked for a while.
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, you witnessed an incredibly attractive girl walk by and it increased your heart rate. Mamma mia!
			</text>
			<effect>energyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You noticed there was nobody sitting on the leather couch in the lounge. Checking to see if there was anybody already sitting there, you hopped on!
			</text>
			<effect>energyUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting at the bar, the bartender told you about a new food ordering app. She also mentioned that if you use her code with your first purchase, you get the first order for free!
			</text>
			<effect>hungerUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Swiping through the dating app Cinder, you matched with someone! The two of you exchanged a few messages back and forth.
			</text>
			<effect>soaUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting by yourself at the bar, the girl sitting next to you said she couldn't eat another bite and asked if you wanted the rest of her cake. Hell yeah! Free sweet things are the best things!
			</text>
			<effect>hungerUp</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Talking to the bartender, they brought up that they received a shipment of seasonal beer. The bartender then offered you a small sample which turned out to be very sweet!
			</text>
			<effect>energyUp</effect>
		</event>
	</good>
	<bad>
		<event>
			<text>A group of friends asked what your shirt was referencing which got you spewing out a long winded explanation of "Ponies in High School"; everything from your favorite pony pairings to pony conspiracy theories. They interrupted you saying that they had to leave.
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>While practicing darts, you were challenged to a dart-off! You dominated the game and rubbed your victory in their faces. Since they are human, they got peeved with your childish behavior as they call you a bad name and walk off.
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Deciding to practice your pick up artist techniques, you blurted out the first neg you could think of to m'lady: "That dress of yours is stupid, but it's also pretty okay too" and turned your body away from her. She groaned in disgusted and walks off.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You spot a fair maiden at the other side of the bar with your elven eyes. You offer her a drink. When you ask her what she wants, she replies with 4 long islands. Once the drinks come out, she takes them to her group of friends and ignores you for the rest of the night.
			</text>
			<effect>moneyDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You see the girl of your dreams across the bar. She is wearing a shirt with your favorite anime on it. You made your way to her and tried to get her attention by blurting out random facts about the anime. After reciting your 5th fact, she told you to go away.
			</text>
			<effect>heartbroken</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You decided to change the song on the jukebox to some classy jazz music. You overheard somebody complain at the bar's selection of music. You felt bad for ruining a stranger's enjoyment for 3 minutes.
			</text>
			<effect>embarrassed</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You overheard two people getting into a heated debate about a popular science fiction movie series. As a huge fan, you couldn't help but get involved with the argument. You got unnecessarily intense which creeped everyone out.
			</text>
			<effect>emasculated</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Your eyes met with a girl was sitting across from you. You fantasized a perfect conversation starter, which which led to you thinking about your marriage with her and your future children. However she suddenly left into the night...
			</text>
			<effect>heartbroken</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The TVs in the bar were erroneously on the kid's channel playing the show "Ponies in High School". After watching for a few minutes, the channel suddenly changed to sports. You had a temper tantrum and started to cry.
			</text>
			<effect>dishonored</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>While standing outside, the bouncer stood next to you. You panicked and shouted at the bouncer "I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING" and ran to the bathroom to hide. You waited until the bouncer left until you snuck in feeling anxious for the rest of the night.
			</text>
			<effect>paranoid</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>There was a bachelorette party at a table near you and you tried to work on your pick-up artist techniques. You stood in the center of the party not making eye contact with any of the women. They talked poorly of you behind your back as they moved to the other side of the bar.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>There was a sports game on the TV and a bunch of dude-bro plebs were getting rowdy near you. Peeved off, you asked them to lower their low-IQ voices and they told you to piss off. Feeling emasculated, you actually did piss off...
			</text>
			<effect>emasculated</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>On karaoke night, you chose to do a song from your favorite Japanese anime! Everyone boo'd you off of stage after the first few seconds of the song. Some people just don't understand Japanese culture...
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You walked into a guy and he spilled his drink all over you. He apologized and said don't worry about getting him another drink, but you now have to deal with a massive stain on your clothes for the rest of the night.
			</text>
			<effect>discontent</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>While walking across the bar, you accidentally walked into a guy spilling his drink. You had to buy him another drink as a replacement. Unfortunately he got a pricey beer...
			</text>
			<effect>moneyDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, a dishevelled sailor sat down next to you. He asked you if you would be interested in hearing the story of how he lost his hand. Despite your best efforts, you couldn't get out of the conversation as he kept speaking for hours...
			</text>
			<effect>energyDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, a woman sat down next to you to order her drink. Game on! You try to seduce her with your best opener "I would marry you so hard!". She just looked at you with a disgusted face and walked off before she could get her drink.
			</text>
			<effect>emasculated</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, a woman sat down next to you. Game on! However after looking closer, she seemed unkempt. With a raspy smoker's voice she said "Hey stud, you looking for a good time?" You had to pay her money just to leave...
			</text>
			<effect>moneyDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You scheduled a date at the bar with m'lady on the dating app Cinder. Filled to the brim with excitement, you waited at the bar for your date to show up for hours. You then started spamming her messages asking if she was coming, but she never did...
			</text>
			<effect>heartbroken</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You ordered food with some cheese sauce on the side. But they forgot the cheese sauce and you were too embarrassed to bother the waitress. However when the check came in, you still had to pay for it.
			</text>
			<effect>moneyDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>People watching at the bar, you saw a man working his game on m'lady. You got shot down when you tried to seduce her earlier in the night, so you looked forward to seeing him fail! However, the girl let him sit down and they spent the rest of the night talking.
			</text>
			<effect>heartbroken</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>While people watching at the bar, you saw a man and a woman playing pool. You were trying to determine if they were dating, but they caught you staring. You tried to look natural, but you still felt awkward for staring.
			</text>
			<effect>embarrassed</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>It's karaoke night and you chose to do a metal song. The genre didn't matter because 10 seconds into the song, you got stage fright and went into the fetal position in the middle of stage. The DJ kept the song going on and you stayed in the fetal position for the entirety of the song.
			</text>
			<effect>emasculated</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Your sinuses started to act up so you ran to the bathroom to throw up. However, you somehow missed the toilet and puked inside the toilet paper dispenser. Not knowing what to do, you ran away and tried to play it cool.
			</text>
			<effect>paranoid</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, a lovely lady sat down next to you. She asked how you were doing, but you were too shy to say words so you grunted like a caveman. Weirded out, she took her drink and left.
			</text>
			<effect>heartbroken</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You were playing your hand-held video game console at the bar, but then the battery died. Next time charge it before you leave the house...
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>While people watching at the bar, you saw a group of girls minding their own business. You think about approaching them, but decided that they weren't pretty enough for you anyway. Unfortunately, you accidentally said that out loud, and they all give you the dirtiest of looks.
			</text>
			<effect>paranoid</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting alone at the bar, you just thought of a funny event that took place in the past and started laughing. However, you lost control of your butt and ended up farting. You felt everyone's eyes upon you as you hid under your hat...
			</text>
			<effect>embarrassed</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Playing darts by yourself, you noticed that the people next to you were terrible at the game. You decide to give them tips on their darting abilities. However, after 5 minutes of tutelage, you lost your cool and stormed off in a huff.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You bought flowers from the store next door to give it to m'lady. You leave briefly to buy the two of you drinks, but when you returned, you see your flowers abandoned and broken on the table. JUST LIKE YOUR HEART!!!! D:
			</text>
			<effect>heartbroken</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You were minding your own business at the bar until a friendly looking woman sat down next to you to make some conversation. She talked about vacuums so you thought the moment was right and leaned in for a kiss. Evading your kiss, she said that she was a saleswoman and walked off in disgust.
			</text>
			<effect>embarrassed</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Feeling pretty hungry, you decided to order some exquisite bar food. Upon completion of the food, you felt your stomach get hit with something as you had to run to the bathroom.
			</text>
			<effect>sick</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>After closing off your tab, thinking that the bartender was cute, you left her a big tip and your number on the receipt. Thinking you sealed the deal, you were shocked and appalled when you never received a text from her for the rest of the night.
			</text>
			<effect>moneyDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Making your way to the bar, you spotted your favorite waitress walking to your direction. You throw your hand in the air for a high-five, but she didn't notice and walked passed you. You tried to not cry, but you failed spectacularly.
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting outside, you overheard a woman state that she was cold. You walked over and ADAMANTLY insisted that she take your jacket to which she declined. When you got super into it, she ran inside with you following behind her. The bouncer got in the way and told you to leave her alone.
			</text>
			<effect>heartbroken</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, an old man sat down next to you spouting politically incorrect statements about certain controversial topics expecting you to agree with him. It was a long and uncomfortable 20 minutes...
			</text>
			<effect>discontent</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You brought your pony toys with you to the bar to play with them and accidentally spilled beer on them. Especially on your favorite pony! She will forever be unclean...
			</text>
			<effect>heartbroken</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Working on your pick-up techniques at the bar, you walked up to a woman and said "Hi". However, you maintained flawless eye contact. So much so that you were just straight up staring at her without saying anything. She left mentioning that she will never come back to this bar.
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>While playing darts, you somehow missed and broke your three darts consecutively. Feeling like a massive failure, you hid under your hat in shame.
			</text>
			<effect>embarrassed</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Needing to drain the dragon, you made your way to the bathroom. However upon opening the door, you walked in on two young men partaking in some hard drugs. The needles kind.
			</text>
			<effect>discontent</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>From the other end of the bar, you see one of your friends from behind. You decided to go for a surprise glomp! Once the glomp happened, it appears that the person you glomped is not the person you thought he was. Ready to die from embarrassment, you ran to the opposite side of the bar to hide.
			</text>
			<effect>embarrassed</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting at the bar, the person sitting to the left of you complains to their friends that it smells like body odor. It can't possibly be from you! You sprayed yourself with cologne and showered last week. Regardless, you are still worry that it might be you.
			</text>
			<effect>paranoid</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You got blinded by a flash of light aimed at your direction. Is someone taking a photo of you? Or worse: are you making an unflattering face in the background of someone else's photo? You're going to end up being a meme for sure!
			</text>
			<effect>paranoid</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You walked passed a group of people and noticed that they started laughing. Are they laughing at you? What did you do to deserve this judgement! You feel like everyone's eyes are on you.
			</text>
			<effect>paranoid</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Watching the sports game on the television, a drunk guy walked up to you and wanted to start some beef! Despite your fondness of meat, you pointed the other direction and ran away to the bathroom to hide out for a while.
			</text>
			<effect>emasculated</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Wanting to play fooseball, you stood by the machine and waited for somebody to join you. After a long period of waiting, you still stood there not playing the game...
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>After sneezing, somebody said "God bless you" as a response. Wanting to spark a nice intellectual debate, you replied with a "I'm atheist." The person just sighed and left. So much for your intellectual debate...
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You saw a large group at a table with a hookah set in the center. You made your way over and demanded that they provide a puff or two like a real alpha male. However, they were extremely put off by your attitude and told you to go away.
			</text>
			<effect>emasculated</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Seeing a group of girls, wanting to demonstrate your higher value as a potential mating partner, you start talking about how the bouncer is a push-over and how you can beat him in a fight. However you noticed him walking by. Thinking he was going to kick your butt, you hid in the bathroom.
			</text>
			<effect>embarrassed</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You see a muscle-bound "dude bro" preying on m'lady. Coming to save the day, you chime in with a "I don't think m'lady wants to talk to you." M'lady left you and the dude bro. Dude bro replies "Just because you can't get any doesn't mean you should be a cock block, loser."
			</text>
			<effect>emasculated</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You ran into a group of coworkers at the bar, so you invited yourself over. They were making fun of some weird fat guy who wears a fedora all the time. Once you showed up they started looking uncomfortable to the point that they suddenly had to leave. Wait a minute... they were making fun of you!
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You ran into a philosophy professor you had in college at the bar. Feeling desperate for a job, you rushed over to him with tears in your eyes and snot running down your nose begging for a job. Startled and uncomfortable, your professor left leaving you broken on your knees.
			</text>
			<effect>heartbroken</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You ran into someone you used to have a crush on from high school. You readjusted your fedora and decided to seduce her. "Damn, is your body an orphanage?" Before you finished, she walked off in disgust. You chased her shouting the second half of the line, but I don't think it's working.
			</text>
			<effect>heartbroken</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You saw a lovely blonde from behind sitting by herself at the bar. You thought "Game on!" and talked to her. However when she turned to look at you, she was actually 60 years old. She wouldn't let you leave :|
			</text>
			<effect>discontent</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You saw a cute girl wearing an anime shirt. Thinking that you had a lot in common, you really wanted to talk to her. However you never really had the nerve to talk to her until you watched her leave. Damn, that's disappointing.
			</text>
			<effect>discontent</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>After eating some food, you felt pretty gassy. Trying to be discreet, you released some gas in small intervals. However you felt your body take it one stage way too far. Hopefully nobody around you noticed that you soiled your pants...
			</text>
			<effect>deadInside</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You participated in bingo night and aimed for the money prize! You were doing well until a chad stole the win from under your nose. Not one to take losing well, you threw a temper tantrum and cried in the bathroom. You felt like a fool when you returned to your seat.
			</text>
			<effect>embarrassed</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business, a loud Anime opening theme song blasted through your pocket. It was your mom started calling, but you were too embarrassed to answer as you felt everyone's eyes on you. 
			</text>
			<effect>embarrassed</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Some random drunk guy asked you to be his wingman as he pulled you to another table with two women sitting there. Not knowing what to do on the spot, you talked about your favorite cartoon Ponies in High School. The women instantly left as the drunk guy berated you for being a terrible wingman.
			</text>
			<effect>dishonored</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business, you felt somebody pull your fedora off of your head. Despite it being a joke, your first instinct was to shout "REEEEEEEEEEEEEEE!" freaking out everyone in the bar to the point that it got quiet. You froze in the spotlight as your hat was awkwardly place on your head.
			</text>
			<effect>deadInside</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>As your food came out from the kitchen and in front of your face, a random bar goer asked you what you ordered. Intimidated by this beast's insatiable hunger you shield your food and ran away with it. Unfortunately you tripped and dropped everything you ever looked forward to on the ground.
			</text>
			<effect>hungerDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Ready to stuff your face in with food, a group of bar patrons asked you what you ordered. After you gave your answer, they ended up ordering something else. If your food isn't good enough for strangers at the bar, why should it be good enough for you?
			</text>
			<effect>hungerDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Just as you were about to shove your food into your mouth, you were approached by a drunk guy. He incoherently spoke with you for what seemed like ages. When he left, you turned back around to your food. To your horror, it was cold and lifeless on the plate of the bar.
			</text>
			<effect>hungerDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting by the bar, a small child asked you for donations for their softball team's field trip. You initially declined, but the child started crying and guilted you into giving away your money. You swore you saw the child smile deviously as they left the bar.
			</text>
			<effect>moneyDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>There was a local rock band performing at the bar tonight and during the more quiet parts of the song, you shouted "FREE THE BIRD!" thinking you were being hilarious and creative. You weren't. Seriously, you are literally the worst.
			</text>
			<effect>deadInside</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>While waiting on your drink, you overheard two people talking about politics. Feeling the need to assert your intellectual dominance, you joined the debate, insulting their beliefs. Being sick of your presence, they took their drinks and left, leaving you debate-less.
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Feeling the urge to wake up the sheeple, you walked into a random group of people and spouted conspiracy theories about the government and recent events. However they told you to piss off. But your don't even need to use the bathroom...
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting by the bar, you pulled out your vape and took a puff. However the bartender told you that you weren't allowed to vape indoors. But... you need your vape to feel euphoric!
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Wanting to meet your future wife, you were peacocking mad hard. Despite how hard you peacocked, nobody gave you the attention you seeked.
			</text>
			<effect>heartbroken</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>While playing your portable gaming console at the bar, you made a lot of progress but died to a critical hit. Brushing yourself off, you reloaded your last save but to your horror, you lost two hours of progress.
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Someone calls you a bad name for no reason. Unfortunately you didn't have a good comeback and just took it. You proceeded to internalize the insult and your disappointment - possibly for the rest of your life!
			</text>
			<effect>emasculated</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>When you got your bar tab, you noticed that it was way too little. Being such an honest and nice guy, you brought it to the bartender's attention. However, instead of being rewarded, you actually ended up having to pay the correct price!
			</text>
			<effect>moneyDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Feeling the need to alleviate your bladder, you were shocked when you saw that the line was super long. You had to walk across the street just to use the bathroom. By the time you walked back to the bar, you were exhausted.
			</text>
			<effect>energyDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Walking into the bathroom, you opened up a stall. To your horror, somebody has thrown up in the stall earlier in the night. You had to fight the urge to throw up for the rest of the night.
			</text>
			<effect>sick</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>During karaoke night, you heard the intro to your favorite song and was filled to the brim with excitement! However when the person started to sing, they butchered it!
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting by yourself outside the bar, a well-dressed man approached you asking if you had time to discuss their lord and savior. Despite you replying with "No, I do not wish that" the man insisted and talked to you for a long time about his religious views.
			</text>
			<effect>energyDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>While watching the TV, a food commercial comes on. The food that this restaurant was advertising looked so orgasmic that you started to feel hungry...
			</text>
			<effect>hungerDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>It was open mic night at the bar and there was a comedian going through their act. However the comedian was so bad that he failed to get any sort of laughter. You cringed at every joke that was made that evening.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>It was open mic night at the bar and there was a comedian going through their act. However the comedian was a roast comedian used you as a prop for their comedy. He said some very mean things to you!
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You overheard a group of friends talking about how one of their friends just got engaged. You then overheard how old they were... HOW COME PEOPLE YOUNGER THAN YOU ARE ALLOWED TO BE HAPPY!?!?!?!?!?!
			</text>
			<effect>heartbroken</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>It was open mic night at the bar and there was a solo trumpet player playing a song. However the musician spend a really long time on the stage boring the audience to tears. You almost passed out!
			</text>
			<effect>energyDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Noticing a lovely lady dropped her wallet, you called out to her. However when m'lady turned around, you discovered that she was a he! He thanked you for the save, but you still felt bad about it. He had some gorgeous locks...
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Salivating over the food that was just place in front of you by the waitress, before you could dig in, somebody accidentally sneezed in your general direction. You can no longer eat your food as it has been tainted. FOREVER UNCLEAN!
			</text>
			<effect>hungerDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting at the bar, somebody sneezed  near you. As a knee jerk reaction, you accidentally said "God bless you". After the G-word slipped out of your lips, you began to feel sick.
			</text>
			<effect>sick</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting at the bar, somebody sneezed  near you. Somebody replied with a "God bless you" which triggered you. You ended up getting into an argument with them over religion to which nobody won.
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Trying to look cool walking around the bar, you forgot to pay attention to your surroundings and accidentally walked into a wall.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You held the door open for m'lady and tipped your fedora, but she didn't even say thank you. If you were muscular and attractive, she probably would have thanked you... THAT BROAD!
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Minding your own business at the bar, you took note of the song playing in the background. It's a standard 4/4 pop song that's been playing on your mom's radio all the time. It burns your ears!
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Sitting at the bar people watching, you witnessed a muscular chad walk in. Feeling superior intellectually, you smirked to yourself. However, the chad was able to walk up to a girl and talk to her no problem... What does chad have that you don't?!
			</text>
			<effect>emasculated</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Looking through your phone at the bar, you opened up the internet browser and hentai started blasting through the speakers. It was loud, high pitched, and squishy sounding. You felt everyone silently judging you.
			</text>
			<effect>deadInside</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>You noticed from across the bar a woman with bigger than average mammary glands - you couldn't stop yourself from looking! But your eyes collided! She now thinks you're a creep :|
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Wanting to look busy, you unlocked your phone to a picture of a half naked anime girl. As erotic as that is to you, you instantly covered your phone with your other hand in shame.
			</text>
			<effect>soaDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Swiping through the dating app Cinder, you got a matched! You worked on the world's greatest opening line and hit send - but you were greeted with a generic response. She turned out to be a bot.
			</text>
			<effect>excitementDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>Feeling hungry, you wanted to get the attention of the bartender for food. Even though you called out to her, she walked passed you without acknowledgement.
			</text>
			<effect>hungerDown</effect>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>After coming back from the bathroom, you noticed that your chair was not where you placed it... now you're stuck standing.
			</text>
			<effect>energyDown</effect>
		</event>
	</bad>
</doc>